Chapter 656: Anger!

After Zhao Hai had sat down, he immediately felt countless amounts of gazes targeted towards him. Some of these gazes even held great hostility, while some were loathing.

Zhao Hai was very clear about why he was receiving such gazes, it was either because he was Human or he was a Dark Mage. Both conditions were enough to make Elves look at him in a negative way.

It was needless to say that the Elves might even hate Humans much more than the Divine Race. After all, the hatred between the Elves and the Divine Realm happened too long ago. Even if the lifespans of the Elves were more than the Humans, not even them can live for longer than 10 thousand years. Moreover, it was also impossible to remember matters of tens of thousands of years ago.

On the other hand, their hatred for the Humans was quite recent. Although it had happened in about less than a thousand years ago, there were Elves who were still alive from back then. Therefore, the Elves still held a huge grudge against the Human Race.

Additionally, Zhao Hai was a Dark Mage. Dark Mages were the deemed by the Elves to be the most repugnant profession there is. The Elves respected life and loved peace. Although they were were quite fastidious about art, they were even more fastidious when it comes to peace and preservation of life, it was to the point of extreme obsession.

Because of this, the summoning magics of the Dark Mages were seen to be the biggest disrespect to the Elven beliefs. Reanimating a person who was already dead was an insult to life. Therefore, Zhao Hai was not confused about the gazes that were thrown his way.

After they had sat down, the Queen looked at Billy and Zhao Hai, “Patriarch Billy, Patriarch Zhao Hai, I want to know, is Patriarch Billy really telling the truth? Patriarch Zhao Hai, do you have any proof to back your claims?”

Zhao Hai looked at the Queen in annoyance. He didn’t think that the Elves would still be doubtful this far into their contact. However, he still took out the beast skin scroll that was signed by the Dwarves, the Beastmen and the Fishmen. Then he stood up and said, to the Queen, “Read this and you will know.”

The Elf Queen nodded, then she beckoned her hand as an Elf received Zhao Hai’s beast skin scroll and handed it over to the Queen.

The Queen opened the scroll and carefully read the contents inside. She noticed Billy’s and the others’ mark, her face couldn’t help but show surprise.

The Dwarves, the Beastmen, and the Fishmen were huge groups of the Continent. In the past, the Elves also had contact with these races. Only when the Radiant Church instigated the Humans to break the relationships with these races did the Elves come in contact with the others races fewer and fewer times.Only when the Dwarves had dug their tunnel did the Elves have in contact with them.

Although it had been a long time since contact has been made, the Queen can still recognize the unique marks of the other races. These marks were simply unable to be forged. Additionally, Billy was sitting right there, which proves that these marks were indeed real.

After looking at the scroll, the Queen handed it over to the Great Elder before turning her head to Zhao Hai and said, “It seems like Mister is telling the truth. Also, did the Radiant Church and the Dragon Race really occupy the Ocean Waves Dynasty as well as the Lyon Empire?”

Zhao Hai just nodded since there was no need for useless words. He really couldn’t understand why the Queen refused to believe in him. He and Billy had time and time again displayed their sincerity. But after all this time, the Queen was still doubtful, this annoyed Zhao Hai very much.

The Great Elder also looked at the scroll before she handed it over to the Prince. At this time the Queen asked, “And does mister have any plans?”

Zhao Hai nodded and then said, “I do. I don’t think that the Dragons’ action this time was due to pure coincidence. It was possible that they had received a message from the Divine Realm. Therefore, as soon as I leave the forest, I shall go and deal with the Dragons. Their race needs to be eliminated from the continent. Otherwise, we would be placed in grave danger once the Divine Race arrives.”

The Elf Queen looked at Zhao Hai, her eyes shone with interest, making her more attractive than before. The Queen expressed her noble aura as she asked with a serious tone, “Is mister confident in dealing with the Dragon Race?”

Seeing the look on the Queen’s face, Zhao Hai knew that she was thinking about how invincible the Dragons were. It was no wonder that the Queen had her current expression when she heard that Zhao Hai was going to eliminate the Dragons.

Zhao Hai didn’t become polite, he just nodded and said, “I do. I have no choice, after all, the Dragons had controlled the Lyon Empire, essentially halving the entire continent. If we don’t deal with the Dragons, then when the Divine Race comes, they would be able to establish a base in Lyon Empire. Then, along with the Ocean Waves Dynasty, the two of them would quickly take care of the Buddha Empire. After that, they can then focus on attacking the Rosen Empire and the Aksu Empire. And most importantly, the Lyon Empire separates the Dwarves and the Elves. The elimination of the Dragons is required for the future cooperation between the Dwarves and the Elves in dealing with the Divine Race.”

The Elf Queen nodded. At this time, the Prince had also read the beast skin scroll, he curled it and then passed it over to an Elf and had it returned to Zhao Hai.

The Prince looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Then what does Mister require of our Elf Race?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and replied, “You don’t have to do anything. I just want the Elves to know this so that when the Divine Race comes, we could stand side by side in resisting and fighting back.”

But then the Great Elder suddenly said, “And how can you assure our safety? How can we feel relieved when fighting together with you? How can we make sure that you’re not doing this just to enslave us?”

Zhao Hai had already thought about this issue, so with a serious tone he answered, “As long as the Elves is our ally, I, Zhao Hai, shall assure your race’s absolute security. I have the strength to back this up.”

The Great Elder coldly snorted and said, “Do you really believe that the Elven Race would ally with you with just those few words? Aren’t you being too naive?”

At this point, Zhao Hai had gotten angry. Every since him and Billy started their contact with the Elves, the latter had always been dragging its feet. And now, he had come with sincere intent, but the other party was still being like this, not trusting him. This made Zhao Hai fume with anger. He looked at the Queen, the Prince, and then the Great Elder before he said with a cold voice, “I came here in the hopes of forming an alliance with the Elf Race. I was hoping that you would know that your race wouldn’t be excluded from being targets when the Divine Race comes. I’m only here to propose an alliance and not to beg for help. If you ally with us, then only good things would happen to the Elves. When the Divine Race arrives, you would have allies to share the burden of battle with. Moreover, if the Divine Race comes, do you really think that we would be in the mood to enslave the Elven Race?”

Billy was similarly incensed. The Elves might be clueless, but Billy was aware of what Zhao Hai had done in the past few days. He had kept going back and forth to different races just to unite them all. His effort alone was already worthy of respect. The Elves’ completely distrustful attitude truly lit the fuse of this Dwarf Patriarch.

Billy stood up and the looked angrily at the Elf Queen as well as the others, “What do you mean? You still don’t trust Zhao Hai? I had already told you before, besides being a Human, he had become a Foreign Elder to the Dwarves. At the same time, he is also a Foreign Prince of the Beastmen. Moreover, he is also in extremely good graces with the Fishman. Is this status still not enough for the Elves? Are you looking down on us?”

Dwarves have their own temper, and it was not easy for them to hold back for a long time. Zhao Hai has been regarded well by Billy. In this case, how could Billy tolerate the Elves’ distrust of Zhao Hai? This was akin to the Elves being distrustful to the Dwarves.

The Elf Queen frowned, she also thought that the Great Elder’s words were somewhat improper. In fact, the Elves had already investigated the words coming from the Dwarves and the Queen was already willing to form an alliance with Zhao Hai. however, she didn’t had the means to make a decision because the Great Elder has been opposing to it all this time. This was the reason why this matter has been dragged on for so long.

The Queen understood why Zhao Hai and Billy would get angry at the Great Elder’s words. She already trusted Zhao Hai and Billy. Even if she had doubts about the Human, her suspicion didn’t extend to the Dwarf. The Elves had been in contact with the Dwarves for a long time, so the Queen was aware about their temperament. The Queen can affirm that the Dwarves wouldn’t just help the Humans to deal with an enemy if the reason was not fully investigated through.

But at this time, the Great Elder once again coldly snorted and said, “And why would I trust a human? Even if he is the Foreign Elder of the Dwarves as well as a Foreign Prince of the Beastmen, he is still a Human. Also, the Dwarves have been living easy because of the Elves. And you count yourself as our equal? Completely laughable!”

When he heard the Great Elder’s words, Billy’s face expression turned completely dark. “So it turns out that the Elves are the saviour of the Dwarves? Hahaha. This is the most ridiculous joke that I had ever heard. We have it easy? Just from those artworks that you make? Our Dwarven ironwares are famous all over the continent. At the same time, we Dwarves also have no problems when it came to food and clothing. On the other hand, you Elves have been using your products in order to trade for supplies from my Dwarf Race. Now, I must ask the Great Elder, what days did the Elven Race have before we came in contact with you? Now, after we Dwarves came, how much did your quality of life improve?”

Chapter 657: A Suspicious Great Elder

Billy wasn’t incorrect, the reason why the Dwarves were living well even until now was their ironware. And with how the Buddha Empire exhibited their prowess, Dwarven ironware has been known to be the best all around.

On the other hand, even if Elven wares were expensive, their rate of production was just pitifully low. If it weren’t for the Dwarves, the Elves wouldn’t have ample living materials. After all, there was no way to get in contact with the Elves, nor was it easy to interact with them. Among the races in the continent, it was the Elves that were the hardest to approach.

When the Great Elder heard Billy, he didn’t know what to say, but this also made her angry. The Elder had always thought that the Elves were the most noble race in the continent. This was because the Elves were the most beautiful, had the longest lifespan, and were able to make the best artworks. This fact made the Elves very proud, to the point that they looked down on the other races. In fact, the Dwarves were too crude in their eyes. If they didn’t need to trade for living necessities, then they wouldn’t have come in contact with the Dwarves.

The main reason of this thinking was the fact that they were not in contact with other races. They had always thought that they were the most noble while always staying inside their kingdom. They were like frogs inside a well, thinking that the sky was the only one that existed.

At the current time, there were still a lot of Elves who had this mentality. After all, they hadn’t come in contact with the outside world. This cause them to gradually have this attitude of self-importance.

The Queen was aware of this quality, but she didn’t have the means to change it. This was because the Elves cannot come in contact with the Humans. At the same time, they also see the Beastmen to be quite dangerous. In all honesty, the Queen was feeling quite helpless with regards to this matter.

One shouldn’t see the Queen as the one who managed the entire Elven Kingdom. With both the Prince and the Great Elder to decide matters with, the Queen felt powerless. It was just unfortunate that the Elves always had this type of governance.

Normally, the Queen and the Prince should have a more intimate interaction with each other, after all, the Prince was the Queen’s husband. However,  the Queen’s current situation was a bit special. Although they were husband and wife, the Prince was actually the son of the Great Elder. That is to say, the Queen was actually the daughter-in-law of the Great Elder. Since the Prince grew up in the care of the Great Elder, everything was done in accordance to the Great Elder’s decision. Therefore, when a matter arrives, it was always the Great Elder and the Prince who would come into a unanimous decision. If it weren’t for the Great Elder, the Queen wouldn’t have allowed Zhao Hai’s matters to reach this point.

When the nearby Prince saw that Billy was berating the Great Elder, he immediately became angry, he stood up and pointed to Billy and said, “Rude! How dare you disrespect the Great Elder! Apologize immediately.”

Billy turned his head to the Prince, he coldly snorted and said, “Me, being rude? Isn’t that something that I should say to you? Don’t forget, I am the Patriarch of the Dwarven Race, a position that is equal to your Queen. Meanwhile, you’re just a Prince, what gave you the authority to scold me? Who do you think you are?”

The explosive temper of the Dwarves was quite famous in the continent. At this point, Billy couldn’t stomach the Elves’ attitude of always having their noses turned to the skies. Billy’s politeness had already run out.

Zhao Hai looked at the Great Elder and the Prince, he couldn’t understand how the matter reached this point. Why were the Great Elder and the Prince having these reactions?

They came to the Elves this time to offer an Alliance, not to ask for anything. Moreover, it was an alliance to fight shoulder to shoulder when the Divine Race came. In this case, why was the Great Elder in opposition to this? What exactly was he thinking?

Zhao Hai was frowning while looking at both the Great Elder and the Prince. It might be an illusion, but Zhao Hai saw that when Billy and the Prince quarrelled, the Great Elder had a flash of happiness in her eyes.

An alarm suddenly sounded inside Zhao Hai’s heart. He can remember the time when the Beastmen were being brainwashed by the Radiant Church. Was it possible for the Church to brainwash an Elf? Was the Great Elder brainwashed by the Radiant Church?

But Zhao Hai changed his mind. If this was really the case, that the Great Elder was a person of the Radiant Church, then she would’ve already told the Church about their plans. But from the response of the Church, it seems like they still weren’t aware of his plan. This made Zhao Hai doubt his initial suspicion.

When the Prince heard Billy, his handsome face turned red. He unsheathed the sword on his waist and pointed it towards Billy, “Apologize, otherwise, face death!”

Billy looked at the Prince coldly and said, “Letting me apologize? Keep dreaming. If you want to fight me, then bring it on! Let’s see who survives to the very end.”

Since he came to see the Queen, Billy didn’t bring any weapons. However, Dwarves were never afraid of a fight. Even if they were killed, they wouldn’t just go down that easily.

The Queen frowned and said, “Gaye, that’s enough. Don’t forget, Patriarch Billy came were politely. Don’t be disrespectful.”

Just as the Queen finished talking, the Great Elder suddenly said, “How could it be disrespectful? We still haven’t formed an alliance with them. They just want us to be in an alliance with them so that when they can slowly enslave our race once again.”

Zhao Hai looked at the Great Elder, he was still quite suspicious towards her, but he didn’t express it. He just turned to the Great Elder and said, “I’ll have to disagree with that, Great Elder. After all, your combat prowess won’t reduce when you become our allies. At that point, how could we possibly enslave you? Moreover, are you confident in resisting the attack of the Divine Race? Will you be safe by yourselves?”

The Great Elder coldly snorted and said, “Even if we surrender to the Divine Race, at least we won’t be treated as slaves.”

When Zhao Hai heard the Great Elder, his pupils couldn’t help but shrink. His eyes flashed a cold light and said, “How can the Great Elder be sure that the Divine Race wouldn’t enslave you? If the Divine Race was not planning to enslave you, then why did the Elves joined the war against them a long time ago? How can the Great Elder make her current judgement? Has the Great Elder been in contact with the Radiant Church?”

After hearing Zhao Hai speak, the entire hall suddenly turned quiet. All the Elves present were looking at the Great Elder.

The Elves weren’t stupid, in fact, they were more intelligent than the Dwarves or the Beastmen. It was only because of their beauty as well as the plot of the Radiant Church that they were unable to come in contact with the Humans. One must know that in the past, during the time where the Elves were still in contact with the continent, there were a lot of big Merchants who were Elves. At the same time, there were even some Elves who held high-ranking position in the various nations. This was ample evidence for the Elven intellect.

Zhao Hai’s question immediately made the Elves inside the hall find something wrong. Zhao Hai’s trip was done in pure sincerity, he didn’t even make the Elves leave their forest. He also didn’t say that the Elves would have to listen to his command. He only came to propose the alliance to the Elf Queen, and to express his idea of fighting together against the Divine Race. In this case, the Great Elder’s reaction was truly overboard. Especially when she said that they would just surrender to the Divine Race, this made the Elves doubt her words.

The Great Elder also discovered that her mouth had slipped, but she didn’t surrender and steeled her resolve, “Correct, a person from the Radiant Church came. They were very sincere in their visit and told me that as long as the Elves help the Divine Race control the continent, then they would guarantee the safety of our race. They also assured me that the Elves would continue living inside the Elven Forest.”

Zhao Hai looked at the Great Elder and said, “How come the Great Elder believed their promise while doubting mine? I am a Foreign Elder of the Dwarves as well as a Foreign Prince of the Beastmen, my status should be a match for the Radiant Church. May I know then why?”

The Great Elder looked at Zhao Hai and then sneered, “That’s an easy question, did you realize who you are Zhao Hai? You’re a Dark Mage. How could you be credible when you don’t even respect the dead? I would never believe you. I might as well believe a Light Mage than a Dark Mage.”

When the other Elves heard the Great Elder, humming discussion was suddenly heard inside the hall. It was clear that they approved of the Great Elder’s view.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but couldn’t smile and said, “Being respectful to people? Great Elder, can you really be this naive? Do you know the reason why the races became like this? Do you know why the Elves were turned into slaves by the Humans? Do you know why the Humans suddenly loathed the other races when they were initially peaceful with them? May I know whether the Great Elder had thought of these questions?”

The Great Elder coldly snorted and said, “It is because of how greedy the Humans can be. Therefore, they suppressed the different races of the continent. What further thinking does this need?”

Zhao Hai sneered, “The reason why I claimed that the Great Elder is being naive was because the Great Elder seemed to not have recognized the core of the matter. The reason of the current situation was due to the fact that the Human records have been changed. In the past, history books of the Humans depicted the Dwarves and the Beastmen with a positive light. Although the Beastmen loved to fight while the Dwarves had shallow temper, they were still written to be good people. On the other hand, the Elves were also regarded quite well. Nor only are Elves seen as gentle, they were written to be intelligent as well as people who loved art. All these descriptions were worthy for the readers to respect the races.

The Elves in the hall couldn’t help but nod, even the Great Elder nodded. Then Zhao Hai looked at everyone and said, “But later on, some people revised the contents of the Human books. In this revision, the Beastmen turned from being brave to being ruthless barbarians. The Dwarves had turned into being with unreasonable temper. But since the Elves had zero negatives to their attitude, they were written to be races who had nothing else but beauty. The Humans were slowly influenced by these books and suddenly changed their attitude towards the other races, and before long, they were suppressing them. Does the Great Elder know who revised the records?”

Chapter 658: Rebels

The Great Elder couldn’t help but stare when she heard Zhao Hai. Although they have their own records, the Elves’ history only recorded how the Humans have suppressed them, it didn’t record the reason why. Because of this, the Elves had always blamed their suppression and enslavement to the greed of Humans. Now that Zhao Hai expressed this matter, things suddenly seemed to be not so simple.

The Great Elder looked at Zhao Hai and said, “And do you know who did it?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Yes, I do. The Humans aren’t like the Elves or the Dwarves who always had peace with each other. Due to the ambitions of the Humans, they weren’t able to unite internally and even had multiple cases of war. This made it hard to preserve Human history and extremely easy for someone to slip in some revisions. And there is an organization that can easily do it in the past, and it was the Radiant Church.”

It was not only the Elves who were startled with Zhao Hai’s words, Billy was the same. All of them stared at Zhao Hai, waiting for him to back his own words.

Zhao Hai looked at everyone and said, “The Radiant Church had existed way before all of us thought. They were just being extremely low-key, only becoming slowly formidable in the recent several hundred years. Before the church officially rose, they were sending their priests to various battlefields in the continent and offering help to injured soldiers as well as affected commoners. This allowed the Radiant Church to accumulate universal praise from everyone. Some time after that, the nations in the continent started to trust the church with the responsibility of being in charge of the Human records. It was at that point that the Church started to revise the history books of the Human Race. Humans suppressing the various races was caused by this revisions by the church. In their edition of Human history, the other races of the continent were lesser beings, they made Humans feel disgust in interacting with these lesser races.”

Everyone stared at Zhao Hai, they have not heard about this before.

Then Zhao Hai continued, “In the Radiant Church’s revision, the Dwarves, Beastmen, and Fishmen were lesser beings that were diseased and should not be mingled with. It was said that anybody that came in contact with these races for too long would turn into the same lesser being. This made the Humans stray away from the other races. However, the Radiant Church came into a problem when it came to the Elves. The Elves were perfect in Human standards, there were no negative things to pin on them. Therefore, the Radiant Church wrote that the Elves were historically high-quality slaves. In this way, the Humans would enslave the Elves, which in turn, made the Elves loathe the humans. And now, Great Elder, you actually believed such words from that organization. Hahahaha. This should be the funniest joke that I have ever heard.”

When she heard Zhao Hai, the Great Elder’s expression suddenly changed. With a paled face, the Great Elder retorted, “This is only based on your own words, who knows if they are true or not.”

Zhao Hai gave the Great Elder a cold look before saying, “The Great Elder still doesn’t believe me? Right, I forgot to ask, I believe Patriarch Billy had included the matter where I repaired their Divine Artifact in the letter that he sent. I can repair your Divine Artifact as well. The Artifact Spirit of the Dwarves already told us the reason why they fought with the Divine Race, this was not only because they want to enslave you, but it was also because the God that you worshipped is in opposition to the God that the Church idolized. For the Church to rule this continent, the God that needed to be worshipped should only be the Radiant God, not the individual Gods of the races. Once everyone believed in the Radiant God, the other Gods would lose spiritual support, which would allow the God of the Radiant Church to eliminate them. Oh Great Elder, trusting the Radiant Church is akin to trusting the Radiant god, this also meant that you are betraying your God of Life. I don’t know if the Great Elder is aware of this.”

The Great Elder’s face turned dark when she heard Zhao Hai, she couldn’t bear sitting still as she stood up and glared at Zhao Hai, “Nonsense! Complete nonsense! Do you really think that we’ll believe you just because you told us that you can fix our Divine Artifact? You’re completely talking nonsense!”

Zhao Hai looked at the Great Elder and coldly snorted, “I can fix your Divine Artifact. There’s no need to deceive you with this, just hand me your Divine Artifact and you’ll know then whether I can fix it or not.”

With a berating tone, the Great Elder shouted, “And why would be hand our Divine Artifact over to you? Who knows, maybe you’ll steal our Divine Artifact away.”

Zhao Hai looked at the Great Elder’s reaction and became sure that the Great Elder was a chess piece that the Radiant Church had sent inside the Elven Race. Otherwise, she wouldn’t have these responses. He had always spoken with sincerity. If one weren’t a person of the Radiant Church, then they wouldn’t have reacted like this.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but sneer at the Great Elder’s claims, “Great Elder, your accusations are not very pleasant to hear. Moreover, if I really intended to steal your Divine Artifact, then there’s no way for you to stop me. And there would be no need for me to do about it in a roundabout manner.”

At this moment, the Prince who hadn’t spoke for quite some time, loudly said, “Complete nonsense! And for daring to snatch my Elven Race’s Divine Artifact, you deserve to die!” Then he stabbed his sword towards Zhao Hai.

Nobody thought that Gaye would act like this. After seeing Gaye’s action, the Queen immediately shouted, “Gaye, stop!” However, it was already too late, Gaye’s thorn sword was already close to reaching Zhao Hai.

One must know that Gaye was an Elven Great Warrior who was outstanding in both the harp and the sword. There was no need to mention about his strength, Gaye was a talented Elf, being peak 8th rank strength despite being relatively young. In addition to the emphasis of speed in Elven sword techniques, Gaye’s attack was no less than a sneak attack. Gaye wasn’t far from Zhao Hai, so a short time after his words just fell, his sword was already at Zhao Hai’s throat.

Billy’s face changed completely, although he was near Zhao Hai, he still couldn’t block Gaye because of his lack of weapon. But even so, Billy still roared as he aimed his fist towards Gaye’s head. He wanted Gaye to abandon his sword strike in order to dodge the punch. [1]

However, it seems like Billy had underestimated Gaye’s strength. Gaye’s sword was extremely quick, so he didn’t care about Billy’s punch since he knew that he could still dodge the punch right after he killed Zhao Hai.

But at the same time, Gaye also had underestimated Zhao Hai’s strength. While the sword was heading towards his throat, Zhao Hai didn’t even move an inch. Instead, he looked at Gaye with a contemptuous gaze. Gaye felt that something was wrong when he saw this gaze, but it was already too late to retract his attack. Gaye hardened his resolve as he accelerated his stab towards Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai didn’t make a move as Gaye’s sword reached his sword. Upon seeing that the sword was about to puncture through the other party’s throat, Gaye revealed an elated expression. He thought that Zhao Hai was dead. But it didn’t take a long time before Gaye noticed that there was no stabbing feeling on his sword. Instead, he heard a ‘ding’ sound before his sword stopped moving further.

Gaye stared, then he saw that Zhao Hai’s throat had turned into a crystal. While Gaye was in a daze, Zhao Hai had grasped his sword, which turned it into a crystal as well. Then when the sword crystallized, Zhao Hai made a small twist, shattering the blade into pieces.

Gaye was startled, he immediately loosened his grip on the sword as he used his toes to propel him backwards, dodging Billy’s punch as well. Then he returned to his chair as he grasped hold of his harp.

But at this moment, Zhao Hai made a move. He appeared in front of Gaye and grasped his neck. He raised Gaye with only one arm as he coldly looked at him and said, “You want to kill me? Is it because I have spoken the truth?”

Gaye’s throat was seized by Zhao Hai, making it hard for him to breath as his face turned red. He looked frightened at Zhao Hai. He didn’t think that Zhao Hai would be this strong. Moreover, he had expected that Zhao Hai was a Mage, he didn’t imagine that Zhao Hai was also a very formidable Warrior.

At this time, the Great Elder and the Queen responded. The Great Elder angrily shouted as she wielded her Magic staff and began casting a spell at Zhao Hai. Then Zhao Hai coldly snorted as an incredible pressure began to burst out from his body. Although Zhao Hai cannot use his God-rank strength, his 9th rank power was still something that the Great Elder couldn’t endure. This was when the Great Elder discovered that Zhao Hai was actually a 9th rank expert.

Zhao Hai looked at the Great Elder with a cold gaze, “Great Elder, I’m afraid that the situation isn’t as simple as you being approached by the Radiant Church. I think you are a person of the Radiant Church itself.”

The Great Elder’s face was struggling right now, it seems like she was holding on with all she had, “You talk nonsense. Don’t think that since you are a 9th rank expert, you can tell anything you want. Don’t think that my Elven Race doesn’t have a 9th rank expert as well.”

Zhao Hai actually smiled faintly and said, “Elf friend, you had been observing for quite some time. Why don’t you come out and see me.”

Then just as Zhao Hai’s voice fell, an old sigh was heard, “My Elven race has truly been unfortunate, we’ve made a joke out of ourselves in front of Mister. I’ll be honest to Mister, I had also just recently discovered that she is actually a person from the Radiant Church. Mister, rest assured, I already snatched her letter for the Radiant Church. I just wanted to see what moves they’ll do next. I just didn’t think that she would betray her own race. Sigh, this is really a huge misfortune to my Elf Race.”

Along with this sound, an old Elf walked into the hall. After this Elf appeared, every single Elf in the room stood up and bowed to the Old Elf, “We have seen the Supreme Elder.” [2]

The Old Elf nodded and the turned to Zhao Hai, “Mister, I ask you to please put him down. We will surely provide you with a satisfactory response.”

Zhao Hai loosened his grip on Gaye, then he turned to the Old Elf and bowed, “The Supreme Elder is too polite. This is an internal matter of the Elves, and since I’m a Human, then I will surely hand this matter over to you. I just came here to offer an alliance. How about we resume this matter tomorrow?”

The Old Elf returned the bow and said, “We apologize to Mister. Then, Mister, please.” Zhao Hai and Billy gave a salute to the Old Elf before they both left the hall.

* * *

And since Billy is a Dwarf, it could be described as an uppercut. xD

Like any other elder, but her/his robe just had the Supreme logo in it xD

Chapter 659: Supreme Elder

After seeing that Billy and Zhao Hai had left the hall, the Old Elf then turned to the Great Elder and Gaye before he lightly sighed and said, “Ever since we received Patriarch Billy’s first letter, I had always been paying attention to the entire Tree of Life. Since I don’t want things to be known to the Radiant Church and don’t want to hinder our chances in dealing with the Divine Race, I have intercepted every letter that came out.”

The Great Elder’s face couldn’t help but get pale when she heard the Supreme Elder. Gaye’s face was quite ugly as well, this was because they had indeed been sending letters to the Radiant Church all this time.

The Supreme Elder looked at the Great Elder and Gaye, “Although I always thought that doing this was nonsense, our records pertaining to the Divine Race was indeed too terrible, so I still made an effort. However, I just didn’t expect to find those letters addressed to the Radiant Church. And even if they were encrypted, I can still make sense of some of those words. I didn’t think that there would be traitors in my own race.”

Then the Supreme Elder stared coldly at the Great Elder, “So what made you betray your own race, your own beliefs? Tell me.”

The Great Elder looked at the Supreme Elder, her eyes flashed with fear. However, this fear was immediately replaced by fanaticism, she loudly declared, “The God’s will is everywhere, and you all should surrender to the Radiant God. It is your privilege to serve under him. God is omnipotent, God is all powerful. God will lead us to the shining light!”

The Supreme Elder looked at the Great Elder’s expression and his face sank. Then a ray of light came out of the hands of the Supreme Elder and entered the Great Elder’s body. The Great Elder pitifully groaned out before her body collapsed on the floor.

Then the Supreme Elder turned his head to Gaye and did the same thing, Gaye cried out before collapsing. Then the Supreme Elder turned his head to the Queen and said, “I have crippled their cultivation, take them away.” The Queen nodded, then she immediately had people drag the bodies of the Great Elder and Gaye away.

At this time, everyone in the hall was paying attention to the Supreme Elder. Similarly, the Supreme Elder scanned the hall and then said, “Our race’s history is divided into two parts; one part is accessible to everyone while the other can only be read by our race’s 9th rank experts. In the records, the Ark Continent had been subjected into a war against the Divine Race. Our Elven race is a main force during that war, the Dwarves and the Beastmen were main components as well. There was also the Mermaid Clan and some Human 9th ranks that joined. However, a lot of the Human 9th ranks were also on the side of the Divine Race along with the Dragon Race. The war was incredibly fierce, and in the end, the Elves, Dwarves, and Beastman’s Divine Artifacts managed to wound the God-ranked expert, driving him back to the Divine Realm. In that fight the Divine Artifacts of the three races were seriously damaged. The Beastman Race’s Beast God Spear was heavily injured, the Dwarven Race’s Iron Hammer was similarly wounded, only our Elven Race’s Bow sustained light injuries. At one time, the Elven Bow’s Artifact Spirit managed to materialize for a short time, informing our ancestors about the war with the Divine Race. After that, the Artifact Spirit fell into a deep slumber.”

The Elves in the hall were very silent as they listened to the Supreme Elder. They were completely unaware that there was another part in their race’s history.

The Supreme Elder looked at the people present and said, “Just like what Mister Zhao Hai said, the Radiant Church’s God in the Divine Realm is in a hostile relationship with our own God. This made them send people to deal with us, and wanting to control the entire Ark Continent, enslaving all of the races in the process. They will treat us as livestock, and when our strengths reached a sufficient level, they would send us to the Divine Realm and join their army. Basically, the Divine Race wanted to turn the Ark Continent into a soldier producing factory. Because of this, the major races in the continent decided to resist the Divine Race. Mister Zhao Hai did nothing wrong. And we will establish an alliance with him to deal with the incoming Divine Race.”

No Elf in the hall dared to oppose, all of them simultaneously nodded. The Supreme Elder nodded and the turned his head to the Queen and said, “You have done well all these years. You shall go form an alliance with Mister Zhao Hai tomorrow. Mister Zhao Hai came here in person despite being a 9th rank expert himself, this is already giving us a huge face. Discuss this matter with him yourself. At the same time, deliver the Elven Bow to Mister Zhao Hai and ask him to help us fix it. If Mister can fix our Divine Artifact, then it would be good for our race. I suspect that there are more traitors within our race. When the Divine Artifact gets fixed,  finding those rebels would be easy.” Then the Supreme Elder scanned the hall as if looking for the traitors present.

The Elves in the hall felt their backs to be coldly sweating. Even if they haven’t betrayed their race, the Supreme Elder’s gaze alone made them feel guilty.

The Queen immediately nodded in reply. The Supreme Elder also gave her a nod before turning around to leave. After the Supreme Elder left, the Queen looked at the other Elves and said, “Alright, everyone can go back. Make sure to manage your subordinates well. This is a special period in our race. While the Divine Artifact is being fixed, nobody is allowed to leave the Tree of Life.” The Elves nodded before they stood up and left the hall.

After the group left, the Queen found herself weak as she sat on her chair. She didn’t feel great at all. Of the two who were captured, one of them was her husband while the other was her mother-in-law.

At this time, Gellar walked in and went towards the Queen, “Mother, what just happened? Why were Nana and Father dragged away?”

The Queen looked at her and sighed. Then she told Gellar about everything that just happened. Gellar looked at the Queen, her expression as though she couldn’t believe it, “Mother, are you telling the truth? How could that be possible? Why would father betray our own race? Why would Nana side with the Radiant Church?”

The Queen shook her head and said, “I also don’t know. I have lived for many years with your father, but I still didn’t notice that he is a person of the Radiant Church. At the same time, your Nana has lived here for her entire lifetime yet nobody noticed that she was a traitor. If mister Zhao Hai didn’t come here, then we wouldn’t have known about it for a long time.”

Gellar looked bewildered at the Queen, she didn’t know what to say. There was really no way to explain this matter. The Great Elder had lived with the Elves for her whole life, even to the point of being the Great Elder. She did her best for the betterment of the race and also hated the Humans to the bone. It was because of her qualities that she managed to attain her current position. But who would’ve thought that she would actually be a person of the Radiant Church.

The Queen looked at Gellar and sighed. It wasn’t only Gellar, the Queen couldn’t accept what happened as well. But since there were still matters that needed to be process, the Queen looked at Gellar and said, “Gellar, make sure to take care of Mister Zhao Hai’s group as much as possible. There shouldn’t be any mistakes. I shall deliver the Bow to Mister Zhao Hai tonight. At the same time, I shall also ask him why the Great Elder and Gaye would betray us. I think he knows the reason why.”

When she heard the Queen’s instructions, Gellar immediately nodded, then she turned around to leave. In the Elven Race, the children were always more closer to their mothers. This was because the Elves were a matriarchal race. The key positions of the government were mostly handled by women. Because of this, Gellar didn’t have much of a connection to Gaye. But no matter what, Gaye was still Gellar’s father. This matter made Gellar sad, she didn’t understand why her father would do such a thing.

When Zhao Hai and Billy returned to the room that was arranged for them, Billy immediately looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, were the Great Elder and Gaye really sent by the Radiant Church?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “The Great Elder is for certain, however, Gaye might not be. Gaye is the Great Elder’s child, so it was possible that it was the Great Elder who educated him about this since childhood. Therefore, making Gaye exhibit such actions. The Great Elder was brainwashed by the Church while Gaye was brainwashed by the Great Elder.”

Billy knit his brows and said, “Maniac, she’s really a maniac for doing this to her own child.”

Zhao Hai sighed and said, “This is in line with the Church’s philosophy. These people were avid devotees of the Church. For the Church, they would give up everything they have.”

Billy frowned, “That 9th rank elder clearly saw Gaye attack you. So why didn’t he stop it? What happens if you weren’t a 9th rank expert?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I don’t exhibit my 9th rank aura, so that’s why you can’t notice it. However, other 9th ranks would surely be able to feel it, so he just let it be. I just didn’t expect the Supreme Elder to be so thorough. It was great that he had confiscated the Great Elder’s letter when he found out. Otherwise, our plans would’ve been in trouble.”

Billy frowned and said, “Right, we were too careless this time. Fortunately, they did things very carefully. It would be terrible if our plans were to be known to the Radiant Church.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he sighed and said, “I thought that since the Elves have isolated themselves from the world, then the Radiant Church would not have the opportunity to get to them. We weren’t careful enough and underestimated the Church. The Radiant Church has been preparing their plans for countless years, their moves might always be out of our expectations.”

Billy nodded, then he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, is the story about the Church changing history true? Is that the reason why the Humans started to suppress the other races?”

Chapter 660: Fixing the Elven Bow

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I also wasn’t aware of this matter before. But when I went to the Fishmen, I discovered that their history was much more complete. It was them who told me about this matter.”

Billy’s expression calmed down as he said, “Radiant Church, truly vicious beings. Up until now, we still haven’t understood why the Humans have suppressed us. As it turns out, it was the Radiant Church’s plan all along. We must completely destroy them, all of them!”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Patriarch, don’t worry, we will surely have the opportunity to do that, we certainly will. Sooner or later, we will come in contact with the Church, at that time, we will deal with them ourselves.”

Billy coldly snorted, he knew that he couldn’t be anxious about this. In any case, there would be an opportunity in the future. Zhao Hai looked at Billy and said, “Patriarch, what do you think would happen to the Great Elder and Gaye?”

Billy snorted and said, “They shouldn’t be let off easily. Except for the Humans, other races treat treason as a major crime.”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but sigh. What Billy said was true, whether it be Dwarves or Beastmen, or even the proud Elves punish rebels quite severely. This was something that differed from the Humans. In the continent, there were many Human Empires. And the Humans on those Empires had more sense of belonging to their own Empire compared to the entire Human Race.

At this time, Gellar arrived. Zhao Hai and Billy discovered that Gellar’s expression wasn’t the best, but they didn’t say anything about it. Gellar accompanied the people who delivered them some food to eat. Elven diet was quite peculiar, they mostly don’t eat meat, giving priority to consuming fruits and vegetables. Therefore, there were a lot of fruits and vegetables in the food that was presented to Billy and Zhao Hai. There was a staple food that seemed to taste like the bread fruit, but it didn’t have a hard outer shell, and it was also shaped like a horn.

Zhao Hai wasn’t disgusted by the food, but Billy was different. The Dwarves liked to eat meat, so when he saw the spread on the table, he couldn’t help but lose appetite.

After the food was set on the table, Gellar gave Billy and Zhao Hai a bow and said, “Please enjoy our food. If you need anything, just shake the bell on the table and someone will come and listen to your requests.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Thank you, Miss Gellar. The food looks delicious.”

Gellar gave another bow and then seemed to have some words that she wanted to say. But in the end, she didn’t say it and just turned around to leave. Zhao Hai noticed her hesitation so he smiled faintly and said, “Miss Gellar, wait. Do you have anything you want to say? Please, don’t hesitate to tell us.”

When Gellar heard Zhao Hai, she couldn’t help but stop. She turned her head to Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, I just want to ask, why did the Great Elder and the Prince betray the Elf Race?”

Zhao Hai stared, he didn’t think that Gellar would ask this question. He looked at Gellar and asked, “Why would Miss Gellar ask about this matter? What relationship does the Great Elder and the Prince have with you?”

Gellar’s face paled slightly as she answered, “The Great Elder is my Grandmother while the Prince is my Father. If mister Zhao Hai knows the reason, please do tell me.”

Zhao Hai and Billy stared, they didn’t expect that the person in front of them was an Elven Princess. While looking at Gellar, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but sympathize with her, he sighed and said, “I have a guess, but it doesn’t mean that it’s true. It is highly possible that the Great Elder was a spy that was sent by the Radiant Church a long time ago.”

Gellar was confused at what Zhao Hai said, this was because Zhao Hai said that the Great Elder was sent by the Radiant Church. This was completely different from the Great Elder betraying the Elven Race.

Zhao Hai looked at Gellar and continued, “There has been a long standing plan of the Church to abduct the children of major races and brainwash them, making loyal believers of the Radiant God. They will transform those children into people who would give everything for the Church’s deity. After brainwashing those children, they would then send them back to their races, effectively infiltrating the races. I have come across a similar situation back in the Beastman Prairie. Therefore, I thought of the possibility of the Great Elder being one of these abducted children. As for Gaye, he is the son of the Great Elder, so it is possible that he was educated by the Great Elder from a very young age. But all of these are my guesses, I cannot assure you that it is real.”

Gellar’s face was quite pale while listening to Zhao Hai, she looked at the other party and said, “So Mister means that the Great Elder was taken away by the Radiant Church when she was young, then they sent her back after brainwashing. All of this just to deal with the Elven Race? However, why does the Great Elder seem extremely passionate in serving our race?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “There’s nothing wrong about that. Since your race is extremely sealed off, there was no opportunity to send information back to the Radiant Church. Therefore, she did the other method, work hard and gain a high rank. After that, she would then get access to the core of the race and get more secrets to send in an opportune time.”

Gellar and Billy nodded, this was a highly probable case. The Great Elder was in a position above tens of thousands of Elves. If she wasn’t discovered by the Supreme Elder, then the alliance would have failed. This was something that made spies extremely scary.

Gellar bowed to Zhao Hai and said, “I thank mister for dispelling my doubts. Then I wouldn’t be disturbing Mister’s meal any longer.” Then she bowed towards Billy before turning around to leave.

After Gellar left Zhao Hai’s place, she immediately looked for the Queen. Then she told the Queen about what Zhao Hai had told her. After listening, the Queen immediately thought that this wasn’t a simple matter. So she immediately went to the Supreme Elder and told him.

After telling this to the Supreme Elder, the Supreme Elder’s expression turned cold, then he turned to the Queen and said, “What do you plan to do next?”

The Queen replied, “I suspect that there are more spies aside from the Great Elder. The Great Elder had been in her position for many years, and she had also gained a lot of loyal followers that we need to deal with. I plan to send the Divine Artifact to Patriarch Zhao Hai today. If Patriarch Zhao Hai can really fix the Elven Bow, then the matter would be taken cared of easily. If he can’t, then I’ll have to ask the Supreme Elder to act. We must thoroughly check every Elf inside the tree.”

The Supreme Elder nodded, “This is truly a matter that needs to be looked at. The Radiant Church’s spies in our race need to be completely weeded out. Your Majesty, we should establish our alliance with Mister Zhao Hai as soon as possible. There are only benefits that we can get out of it. At the same time, have the Elves stop making artworks and have them make more weapons. In the fight against the Divine Race, artworks wouldn’t be very useful.”

The Queen nodded, then she turned around to leave. The Supreme Elder sighed, he was worried about the future of the continent. The Divine Race has been preparing for tens of thousands of years. Their strike should be as swift as a thunderbolt, will the Continent be prepared for it?

Zhao Hai wasn’t thinking about any of these right now. At this point, he was already finishing up the food along with Billy. To be honest, these Elven fruits and vegetables weren’t completely unpalatable. However, they weren’t very good as well, they were too bland. With no seasoning, there wasn’t any taste to be amazed about.

On the other hand, the wine that the Eles made were very good. While the two were sitting and chatting, an announcement was suddenly heard, “Her Majesty has arrived!”

Zhao Hai and Billy stared, but they immediately stood up. At this time, the Elf Queen had her men open the door before she walked in.

The two immediately gave the Queen a salute, then the Queen returned the gesture and said, “Patriarchs, please sit down. I’m here to ask Mister Zhao Hai for help.” Then she waved her hand as Gellar brought a longbow in.

This longbow was green, and seemed to be made out of a kind of crystal. It had a vine twining on its body and a single leaf on its top. On the other hand, the bowstring was something that Zhao Hai couldn’t identify. It was not thick, and was even fairly transparent. If one wasn’t paying attention, then they wouldn’t notice its existence.

The Queen extended both of her hands and received the bow, then she lifted it towards Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, this is our Elven Race’s Divine Artifact. We ask Mister to try and fix it.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I will certainly offer my help. I ask Your Majesty to rest assured. However, it would require an evening’s time. By tomorrow, Your Majesty would be able to know if I was able to fix it or not. I also hope that Your Majesty sends word that nobody is to disturb me tonight.”

Naturally, there was no need for the Queen to decline. So she immediately replied, “Mister, don’t worry. I will have people assigned to keep the surroundings peaceful. Patriarch Billy, I have arranged a separate room for you. What do you think?”

Billy understood what the Queen meant, she was afraid that Billy would disturb Zhao Hai. This was a natural worry, so Billy nodded and said, “I understand, then I shall take my leave.” The Queen expressed her gratitude to Billy before she lead the Dwarf Patriarch out of the room, leaving Zhao Hai along inside.

Zhao Hai didn’t immediately head to the Space, he just sat there and carefully examined the Elven Bow. The bow arm was made out of a kind of crystal, and it was evidently quite tough. On the other hand, the bowstring was not only hard to pull, it was also quite sharp to touch. It seems like if one wanted to use this bow, special techniques would need to be learned first.

After examining for some time and finding out nothing, Zhao Hai then took the Elven bow to the Space. The moment he entered the Space, a prompt was heard, “Damaged item detected, proceeding to repair it. Repair has been completed. Subduing the spirit. Unique Crystal has been discovered. Extracting the crystals properties. Improving the host’s crystallization technique.”

Chapter 661: The Radiant Church’s Backup

When Zhao Hai heard this prompt, he couldn’t help but stare. He didn’t think that the Elven Bow would actually give him some advantages.

However, the surprise didn’t end there. At this moment, another prompt was heard. “Thread made out of special material has been detected. The silk thread was made out of variant spider silk. It is very tough. Extracting the silk’s properties. Enhancing the Host’s combat suit. Cuffs has been added to the suit, these cuffs can spew out web in order to tangle the enemy.”

Zhao Hai was shocked this time, wasn’t this function too familiar? Wasn’t this Spiderman’s ability?

Zhao Hai shook his head and didn’t think about it anymore. In any case, the Space was already quite bizarre, so it would not be surprising for these things to happen. The Space itself has Spiderman’s suit, so it wasn’t strange that its function was added to Zhao Hai’s own suit.

Zhao Hai lowered his head and looked at the Elven Bow. He wanted to see what its Artifact Spirit looked like. At this time, a green light suddenly flashed from the bow as a person slowly floated out of it.This figure was very different from Iron Hammer and Bloody War. The figure was actually lying down, when her appearance completely materialized, she yawned and then slowly sat up, just like how an ordinary person would act after being woken up from sleep.

Zhao Hai was curiously looking at this Artifact Spirit. She wasn’t wearing the traditional Elven Robes, but was wearing a tight fitting suit instead. This gave her a martial aura. At this moment, the Artifact Spirit was also looking at Zhao Hai.

The Artifact Spirit sized Zhao Hai up before she bowed and said, “Green Vine has seen Master Zhao Hai.”

Zhao Hai was sizing her up as well, “You’re called Green Vine?”

The Artifact Spirit nodded,” Yes Master, I was named Green Vine.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Just call me Young Master. What are you made of? Why do you seem to be different from Iron Hammer and Bloody War?”

The Artifact Spirit smiled faintly and said, “Answering the Young Master’s question. Bloody War and Iron Hammer are made in Ark Continent. When their masters became God-rank, they were then brought to the Divine Realm, only then did they become Divine Artifacts. On the other hand, I was made in the Divine Realm, so I was made using the materials there. This made me different from Bloody War and Iron Hammer.”

Zhao Hai nodded, no wonder he didn’t get any benefits when fixing Iron Hammer and Bloody War. So Green Vine was actually made in the Divine Realm.

After this thought passed through his mind, Zhao Hai’s heart was suddenly moved. If Green Vine being made in the Divine Realm gave Zhao Hai benefits, then does it mean that there were materials in the Divine Realm that can’t be found in the Ark Continent? If that was really the case, then it would be great to visit the Divine Realm to take a look.

Levelling the Space in the Ark Continent had become very difficult. The most recent boost of level that it had received was from the lotus, but that thing has some sort of a relationship with the Demon Realm. It seem like if Zhao Hai wanted to upgrade his Space, then he would need to visit either the Demon Realm or the Divine Realm.

Zhao Hai looked at Green Vine and said, “Green Vine, are Divine Artifacts divided into levels?”

Green Vine nodded and said, “We are indeed graded. Iron Hammer and Bloody Ware are low-level artifacts. I am classified as an intermediate-level artifact. There are also high-level artifacts. High-level artifacts are very formidable, but they were also difficult make. Because of that, there were very few high-level artifacts in the Divine Realm.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he asked Green Vine about the previous war against the Divine Race. What Green Vine said was the same as Iron Hammer and Bloody War’s testimonies, so there was no need to ask for more details. After that, Zhao Hai instructed Green Vine to protect the Elf Race and also to refrain from calling him Young Master when they leave the Space.

Since Green Vine had surrendered to the Space, then she would naturally follow Zhao Hai’s orders. Then Zhao Hai sat inside the living room and opened the monitor. He wanted to see the current developments in the Elven Race.

After having rested inside the Space, Zhao Hai returned to his room in the morning. After opening the door, Zhao Hai noticed that there were people outside. Zhao Hai wasn’t surprised about this since this was just the Queen’s procedure. She was afraid that people would come and disturb Zhao Hai.

At first, Zhao Hai thought that this method was unnecessary. However, when he thought about the situation yesterday, he thought otherwise. There were still some traitors among the Elves. If it weren’t for the Queen ordering martial law, then they would’ve already approached Zhao Hai’s room.

At this point, Zhao Hai was no longer worried about the rebels. Now that he had fixed the Elven Bow, everything would be taken care of.

Divine Artifacts were truly mysterious enough that they can detect traitors among their race. This was something that wasn’t unique to Green Vine. Bloody War and Iron Hammer were capable of doing this as well.

After seeing Zhao Hai open the door, the people outside immediately loosened their expression. Gellar, who was the leader this time, walked forward and gave ZHao Hai a bow, “Mister, you’re out. Was Mister successful?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and then handed the Elven bow over to Gellar and said, “I’ve succeeded, please take it back to Her Majesty.”

Gellar stared at the bow as it was transferred to her own hands. Then she looked at ZHao Hai and said, “In behalf of the Elves, I express our gratitude. Mister must be tired, please have a good rest. I shall have someone prepare you a meal. When Mister wants to eat, just send words and they will serve it.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Thank you, Miss Gellar. Then I shall be taking my rest.” He gave Gellar a salute before he returned to his room and closed the door.

Actually, Zhao Hai had already rested yesterday, so he didn’t need any more rest. He just wanted to show that fixing the bow took a lot of effort, so he pretended to be tired and returned to his room. After that he entered the Space and opened the monitor to see how the Elves react to the fixed Elven Bow.

Gellar took the Elven Bow to the hall where the Queen was waiting for news. The Queen went sleepless throughout the night as well. At this moment, Gellar came in, holding the Elven Bow on her hands. The Queen couldn’t help but stand up and looked at Gellar. Gellar immediately gave her report, “Mother, he succeeded. Mister Zhao Hai succeeded!”

The Queen looked at the Elven Bow and then let out a long breath. At the same time, her two eyes shined as she quickly arrived in front of Gellar and respectfully received the Elven Bow. Then she turned around to leave the hall, she needed to see the Supreme Elder.

In the Elven Race, the Supreme Elder wasn’t the only 9th rank expert. There were other 9th rank elders as well, there were more than 20 of them.

Today, all of these 9th rank elders convened. They attached great importance to the news of whether the Elven Bow has been fixed or not.

The Queen took the bow to the cavern where the Supreme Elder and the others were. This tree cavern was very big, but there were no decorations inside, only a large empty space. Inside the cavern were several straw mats where the various 9th rank elders were sat down.

The Queen stopped before these 9th ranks and then respectfully bowed and said, “Reporting to the Supreme Elder, Mister Zhao Hai had fixed the Divine Artifact.”

Then the Supreme Elder’s voice was heard, “Your Majesty, please come forward.” The Queen complied, and the took the Elven Bow forward.

There was a bow frame in the middle of this huge cavern and the Supreme Elder was standing right next to it. After the Queen arrived by the Supreme Elder, she immediately placed the Elven Bow on the frame before she respectfully drew back to the sides.

Among these 9th rank elders, the oldest one of them went forward. She was also wearing the same green robe while she had a magic staff on her hand. She bowed towards the Elven Bow and said, “We request Sir Artifact Spirit to come out!”

Then Green Vine slowly came out of the bow. She looked at the Elves and nodded, “Good, I have slept for many years, it’s good to see that the strength of the Elves has recovered. Mister Zhao Hai already told me of what’s happening outside. It seems like the Divine Race is planning to attack once again. I also told Mister Zhao Hai that we would be making an alliance with them to jointly deal with this enemy. Does anyone have any other opinions?”

The Elves present doesn’t dare to oppose, all of them simultaneously said, “We don’t dare, we follow what the Divine Artifact decided.”

Green Vine nodded, then she knit her brows and said, “Why do I feel the aura of the enemy in the bodies of our clansmen? What is this all about?”

When she heard Green Vine, the oldest Supreme Elder replied, “Your Grace, this is the Radiant Church’s conspiracy. They have brainwashed some Elven children and sent them to infiltrate the Elven Race. We had already caught two spies yesterday. However, we weren’t able to find the others. We ask Sir Artifact Spirit to help us in weeding them out.”

Green Vine nodded, then she looked at the Supreme Elder and said, “This isn’t a problem. But after discovering them, what did you do?”

Then the Supreme Elder hesitated for a moment before replying, “Your Grace, we waster their cultivation. What is Your Grace’ opinion on this?”

Green Vine actually snorted and said, “Stupid! These people cannot remain alive. I can feel the aura of the Divine Realm on their bodies. It seems like they weren’t just simple spies sent by the Radiant Church. Their bodies have been altered using a special method, sealing God-realm energy within them, something that all of you cannot detect. As long as a Divine Race expert arrives, they can just activate that seal and release the energy inside. That explosion would have the same power as a 9th rank expert. So how could you just leave them be? If the Divine Race came and released that energy, then what would you do? Have you thought about this?”

Green Vine’s words made the expressions of these Supreme Elders change. The didn’t think that the Radiant Church would have this kind of backup plan. Even if the rebels’ cultivation were wasted, they can still explode, at that point, the Elves would be doomed.

The Supreme Elders were sweating at the thought of this. The oldest Supreme Elder immediately bowed to Green Vine and said, “Sir Artifact Spirit, we know what we should do! ”

Chapter 662: Preparation Begins

Zhao Hai was currently sitting on a boat while looking at the beast skin scroll on his hand. In fact there was nothing special about the scroll. The only change in it was the Elven Race’s mark.

The Elven Race had proceeded with their operation, weeding out more than 100 spies. This made the Elf Queen furious. She didn’t’ think that there would be this much rebels inside her kingdom. The Queen was terrified of the thought of these people exploding with the might of 9th rank experts.

At this point, Zhao Hai had acquired a new status, the Elven Race’s Foreign Elder. But Zhao Hai didn’t care much about it. Now that the alliance with the Elves have been dealt with, then the next plan can start. It was time to take care of the Dragon Race!

Billy was right by Zhao Hai’s side when he read the scroll. Billy couldn’t help but laugh and said, “Now you’ve become a Foreign Elder of the Elves. I believe that you have the most unique status in the whole history of the Ark Continent.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “All of it was due to the current situation. Otherwise, I wouldn’t have been able to gain these many titles. I can say that things have gone smoothly this time. Not only were we able to help the Elves fix their artifact, we also helped them weed out their traitors. Now we can proceed to the next step.”

Billy looked at Zhao Hai and said, “The Dragon Race?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Right, the Dragons, they need to be eliminated. Their current position is very significant to the state of the Continent. We can’t wait for too long, they need to be gone. I have this feeling of dread, it’s as if something is about to happen in the continent. You must be careful.”

Billy nodded and said, “Be relieved, we will be extremely careful. The same applies to you as well, be sure to take care of yourselves. After all, you’re facing against the Dragon Race.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I’m going to be fine. I can assure you of this.” Billy was also quite aware of Zhao Hai’s methods, so he was not that worried about his security.

Five days later, they had finally arrived back at Dwarf Mountain. After resting with the Dwarves for a day, Zhao Hai left. He was ready to deal with the Dragons.

Although Zhao Hai had been with the Elves and Dwarves in the past few days, he was not being idle. He had Cai’er control the Blood Ghost Staff to monitor the Dragons inside Lyon Empire.

Aside from Lyon Empire, Zhao Hai also had the staff fly towards Accra Mountain to see the situation there.

Dragons were claimed to be invincible by the Continent, so Zhao Hai didn’t want to just go in without ample preparations. Fortunately, as long as the map has been collected to the Space, then the Space can monitor the Lyon Empire and the Accra Mountain at any time.

For many years, there were hardly any Dragon sightings in the continent. All this time, the Dragons have stayed inside Accra Mountain, treating it like their own kingdom. They also had a lot of magic beast and lesser dragon subordinates. Dealing with them would be as hard as attacking any other Empire.

Zhao Hai’s plan was to first head to the Lyon Empire and deal with the Dragons that were stationed there. After that, then he’ll go on an attack Accra Mountain.

Zhao Hai didn’t inform the other nations about his plans and only revealing it to the Dwarves, Fishmen, Elves, and the Beastmen.

Zhao Hai wasn’t afraid of any leaks pertaining to these races, this was because the numbers of the traitors in them were very few. Moreover, some of them also have their Divine Artifacts that can detect any rebels among their race. At the same time, it would be impossible for the Radiant Church to infiltrate the Fishman Race. This was because their situation was very special. Even if 9th ranks were to go there, then people would immediately spot them. It was impossible for any Radiant Church spy to evade the eyes of the Mermaid Clan.

When Zhao Hai left the Dwarf mountain, he immediately went to the Space. In the past few days, Laura and the others had been paying attention to the movement of the Dragons. Although the Dragons had controlled the entire Lyon Empire, they still needed to get the recognition of its citizens. Although Humans were easily tempted to go against the Lyon Imperial Clan, it was still quite difficult for them to accept the Dragons as their rulers.

The Dragons were truly formidable, but one shouldn’t forget that in Human eyes, they were still magic beasts. It was impossible for Humans to accept a magic beast to be their rulers.

But it was clear that the Dragons were prepared for this. They already controlled a lot of Noble clans, and with the help of these clans, even if the people weren’t comfortable in being ruled by Dragons, they still weren’t able to make a fuss.

There were 40 Dragons in the Lyon Empire’s capital. Ten of these 40 Dragons were 9th ranks while the other 30 were just a tad bit below. But even if these 30 weren’t 9th ranks, they can still fly, so their threat was no less than the 9th ranks’.

Beside these 40 Dragons, the Lyon Empire’s capital also had about 5 thousand lesser dragons guarding it. These lesser dragons also had their own magic beast mounts. The fighting power of the lesser dragons were around 6th or 7th rank while their magic beasts were 6th ranks. This force was also something that one shouldn’t take lightly.

In order to ensure his success, Zhao Hai spent some time in the Space to fully map the territory of the Lyon Empire. He wanted to see if there were other Dragons in other parts of the Empire.

Sure enough, in the Lyon Empire’s border with the Rosen Empire and Buddha Empire, Dragons were present inside the towns as well. They might now be numerous, but their lesser dragon army were still able to drive away the attacks of the Rosen and Buddha Empire.[1]

After Zhao Hai returned to the Space, he immediately called Kun and Green over to the Space. Then together they discussed how to deal with the Dragon Race.

Zhao Hai showed the full map of the Lyon Empire, then he turned to Green and Kun, “Grandpa Green, Grandpa Kun, the Dragons have garrisons on these places. Which of them should we attack first?”

Zhao Hai had referred to four spots, these four spots were indicated by green dots on the monitor. They were the Lyon Empire’s garrison, the Rosen Empire’s border, the Buddha Empire’s border, and the surroundings of Accra Mountain where a lesser dragon army of 2000 was also situated in.

Green looked at the map and thought for a moment before saying, “With the number of troops in our hand, I think it wouldn’t be hard to attack multiple of them at the same time. I think we should separate our troops and attack the borders of the Rosen and Buddha Empires first. Eliminating those two armies would only take about one evening. Moreover, we need to make sure that those Dragons don’t escape. After that, we’ll wipe out the Dragons in the Lyon Empire’s capital. Lastly we’ll have our army charge towards Accra Mountain.”

Kun nodded and said, “I agree to Green’s plan. Our undead troops are in high enough number that even the Fishmen wouldn’t be able to make a move. So it should be fine if we split them up. Moreover, we have the advantage of being able to increase our numbers the more we fight. The only thing we need to do now is to inform the Fishman and have them destroy the Radiant Church’s navy so that they wouldn’t be able to send any help towards the Dragons. I’m not too worried about the Dragons in the capital, after all, we have the capability to completely clean them up. At the same time, those loyal to the Lyon Empire has already been eliminated when the Dragons took control. Therefore, those who were left behind were those Nobles that sided with the Dragons.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “It’s time to resolve the problem in Lyon Empire. Then it is decided, tomorrow we will act.”

Kun nodded. After the Space has been upgraded, it was now possible to place an army anywhere on the map. This made their tactics much more flexible. However, Zhao Hai still wanted to make a quick move. It was necessary to remove the Dragons before the Nobles were able to act. It would be better if they didn’t get into a fight with the army of the Nobles.

In all honesty, Zhao Hai really didn’t want to fight those Noble armies. In any case, they were still Humans. Later on, when the war happens, they may even be another force that can resist the Divine Race.

After completing the plan, Zhao Hai rested well. However, Green and the others were still staring at the screen. They wanted to see what the Rosen and the Buddha Empires were doing.

SInce they weren’t aware of Zhao Hai’s plans, the Rosen and Buddha Empire didn’t have any movements. They were still fully alert against the Dragons. They wouldn’t dare take the Dragons too lightly.

The day passed quickly while the people in the continent continued to live their peaceful lives. The army of the Dragons were also stationed in their camp. They weren’t afraid of the Rosen and Buddha Empire. In their minds, as soon as their identities as Dragons were revealed, no one in the continent would dare to attack them.

The Dragons had always been aloof while in Accra Mountain. Even the lesser dragons had found themselves being able to move sideways in the mountain.[2]

Due to being subjected to this environment, the lesser dragons had become quite arrogant. Although their current population wasn’t a lot, their status in the Lyon Empire was actually very high. Even ordinary lesser dragons would dare to be disrespectful towards the Nobles of the Empire, they wouldn’t even take the effort to give a salute. There was needless to say when they meet a commoner. In the eyes of these lesser dragons, these commoners shouldn’t even be considered people. In the few days that they had been in charge of Lyon Empire, there were already several thousand people who were killed for no reason. It was basically a massacre.

* * *

I think the arrangement is like this: Northern Icefield ->  Prairie -> Aksu-> Rosen-> Buddha-> Ocean Waves

‘Walk sideways’ means they can do whatever they want

Chapter 663: Taking Two Cities at Night

Aya was a lesser dragon. He is a descendant between a Dragon and an 8th rank shadow leopard. He can also assume the form of a Human, but his strength was in his shadow leopard form.

Shadow leopards were the best assassins of the jungle. There was hardly anyone who can discover them when stealthed. Even Dragons admired their might.

When Aya is in his shadow leopard form, then his fighting strength would be on par with genuine shadow leopard, maybe even more. This was because he wasn’t only carrying the genes of a shadow leopard, he had the genes of a Dragon as well.

However, Aya’s status wasn’t very high among the other lesser dragons, he was only a Junior Captain. At this moment he was guarding the Lyon Empire against the Buddha Empire’s army.

Aya’s cavalry unit was stationed in the Lyon Empire’s most important fortress that faced the Buddha Empire. The Buddha Empire had stationed 50 thousand people here while the Lyon Empire used to station their 50 thousand magic cavalry unit as well.

Now, it was Aya who was assigned to this post. But he wasn’t here mainly to defend against the Buddha Empire’s attack. Aya believes that the Buddha Empire wouldn’t dare to attack them. Aya was stationed here mainly to defend against the original army of the Lyon Empire as well as those civilians that wanted to escape towards the Buddha Empire.

Aya’s recent days have been good. Although the original cavalry of the Lyon Empire was very strong, their magic beast mounts were all acquired in Accra Mountain. And since these magic beasts were under the rule of the Dragons, the Lyon Empire’s mounts would naturally listen to the Dragons’ words. Because of this, the Lyon Empire’s army had found themselves to be cavalries without mounts.

In addition to the Dragons stationed here, Aya and the others were descendants of Dragons as well. So their status was much higher than those magic beast mounts. When those magic beast mounts saw them, they immediately wore smiles on their faces, turning extremely polite. It can be said the Aya’s life here was very much the same back in Accra Mountain.

Tonight, it was Aya’s turn to become the night watch. But Aya thought that this was unnecessary, there simply was no need to do this. Aya didn’t believe that the Buddha Empire would actually dare to attack them. He also didn’t think that there would be any Lyon Empire rebellion. But since this was an order from the higher ups, he didn’t have any other choice but to listen.

Besides his first night, Aya always had a pot of liquor with him in his succeeding night shifts. There were side dishes present as well, so he was living quite an easy life.

Aya was very happy with his current situation. The Dragon Race had endured living in Accra Mountain for all these years. And this time, they had finally took control of a Human nation. Now, people were serving them every day. It was comfortable, nothing can compare to this bliss.

In Aya’s mind, the Dragons should have already come out of the mountain and took control of the continent a long time ago. There was no need for them to endure in the mountain for many years.

Just after taking a sip of his liquor, Aya suddenly stopped. He raised his own ear, it seems like he had heard something. One must know that a shadow leopard’s hearing was very strong. And since Aya had the genes of a shadow leopard, his hearing would naturally be strong as well.

Aya placed his wine glass down and quietly listened. He was right, there were very strange sounds. This sound wasn’t the whistling of the wind, nor was it the rustling of leaves, it was a sound that was made by people hurrying along.

Aya stared for a moment before he slowly stood up and looked towards the city, this was because the source of the sound was inside the walls. There was a night curfew, and every person that was caught would be executed for the crime of conspiracy.

Because of this, Aya felt strange, who would dare run in the middle of the night? He didn’t think that it would be the Lyon Empire cavalry, they wouldn’t dare since they knew that there was a Dragon in this city. This was equivalent to having 9th rank experts, so how could they rebel?

If it weren’t the garrison, then was it commoners? Even them wouldn’t dare. There was a restriction placed on the city, disallowing civilians to hold weapons. Even the act of hiding one would merit execution. These civilians were weaponless, so they wouldn’t dare to rebel. So to which people do these footsteps belong to?

Aya decided to look at the direction of the sound. In addition to their superior hearing, shadow leopards were also gifted with the ability to see in the dark. Aya was sure that he could spot who it was.

Before long, shadows appeared on the streets of the city, and there were a lot of them. Aya’s calm face immediately changed because these people were holding weapons in their hands. Aya knew that these people were enemies. Just as he was about fire an alarm, Aya suddenly felt a pain in his throat. Aya looked down and saw that a dagger had stabbed him on the neck. Before he blacked out, Aya can see blood spurting out of his neck. It was then that he knew that he was already dead. From start to finish, Aya wasn’t able to see what the enemy looked like.

An undead assassin appeared behind Aya and supported his body. After placing Aya back on his chair, the undead immediately turned to look at another person.

Just as the undead assassin turned around, Aya, who was about to fall of of his chair, disappeared. Then he appeared once again. Aya moved his hands and feet to pick up his own swords before going back to his position on the wall. By now, Aya had become expressionless, his eyes stared straight and he wasn’t breathing. Naturally, he had been turned into undead.

Zhao Hai’s main goal was to deal with the Dragons, therefore, he didn’t want to touch the original Lyon Empire cavalry. However, those lesser dragon cavalry weren’t spared. All of the lesser dragons, magic beasts, as well as Dragons had become undead!

With the 9th rank strength of his undead, the sneak attack was completed without a fuss. If one were to ask the Lyon Empire garrison, then they would just tell you that the night went strangely smooth. Even the Dragons weren’t able to respond before dying. Everything was silent, the magic beasts, lesser dragons, and Dragons had all disappeared.

The same situation happened on the border between the Lyon Empire and the Rosen Empire. The Dragons didn’t place too much defenders on these two cities. Zhao Hai only sent 200 thousand undead to kill the defenders in silence. Zhao Hai’s undead didn’t even need to make any significant effort in order to succeed.

The night passed by with no issues. The next morning, the civilians and the garrison had found out that all magic beasts, lesser dragons, and Dragons had disappeared. Only blood can be spotted on the ground, the bodies were nowhere to be seen.

The garrison on these two cities were terrified. The blood on the floor were clearly from the magic beasts and lesser dragons. Even in the place where the Dragons rested, blood can be seen. However, there were no bodies anywhere, this made them very confused.

Among the garrison and the civilians were veterans in battle. From this scene, they can infer that there must have been a huge army attack last night, targeting these magic beasts, lesser dragons, as well as the Dragons. From what they can see, it seems like the enemies were quite ruthless.

The garrison troops immediately got anxious, no matter which party did it, the garrison still wouldn’t be able to escape taking the responsibility. They weren’t in the Lyon Empire anymore, they were in Saint Dragon Empire. It was a nation that was ruled by Dragons, beings who didn’t tolerate shortcomings and were very ruthless. Once they came to know that their subordinates had vanished, how could they be merciful to the garrison troops that survived?

The garrison had experienced first hand how cruel these lesser dragons and Dragons can be. Both the lesser dragons and Dragons simply don’t see them as people. A lot of them had already died because of the indiscriminate slaughter that the Dragons had done. It would be strange if the garrison were to remain alive after all of this blows off.

The garrison was left not knowing what to do, some of the small soldiers had already sneaked away. On the other hand, the officers had no choice but to stay. They had their complete information in the capital. From their hometown to the names of their families were known. It was impossible for them to escape.

Of course, not all officers chose to stay. There were some who already had left their family behind to die. After all, they wouldn’t be returning to Lyon Empire, they planned to live a whole new life in the Buddha Empire or the Rosen Empire.

Because of this, there were nobody in those two cities that reported what happened to the Dragons back at the capital. While they refrained from sending word, they were also buying Zhao Hai some time.

Zhao Hai had already sent word to the Fishmen the moment he attacked. While the Saint Dragon Empire’s army asked for reinforcements from the Radiant Empire, they would be delayed to the point where by the time they come back, the Dragons would have already been extinguished.

Zhao Hai, who had already cleaned two cities, didn’t celebrate. This result was within his expectations. On the other hand, it would be impossible to do the same thing to the Lyon Empire’s capital. There were just too many experts within the capital, and the Dragons haven’t been able to control it for a long time, so everyone in the capital was on high alert. Faced with careful Dragons, the method of sneak attack was just impossible. Therefore, there was only one way to attack the capital, it was by storming it with an army!

But attacking the Lyon Empire’s capital was not that easy. The Lyon Empire’s capital was similar to the Rosen Empire’s capital. On the outskirts of the city, noble castles had been erected. Gathering all of the soldiers here would amount to no less than 200 thousand people. At the same time, the capital’s garrison would number to be 500 thousand. Among those 500 thousand were 200 thousand elite troops as well as 300 thousand heavy armor infantry. Additionally, there were also 5000 lesser dragons as well as 40 Dragons.

If this was just the case, then Zhao Hai can be assured that he would be able to take the capital in a short period of time. However, there were two bumps that Zhao Hai can see. First was the huge magical formation that protects the Lyon Empire. This formation had been in the capital for hundreds of years. If the Dragons didn’t have people from the inside, then they wouldn’t have been able to take the capital in such a short period of time.

Chapter 664: Dark Creatures of the Underworld

The second reason was very simple. Near the Lyon Empire’s capital city were four fortresses. These fortresses stand guard near the capital city. They weren’t very far from the capital, it would only take a day for their troops to arrive by horse. In other words, Zhao Hai needed to take the capital in one day. If he failed to do so, then he would have to face both inside and outside attacks.

The four fortresses around the capital had 100 thousand troops each, all of them were cavalry. Although they weren’t the most elite cavalry of the Empire, they were still quite problematic to face.

Naturally, Zhao Hai wasn’t afraid of these cavalry units. He just didn’t want to face them in combat. To be honest, Zhao Hai didn’t have any good impression for these cavalry. When the Dragons attacked the Lyon Empire, they didn’t do anything. After the establishment of the Saint Dragon Empire, they still remained as is while enjoying the same treatment as before. This shows that these people had already sold themselves to the Dragons.

Zhao Hai really wanted to kill these people, but the reason why he held back was the fact that these soldiers were only common soldiers of the Lyon Empire. Moreover, they weren’t just born out of stone, they had their own family members. If Zhao Hai killed these soldiers, then these family members would definitely hate him. When the time comes, a chain reaction would happen, causing chaos in the Lyon Empire, adding trouble to the current situation.

Because of these conditions, Zhao Hai didn’t want to get in a fight with the Dragons for a long time. It would be best if he were to take care of things fast.

This time, the method of sneak attack wouldn’t work. This was because ever since the Dragons had taken over the capital, they had enacted a curfew every night, and they also activated an alarm magic formation on the whole the capital during those times. This made it impossible for Zhao Hai to sneak in some assassins. Therefore, the only thing he could do was wait for the daylight before storming the capital.

After attacking the two fortresses, Zhao Hai prepared himself to attack the Lyon Empire’s capital on the next day. However, since he still wasn’t confident in his plans, he had decided to delay it for another day.

Zhao Hai and the others discussed what they would do and finally thought of a plan that Zhao Hai felt to be feasible.

After having rested for a day in the Space, Zhao Hai immediately began to prepare  the attack. Him along with Green and the others were in the Space’s living room, looking at the Lyon Empire’s capital on the monitor.

The Lyon Empire’s capital was not much worse than the Rosen Empire’s capital. After all, the Empire was still the second strongest in the continent. At this moment, there were 40 Dragons in the capital altogether. However, these Dragons weren’t grouped up, they were scattered all throughout the city. It might seem like they were dispersed in order to protect the populace, but they were doing this so that they can maintain control.

These Dragons weren’t weak, even if Zhao Hai wanted to use his previous method then it would prove impossible. There was a warning formation in place.

The Lyon Empire’s capital always had its warning formation enabled, however, the formation wasn’t as strict in the day compared to at night. It would only be activated in places where the Dragons were staying. This was exactly why Zhao Hai cannot attack in the night. Zhao Hai wasn’t worried about the Lyon Empire’s protective shield at all since the Space can just place the undead directly inside the city. However, these warning formations were the annoying ones, they simply cannot be bypassed.

At this moment, the sun had just risen, so the gates were still shut. Those commoners that wanted to do business in the capital were still barred from entering. This was also the best opportunity for Zhao Hai to attack. If these people were already in the city at the time of the attack, then they might become victims of the crossfire. But if Zhao Hai attacks before they enter the gate, then these civilian could still run in the opposite direction.

Zhao Hai looked at the time, it was close to the moment where the city’s gates would open. He turned to Green and said, “Grandpa Green, it’s time to start.”

Green nodded and said, “Let’s begin. We need a total of 50 cubes. Young Master, be careful in controlling them.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he waved his hand and launched his attack! At this time, the skies of the Lyon Empire’s capital had suddenly turned dark. Then a large patch of dark cloud appeared. The black clouds kept rolling, making it seem like rain was going to pour soon.

But what confused the people in the city was the fact that they couldn’t hear the sounds of a thunderclap. They also didn’t feel any kind of wind that would be associated with such a cloud.

It was the garrison troops that felt something wrong first. They knew that this wasn’t any simple dark cloud, so they couldn’t help but grab their weapons.

At this time, in the middle of the cloud, a thunderous voice can be heard, “Shameless Dragon Race, since you dared to attack a Human city, then you shall be paying your sins with blood!”

As this statement  fell, the dark cloud suddenly moved, turning into 50 smaller dark clouds. At this point, even idiot would notice that something was wrong about these dark clouds. Before long, the entire capital had turned into chaos. Those people who were about to leave for work immediately abandoned everything as the ran back home with the quickest speed before locking themselves up inside.

The soldiers immediately became nervous, at this time, a garrison commander suddenly shouted, “Quick, inform the generals. Open the protective formation! Sound the alarm! Give way for the Mages!”

Along with the commander’s orders, the city’s magical formation was immediately activated. Fortunately for them, the formation had just been retracted, so it was very convenient to activate it once more. When the formation came into life, a ray of yellow suddenly flashed as a hemispherical dome covered the entire capital.

However, only after the formation was placed did the soldiers notice something wrong. The formation had indeed been activated, but the dark clouds were actually included inside. This must be the reason why the garrison felt strange, the dark clouds were actually very close to the ground.

Seeing that the protective formation became useless, the soldiers didn’t panic immediately. At this time, the Mages that guarded the city had arrived at the wall. When they saw the dark clouds, a Light Mage face suddenly paled as he shouted, “Light Mages of all ranks, use light magic to attack. This is a Dark Mist spell of the Dark Mages!”

When this Light Mage shouted, the other Light Mages immediately took their stance and started to cast light magic towards the dark clouds.

Now that the Radiant Church and the Dragon Race had made an alliance, the Radiant Church had sent a lot of Light Mages to help the Dragons. Therefore, there were a lot of Light Mages defending the capital city right now.

As expected, the Light Mages had become useful. When their magic hit the dark clouds, they immediately started to slowly disappear. This made the garrison troops cheer.

However, the Light Mages actually think that there was no point in celebrating. They were people who completely understood Dark Mages. They knew that the Dark Mist spell was just a 1st rank magic, it had zero attack power. Its biggest use was in blocking the enemy’s sight. Therefore, dispelling the dark clouds wasn’t something remarkable.

As the dark mist slowly dissipated, the cheering garrison suddenly found themselves to be like ducks who were caught by the neck, they were suddenly jolted into silence.

This was because they saw battle formations in place of the dark clouds. This battle formation was very strange, it was because it was structured into a cube and was floating in mid air. It looks like every single cube floating in mid air is the same. The peculiar thing was that every unit in these cubes were composed of undead creatures.

Just as the Dark Mist vanished, the battle formations suddenly moved. Their gradually accelerated as they went straight to specific points in the city.

When they saw these flying formations, the garrison troops’ complexion suddenly changed. This was because those points were places where the Dragons were resting in. It seems like the other party came completely prepared.

At this time, the voice came once again, “To the garrison troops, listen. I came this time to deal with the Radiant Church and the Dragons. Since they shamelessly united to usurp the Lyon Empire, I am going to eliminate all of them. I hope you won’t participate in the battle, otherwise, you will definitely be killed.”

The garrison troops looked at the flying figures in the sky. Although they weren’t that strong, as long as they are from the Ark Continent, then they are aware what being able to fly meant. Aside from flying magic beasts, all other flying beings were 9th rank experts. Even if they haven’t heard of flying undead before, they knew that these undead were going to be trouble if they were provoked. Their ability to maintain a formation alone was enough to convince the garrison of how formidable they were. Additionally, those who commanded these undead were even more frightening.

At the same time, the garrison also found out that the voice wasn’t lying. Those flying undead were indeed specifically targeting the Dragons. Their flight direction was towards the places were the Dragons were resting in or the places where the lesser dragons were. None of the flying undead were heading towards the place where the garrison troops were.

The lead Light Mage who commanded the other Light Mages was very pale right now. The be honest, even he couldn’t remember reading about flying undead. In the history of the continent, the strongest undead that was spotted had the strength of 6th rank. The strongest creature summoned by a Dark Mage was not an undead, but instead it was a creature of the dark that came from the Underworld. This creature was extremely powerful. If one was a high-level Dark Mage, they can use a method of sacrifice in order to summon these 9th rank creatures. However, the requirements to summon such a creature was extremely high as well. After the summoning, their life force would be heavily affected. Moreover, there were also cases where the summoned dark creature turned against its own summoner.

Chapter 665: Easily Accomplished

Although he had never heard of flying undead before, this didn’t hinder his judgement. He was sure that the strengths of these undead were surely extraordinary. Because of this, he decided to fight, the other party already stated that he was here in order to deal with the Dragons and the Radiant Church. It was for certain that Light Mages like him weren’t going to be let off.

When he thought of this, the Light Mage immediately commanded loudly, “Don’t be afraid of them. Their display is no more than deception. There is no way that they are 9th rank undead. Everyone, attack!”

But just as he shouted, he suddenly felt a pain in his chest. He lowered his head to look only to see the tip of a sword that was slowly being pulled back. With great difficulty, he turned his head and saw a black-clothed undead. As the undead slowly withdrew its rapier, the Light Mage can swear that the undead was grinning at him.

Bang! A noise suddenly sounded at the side of the Light Mage. He took effort in turning his head and found out that all of the Light Mages on the wall had an undead right behind them, and that those Light Mages were killed as well.

“We’re finished!” This was the Light Mage’s last thought.

The defenders on the wall were all startled when they saw these undead that just suddenly appeared. They wanted to attack but found themselves shaking. Even their weapons seemed to be shaking, not wanting to make an attack.

These undead assassins turned to look at the soldiers, then with a flash, their bodies floated in the air where they drifted towards something. Before long, more and more undead floated up from the walls before forming a cube, then it turned around and flew towards the city.

The soldiers on the walls were relieved. At this moment, the previous voice sounded once again, “I’m saying this again. We only came to deal with the Dragons and the Radiant Church. For the others, as long as you don’t make a move, then we won’t hurt you. If you resist, then we will execute you immediately.”

The soldiers looked at one another and didn’t make a move. To be honest, these soldiers didn’t have a strong sense of belonging to the Dragons. They still take themselves as people of the Lyon Empire. After all, the Lyon Imperial Family had been ruling the empire for more than a thousand years.

Since nobody took the lead, nobody made a move. Even the officers didn’t dare to make a move, they don’t want to suddenly get stabbed by a rapier. So they decided to behave themselves.

At this moment, a roar was suddenly head inside the city. Along with this initial roar, more Dragon roars can be heard from other parts of the city. The garrison troops knew that this was the sign that the Dragons have awoken. Their faces couldn’t help but pale, they didn’t know what to do. The Dragons were extremely formidable in their eyes, but the strength of these undead were terrifying as well. They didn’t know which side to pick.

With the roar of the Dragons, all of them immediately took to the skies, covering the skies of the capital with their hulking figures. Those who were timid couldn’t help but kneel on the ground, shaking.

But the garrison soon discovered that although the Dragons have appeared, they were immediately met with an attack from the flying undead. Although the group of undead formed a cube, they were still smaller than the Dragons. But at the same time, the cube of undead was more flexible than the Dragons, so when the Dragons appeared, all of them immediately went to clash with flying beasts.

In their process of flight, the formation immediately changed. Every cube formation transformed into a giant scorpion as it clashed with the Dragons.

The Dragons were also keen to meet the enemies. In the eyes of these Dragons, the undead were just like ants. They were thinking that the undead would just need to be slapped a few times before they were taken care of.

However, the moment they exchanged blows, the Dragons immediately found their mistake. They thought that the Undead were just flying because of a special spell by their Dark Mage, it was impossible for these undead to have 9th rank strength. This was because a 9th rank Undead hasn’t been spotted in the continent before.

But in this exchange, the Dragons discovered that the undead weren’t pretending, they really had 9th rank strength, they were 9th ranks!! This startled the Dragons.

The bodies of the Dragons were tough, an 8th rank Dragon can be compared to a Human 9th rank. At the same time, 9th rank Dragons had bodies that were extremely close to being invincible. This was exactly why the Dragons were known to be invincible.

However, even Dragons would find it impossible to withstand the attacks of several hundred 9th ranks. 9th rank Dragons might be able to withstand it, but those 8th ranks certainly couldn’t. Just as those 8th ranks clashed with the undead, they began to fall one by one.

The first dragon to fall cried out pitifully before it was knocked down by the undead. Then a clump of dark mist wrapped the Dragon before it turned into a Bone Dragon. After that, the Bone Dragon rose to the sky and joined the fight to slaughter the remaining Dragons.

The garrison troops that were on the wall saw everything that happened. They couldn’t believe what they were seeing. The almighty Dragons were actually taken down and even turned into undead. This development was completely out of their imagination. The weapons of some of them had unconsciously fallen to the ground, however, none of them were able to notice it at all.

Forty Dragons, ten of them fell first and became Bone Dragons who joined the slaughter. Before long, the 40 Dragons had been reduced to 10. These ten Dragons were the strong 9th ranks. However, their situation had turned dangerous. With the addition of the Bone Dragons, the defenses of these 9th rank Dragons began to crack.

The suddenly, among the ten 9th rank Dragons, one of them screamed and fell from the sky. This scream smashed through the hearts of the garrison like a huge hammer. At this point, any rebellious thought that they had were completely erased. Those who still had weapons on their hands immediately threw them away as though they were venomous snakes. All of them were staring at the skies with a pale complexion.

But these garrison troops were completely unaware that in the city’s lesser dragon compound, a massacre was happening. All of the lesser dragons and magic beasts were eradicated. At the same time, Undead were also blocking the exits of the army barracks, killing all those who wanted to resist. Additionally, when these soldiers saw that the Dragons had started to fall, their thoughts of resisting were gone. Unexpectedly, the capital had calmed down after only a short time. On the other hand, an army had formed outside the capital. There were Nobles who wanted to enter the capital in order to help. However, all of them were blocked by the city’s protective formation. The Nobles even shouted to the garrison, ordering them to deactivate the formation. But at this time, there was no garrison soldier that would dare to make a move. They just witnessed the Dragons being slaughtered as though they were chickens. If these people needlessly moved, then they would be like cockroaches that would be stepped on.

Zhao Hai calmly witnessed the battle outside. Laura and the others were sitting right beside Zhao Hai. This time, the battle plan was left to Lizzy, Megan, Green, and Kun. They had found out that the strength of the undead would be expressed to it full potential when it was in the Fishman’s cube formation. They planned to deal with the Dragons and the lesser dragons at the fastest speed. Once the Dragons fell, the other people in the Lyon Empire would naturally stop their actions.

This time, if they wanted to kill the Dragons, then they needed to do it in front of the soldiers. Only in this way can they stand up and go against the Nobles of the Lyon Empire. At the same time, it was also to inform the Nobles that the Dragons weren’t the invincible beings that the legends had stated.

From the time where the black clouds appeared up until the end of the battle, no more than three hours has passed. Forty Dragons, 5 thousand lesser dragons, nearly 100 thousand magic beasts, nearly 1 thousand people from the Radiant Church had fallen. Additionally, there were also 10 thousand defenders, 30 nobles, and 20 generals who participated in resisting. All of them were promptly killed by Zhao Hai and turned into undead. Although they were turned into the undead, their blood still flowed in the streets, painting it blood red. Especially the blood of the Dragons, there were whole residences that were turned red just by being splashed by draconic blood. The residents didn’t dare to come out of their house or even take a single step out of their door.

The fight also ruined about 200 private residences. It killed about 87 civilians while injuring 302. But these ruined residences were immediately fixed by the undead. The injured civilians were also healed by some undead Light Mages. The undead also visited the houses of those who were affected and gave each of them a bag of coins containing no less than 1000 pieces of gold inside.

After three hours, the entire Lyon Empire’s capital had turned calm. There were no fights that happened nor was there any other disturbance. The garrison stayed in their own barracks, nobody dared to take action.

At this time, the undead that just slaughtered the dragons were forming a huge cube in the air. The Dragons, lesser dragons, and the others that were killed had also become a part of this formation. Some courageous citizens opened their windows and looked at the huge formation in the air. They were waiting for their unknown fate.

Then suddenly, the formation suddenly gave way to a red mansion. This red mansion was shackled to a Dragon as it slowly appeared in front of the formation. Then the mansion’s door opened as a man came out of it.

This person was very young and wore a Dark Mage’s robe. He looked extremely ordinary along with his average looking face. However, nobody dared to underestimate this young man. Everyone knew that this person was the one who controlled the undead!

Chapter 666: Officially Declaring War

Ritchie was a Lyon Empire Merchant and was a marine trader. His business was quite well known in the Lyon Empire.

However, in the recent days, Ritchie had come to find that the changes in the Lyon Empire was beyond his understanding. First, there were the Dragons, who, with the cooperation of the Nobles, suddenly broke through the Empire and slaughtered the Lyon Imperial Family. Then the Dragons titled themselves to the the Royal Family of the Lyon Empire, renaming the Empire to Saint Dragon Empire.

Ritchie thought that the matter can only continue on like this. Everyone knew what the Dragons were. Moreover, the Buddha Empire, Rosen Empire, Aksu Empire, as well as the recently changed Radiant Empire, approved of the Dragon’s rule of the Lyon Empire. In this case, the Lyon Empire would have to be ruled by the Dragons from here on out.

In Richie’s mind, there was nothing wrong about this. Everyone knew how powerful the Dragons were, and at the same time, the had also allied themselves with the Radiant Church. Although Ritchie didn’t agree to this alliance, he was just a Merchant, he didn’t have any power to speak at all. And even if he did have the ability to voice his thoughts, he still wouldn’t do it if he wanted to live under the rule of the Dragons.

In the beginning, he didn’t find anything wrong. However, it didn’t take a long time before Ritchie knew that being ruled by the Dragons was not a good idea. The Dragons think of themselves too highly and looked down on all the Humans. In the eyes of the Dragons, Humans were just like ants. Even the lesser dragons held the same mindset. In the recent days, the Empire had already lost thousands of innocent civilians. These civilians didn’t do anything wrong, they just forgot to salute to the lesser dragons or even worse, killed just for fun.

Such overbearing attitude makes it impossible for the Dragons to gain popular sentiment. Ritchie had noticed that there were fewer and fewer people who did business in the capital. Even small Nobles didn’t dare to go out of their houses. Feasts and ballrooms disappeared, nobody was in the mood of merrymaking.

The ones who gained the most with this situation were the Great Nobles. Although the Dragons ruled the Lyon Empire, they were still foreigners and were unfamiliar with how the Empire runs. Therefore, everything was handed over to the Great Nobles, giving them power that they had never experienced before.

This also made Ritchie scorn these Great Nobles. To be honest, Ritchie didn’t like the rule of the Dragons. They were too tyrannical, and in addition to being foreign, they also treat everyone as their slaves. In order to gain more benefits, these Great Nobles prostrate themselves in front of the Dragons. This really made Ritchie feel shame in their behaviours.

But he was just a Merchant, famous and rich yet powerless. In fact, Ritchie was afraid that the Great Nobles would do something to him. But fortunately, Ritchie had friends among these Great Nobles, so he still managed to avoid their gaze.

This day, Ritchie was prepared to go on board his ship and go out of the capital. This was because he needed to take a trip at sea, heading towards Golden Island. He was a marine trader, and which marine trader would not head to Golden Island to do business? However, just as he was about to go out, something occurred.

Ritchie’s courage wasn’t small, he had been in the sea for many years. He has seen magic beasts, pirates, and people who died on the water. Naturally, he wasn’t as afraid as the other people. This allowed him to look at all that happened with his two eyes.

It took some time after the battle until Ritchie had recovered his senses. He didn’t think that the invincible Dragons would get taken down one by one. Moreover, they were also turned into Bone Dragons after they fell.

Ritchie was standing inside the attic of his own residence as he looked out a small window and into the cube formation outside. His heart was beating loudly, he was so afraid. One must know that there were only very few individuals who were unafraid of the undead, especially powerful undead like these ones.

At this time, the undead formation suddenly moved as a Bone Dragon with a red mansion appeared in the sky. This mansion was completely red and seemed to be made out of a special crystal. Then a person walked out of the mansion. This person looks quite young and had a very average appearance. However, this person made Ritchie quite shocked, he knew who this person was!

This was the Lord of Golden Island, the Buda Clan’s Patriarch, called to be the Continent’s most powerful Dark Mage, the most romantically fortunate man, the richest Merchant, strongest Patriarch, and more strings of titles. This was Zhao Hai Buda!

Since he had been doing business in Golden Island, Ritchie was also given the opportunity to attend Zhao Hai’s wedding. With his own two eyes, he had seen Zhao Hai get married to his wives. Ritchie was also quite awed by Zhao Hai’s liquor. Therefore, how could he forget Zhao Hai’s face.

Seeing Zhao Hai appear stunned Ritchie. He never thought that this powerful undead army was actually commanded by Zhao Hai.

Then Zhao Hai’s mansion suddenly turned into his Staff as he walked out. He stood on the Bone Dragon’s head as he looked calmly at the Lyon Empire’s capital before he said, “Friends from the Lyon Empire, hello. I am Zhao Hai Buda, Buda Clan’s Patriarch. The reason why I came with force this time is to deal with the Dragons. The Dragons are quite shameless to usurp a Human Empire and enslave the Human Race. For me, this act is simply unforgivable. Today, I, Zhao Hai Buda, in behalf of my Buda Clan, officially declare war against the entire Dragon Race. Today, I have eliminated all the Dragons, lesser dragons, and Human traitors in the Lyon Empire’s capital. Yesterday, I also eradicated the Dragon Race’s forces on the border fortresses. And tomorrow, I shall charge towards Accra Mountains. Friends of the Lyon Empire, don’t worry, I will not violate your safety. Do not be afraid!”

With the help of magic, Zhao Hai voice had reached every corner of the capital. Every citizen inside the city were listening to Zhao Hai’s words. Many commoners opened their windows and looked up into the skies to see Zhao Hai.

Before long, people started to walk out of their houses, slowly increasing as they filled the streets. Zhao Hai calmly looked at the people and said, “I ask everyone to rest assured, I have no intention of encroaching into your Empire. I only came here to specially deal with the Dragon Race. I hope that the garrison troops will help me in keeping the capital’s peace intact. I don’t want any chaos to unfold. After that I shall open the capital’s protective formation and see the Noble army outside. As for the Noble armies, I hope that you don’t do any unnecessary movements unless you want to get hurt.”

After that, Zhao Hai commanded his undead and slowly went towards the north gate. He also deactivated the formation as the yellow hemisphere began to disappear.

Then Zhao Hai appeared in front of the capital’s northern gate. The Noble armies outside the city were actually trembling. Although the protective formation has been removed, they still didn’t have the means to enter the city. Additionally, even if the walls had obstructed their vision, the protective shield couldn’t block sounds. This allowed them to hear Zhao Hai’s words very clearly. They also heard the noises inside and could vaguely guess what just happened.

After hearing that the Dragons and the lesser dragons were eliminated, the Great Nobles started to be afraid. The reason for the Lyon Empire’s fall had a direct relationship with them. If they haven’t sided with the Dragons, then the Empire wouldn’t have fallen to its current situation.

Zhao Hai bringing his undead and killing the Dragons meant that the Great Nobles had lost their backer. They were now waiting for Zhao Hai’s judgement.

When they noticed Zhao Hai and his sky blotting undead army, the Great Nobles wanted to run away. Upon seeing the Bone Dragon beneath Zhao Hai feet, these Great Nobles knew that the capital’s Dragons had already perished.

They understood why Zhao Hai was able to kill the Dragons in such a short time, it was because of those flying undead. However, what were those flying undead? Are they 9th ranks? Are there 9th rank undead? But even if they had their doubts, these Great Nobles still couldn’t help but believe that these undead were 9th rank. Otherwise, they wouldn’t have eliminated the Dragons in this short timeframe.

The Great Nobles found their own legs to be shivering, all of them were thinking, cr*p!

Zhao Hai stood on the head of his Bone Dragon and coldly looked at the Great Nobles. He couldn’t help but snorted coldly and said, “You are traitors to Humanity for siding with the Dragons and helping them suppress our own race. I thought of executing all of you but I don’t want to do it right now. I shall head to Accra Mountain tomorrow to have a decisive battle against the Dragons. At that time, I won’t be here to manage things. Therefore, I hope that you can manage the Lyon Empire very well. Make sure to do things properly, otherwise, when I come back, I shall kill all of you!”

These Great Nobles didn’t dare to say anything right now. They knew that if they resisted for even a small bit, then they would get killed immediately.

They knew what their values were in the eyes of Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai was not short of money, he was the most famous Merchant in the continent. Moreover, he was is control of Golden Island. If he was short on money, then the Continent would have been extremely dirt poor.

At the same time, he does not lack people who would fight for him. He already had several hundred thousand undead behind him right now. And all of these undead were flying on the sky, there were 40 Bone Dragons as well as a lot of magic beasts and lesser dragons. By Zhao Hai’s present strength, he can destroy any nation with ease.

However, Zhao Hai was short in people who could manage. Now that Zhao Hai had eliminated the Dragons in the Lyon Empire, he was left with nobody to manage the Empire. If that happens, then the nation would fall into confusion, and Zhao Hai didn’t want to see this. Because of this, Zhao Hai decided to keep the lives of these Great Nobles and have them manage the Empire. This was their final value in Zhao Hai’s eyes. Nobody dared to resist, all of them nodded in compliance. There were even some Nobles who bowed to Zhao Hai and swore fealty to him.

Chapter 667: Waiting for a Day

In the minds of these nobles, Zhao Hai’s promise to not encroach upon the Lyon Empire was simply impossible. How can a powerful person have no ambitions when placed in front a  ruler-less empire?

For these nobles, Zhao Hai was actually a scorpion that wanted an archway. Therefore, the Nobles expressed their loyalty to him. Zhao Hai looked at these Nobles with no expression and said, “Remember my words, don’t play any tricks. Don’t think that the Dragons would save you. Do you think that the Dragons can deal with my hundred thousand 9th rank undead? You better behave yourselves, don’t annoy me. Any plots and schemes that you all are used to doing are all useless in front of absolute strength. If I hear any whispers of rebellion, then your Clans would need to be prepared. Remember my words!” Then with an intention, Zhao Hai vanished along with his undead army.

Zhao Hai didn’t plan to stay in Lyon Empire for too long. He wanted to prepare for his attack on Accra Mountain tomorrow. At the same time, he also wants to see the reactions of these Nobles. He knew that it would only take a short time before news of what happened reaches the ears of every Empire in the continent.

The reason why Zhao Hai showed his strength was so that he could prepare for later on. After eliminating the Dragons, Zhao Hai would then approach the Human Emperors and tell them about the Divine Race. If his strength was insufficient at that time, then those people might not believe him. Therefore, Zhao Hai showed his strength, making those people understand that he wasn’t joking.

After eliminating the Dragons, Zhao Hai’s next target would be the Radiant Church. Once Zhao Hai eliminates the Dragons, the Radiant Church would surely be aware that their plans had been exposed. When that time comes, it may be possible that they would start their operation immediately. Therefore, Zhao Hai plans to deal with the Dragons quickly before paying a visit to the Human Emperors and explain why he needed to deal with the Radiant Church. If he didn’t do this procedure, then the Human Emperors would become a headache.

The Human Emperors wanted to see Zhao Hai deal with the Dragons, this was because the Dragons were too strong, and were going to be a threat to the Emperors’ rule. However, the same sentiment would happen to Zhao Hai. Since Zhao Hai had eliminated the Dragons, the rulers would shift their attention to him, dreading his strength in the process. If Zhao Hai deals with the Radiant Church without any explanation, then the Emperors would think that he was trying to conquer the entire continent. When that time comes, they may even think of uniting against Zhao Hai, even the Rosen Emperor would participate. This was because for any Emperor, a threat to their throne needed to be dealt with, it didn’t matter if this person was his son or his son-in-law, everything is the same.

Therefore, before dealing with the Radiant Church, Zhao Hai must establish a relationship with the rulers of the nations. He didn’t want to have the entire Human Race as his enemy.

Zhao Hai returned to the Space, but then he saw that the expressions that Laura and the others were giving to him had become different. This made Zhao Hai stare, he looked at the women and said, “What happened? Why are you looking at me strangely?”

Laura looked at Zhao Hai and chuckled, “Brother Hai, I didn’t expect you having an overbearing attitude. Unexpectedly, an overbearing Zhao Hai is actually really handsome!” Megan and the others nodded, before they all laughed.

Zhao Hai couldn’t bear to roll his eyes, then he turned to Green and Kun, “Grandpa Green, Grandpa Kun, have you given the letter to father-in-law?”

The father-in-law that Zhao Hai meant was the Rosen Emperor. Zhao Hai knew that this matter would spread soon, so he had to give the Rosen Emperor prior word. Although he can’t explain everything, after dealing with the Dragons, he would give the Emperor a personal visit.

The reason why Zhao Hai did this was due to Lizzy. Lizzy was the Emperor’s daughter, and Zhao Hai didn’t want her to feel awkward in the future. Therefore, Zhao Hai decided to send a letter to the King in order to calm his mood.

Green nodded and said, “Young Master, rest assured, it has been sent out. On the other hand, the Young Master did a very good job. After you left, not only did those Nobles behave themselves, they also eliminated any thoughts of resistance in their minds.”

Kun smiled as well, “That’s right. Little Hai, your exit essentially told them that you are someone with a Space Divergent Ability. This gave them confidence in your strength. One must know that Space Divergent Mages aren’t only strong in attack, their most powerful weapon is their ability to escape, it was impossible for people to catch them. Therefore, they believed that even if you can’t defeat the Dragons, you can still keep yourself quite safe.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I didn’t think of that. Right, no matter what, we still need talk about how to deal with the Dragons. I think the Dragons would be aware of my declaration of war soon. We need to sweep away their troops on the foot of the mountain before we scale it to the top.”

Green nodded and said, “I think that the Dragons wouldn’t come even if they know what happened here. Their population isn’t a lot, and they just lost 40 of their kind in the capital. It would be impossible for them to retaliate. Moreover, even if they do want to take revenge, they wouldn’t have the time to do so. Before they leave the mountain, we would have already scaled it.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Right, also, it would be better for us to fight the Dragons right inside Accra Mountain. That way, we wouldn’t have to worry about innocent people being killed or injured.”

At this time, Kun sighed and said, “I’m afraid the Radiant Church will have to respond when we eliminate the Dragon Race. It is possible that the Divine Race would come ahead of schedule. We still haven’t made proper preparations yet, we don’t have enough time.”

Zhao Hai sighed as well, “We have no choice, if we don’t make our move, then the Dragons would surely get complete hold of the Lyon Empire. That would be more troublesome for us when the Divine Race comes. At that time, it would be hard to reclaim the Lyon Empire.”

Kun nodded, then they adjusted the monitor to show Accra Mountain. The mountain was very calm, the Dragons simply didn’t expect that someone would actually move against them. In their view, they were invincible existences in the continent and that nobody would dare to provoke them.

It wasn’t only the Humans who were affected negatively by this title of invincibility, the Dragons had been dulled by this title as well. The Dragons had become complacent and was convinced that there were no people who would fight them. And that those warriors who dared face the Dragons were just in heroic novels and poems.

Zhao Hai carefully inspected the military barracks on the foot of Accra Mountain. This camp wasn’t very big since it mostly housed lesser dragons and magic beasts. However, Zhao Hai thinks that dealing with this military camp would be more difficult than attacking the capital of the Lyon Empire. It’s difficult because the camp was backed by the entire Accra Mountain. Although there was still some distance before the home of the Dragons, the magic beasts in the mountain would still reinforce the camp. If one were to ask about the number of magic beasts in Accra Mountain, then nobody would be able to give a confident answer. One must know that nobody has ever scaled the entire mountain before, all of them either died or retreated.

The magic beasts of Accra Mountain were under the control of the Dragon Race. As for those low-ranked beasts, even if they didn’t have any wisdom, they still had the basic animal instinct to obey the command of those more powerful than them. And in the end, the line of command would still fall into the hands of the Dragon Race.

For Zhao Hai, this was very troublesome. But Zhao Hai was not worried, the level of his undead was very high, and it was also impossible for these magic beasts to drown out his undead army. At the same time, as the fight gets longer and longer, the undead’s numbers would only get higher and higher.

The Radiant Church would have to do either two things upon receiving news, they can support the Dragons or they can directly call the Divine Race to come down. If they helped the Dragons, then Zhao Hai wouldn’t need to be afraid. However, if they were to call the Divine Race, then that would be quite the headache.

Attacking Accra Mountain was different from attacking the capital. When he attacked the capital, he was able to use the might of his undead to scare the minds of the garrison troops, terrifying them so much that they weren’t able to move.

On the other hand, the creatures inside Accra Mountain were magic beasts. Although the magic beasts were able to be terrified, they were still magic beasts in the end. Moreover, with their large numbers as well as the command of the Dragons, it would be impossible for Zhao Hai to terrify them into submission. At this rate, it would take a few days before Zhao Hai can scale the mountain, and this was already an optimistic estimate. And in those few days, the Radiant Church would have already made their move.

Zhao Hai was frowning as he looked at the map. He was thinking about the consequences of this war and how it would affect the entire continent. Green looked at Zhao Hai and knew what he was thinking, so Green smiled faintly and said, “Young Master, there’s no need to be worried. Look, when we attack the Dragons, the people of the continent would certainly not meddle. And if the Radiant Church can really ask the Divine Race to come down immediately, then they wouldn’t have waited until now. As long as we eliminate the Dragons and unite the other four Empires, then even if the Divine Race comes, we would not be caught off-guard.”

Zhao Hai nodded and sighed, “Let’s just hope that the Divine Race would give us some time, allowing us to eradicate the Dragons. Right, Grandpa Green, is there word from the Fishmen?” Green shook his head and said, “There’s nothing. I reckon that the Radiant Church was still unaware of what happened in the Lyon Empire’s capital, so they still weren’t able to react. However, the Young Master shouldn’t worry. The Fishmen are the real hegemons of the sea. Even if the Radiant Church is powerful, they still couldn’t contend with the Fishmen when it came to naval battles. There will be no problem.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he looked at the map on the screen and muttered, “Dragon Race, the day of your extinction has come!”

Chapter 668: Removed from the Continent!

And just as Zhao Hai thought, the news of his attack on the Lyon Empire’s capital had swept through the entire continent, shocking everyone who heard of it!

From ancient times to the present, Dragons were synonymous with invincibility. There might be no need to say it, but what are Dragons? They were the most fearful existence in the continent. Some commoners even think of them as gods. And stories of people slaying Dragons only came up in stories and songs. However, in the history of the continent, there were actually instances where the Dragons were slaughtered.

Of course, among these Dragons slayers were Humans. But this fact had been erased in the Human records by the Radiant Church. This was to ensure that the Humans would forever fear the invincible Dragons. This would made them hesitate to fight these beasts of the sky.

It was like two warriors of the same strength preparing for a duel, one warrior had a normal status while the other was renowned throughout the land. In this case, the first warrior would find it hard to face his opponent. Some might prevail due to their courage, but not everyone had a strong heart and mind.

When the Empires of the continent heard this news, their first reaction was disbelief. This news must be fake, how could someone kill a Dragon, moreover, forty of them? This was completely unbelievable.

But when confirmation came, the Empires had a mixed reaction. The Radiant Empire had become chaotic, they couldn’t describe what they were feeling. The Dragons were their ally, but now, their ally had been attacked. This made them stare blankly for a moment.

The first reaction of the Buddha Empire was shock, and after that was silence. They didn’t know how to react to this news.

The Lyon Empire has been destroyed by the Dragons, who then established the Saint Dragon Empire, which itself caught them by surprise. However, because of the Dragons’ reputation, they had to recognize their sovereignty to the Empire. But now that Zhao Hai fought the Dragons, and even openly declared war against them, the Buddha Empire caught themselves unaware of what to do. They didn’t know whether they would help Zhao Hai and deal with the Dragons, or help the Dragons and deal with Zhao Hai.

The Buddha Empire didn’t have the courage to fight the Dragons. But on the other hand, they cannot justify making war with Zhao Hai. After all, Zhao Hai was fighting the Dragons, and they cannot help another race deal with a Human. The Buddha Empire was confused!

And at this moment, there were two things that was on the table of the Rosen Emperor. One was the information about Zhao Hai and the Dragons, and the other was Zhao Hai’s letter to him.

The Emperor was just sitting there, reading the report and the switching to Zhao Hai’s letter. After some time, he still didn’t know what to say or what to do.

The Rosen Emperor had a feeling of loss when it comes to this son-in-law of his. Zhao Hai seemed to be someone with zero ambition. He continued to stay on his own Island and just did business. Even though his relations to the various races in the continent was good, he still didn’t express any great thoughts. This made the Emperor quite satisfied with Zhao Hai.

But just when the Emperor thought that Zhao Hai really didn’t want to do anything grand, this piece of report came. Zhao Hai had waged war with the Dragons and already slaughtered 40 of them. This made the Rosen Emperor utterly speechless.

And at this time, the Rosen Emperor received Zhao Hai’s letter. In this letter, Zhao Hai said that his current action was not to usurp the Lyon Empire’s Domain. And that he has something that he was unable to say right now. Zhao Hai stated that he would pay the Rosen Emperor a personal visit after he had dealt with the Dragon Race.

This letter didn’t just contained Zhao Hai’s words, Lizzy gave her thoughts as well. The Emperor knew this since he could recognize Lizzy’s handwriting.

When the Emperor looked at the letter, he couldn’t help but sigh, then with a low voice he said, “What do you think I should do?”

Then a voice was heard that said, “You wait!’

The Emperor sighed and said, “Alright, then we’ll wait. It seems like that is the only thing we could do.” Naturally, the person that he had spoken to was his Dead Adviser. This was a person that never showed himself and just kept hiding in the shadows.

Under the anticipation of the continent, the day passed by. Everyone was paying attention to Accra Mountain. All of them wanted to know if Zhao Hai would really go to war with the Dragons.

On the other hand, the lesser dragon camp at the foot of the mountain was completely unaware about all of this. All of the influences in the continent had their own means of acquiring information, and this didn’t exempt the Dragons. Moreover, the Radiant Church were their allies, so even if the Dragons weren’t able to send their scouts, the Radiant Church would surely send word. However, nothing came that night, everything seems to be very normal. The mountain spent their night just like they had in the nights before.

Yesterday, although Zhao Hai was resting in the Space, he actually didn’t idle himself. Surrounding the lesser dragon camp was a large net. This net wasn’t to monitor the lesser dragons, but this was to intercept any news and information that was heading towards the lesser dragon camp.

Zhao Hai must make sure that the Dragons were unable to get any news. At the same time, Zhao Hai wanted to see which people were sending word back to Accra Mountain.

Zhao Hai’s efforts weren’t wasted, he had captured 15 people who wanted to report the news to the Dragons. Only five of them were from the Radiant Church. As for the other 10, they were sent by the Great Nobles of the Lyon Empire. It seems like the Nobles were gambling. They submitted to Zhao Hai, causing no trouble back in the capital, but also handing information over to the Dragons so that the Dragons wouldn’t be offended. So later on, whether which side wins, they can still find a way to save themselves. But unfortunately for them, their lives were already forfeit, Zhao Hai would never let them off.

After resting for a day, Zhao Hai’s mind and body had recovered to peak condition, he felt like he can deal with anything at this time. After having breakfast inside the Space, Zhao Hai and the others went out of the Space and stood on the back of a Bone Dragon. Then Zhao Hai turned his Staff into a mansion before having the undead form a cube formation. Then the massive army started to head towards the lesser dragon camp.

This time, Zhao Hai was not planning on hiding themselves. They exhibited their full might as they slowly pressed forward. And in a war, this display was even more frightening. The pressure that one would feel would be no less than a mountain’s pressure.

Currently, there were millions of undead creatures in Zhao Hai’s arsenal. Many of them were from the sea, but after becoming undead, all of these marine undead can now fight on land, without even affecting their strength. Zhao Hai released all of them, millions of 9th rank undead started to appear and form a very large cube formation which slowly approached the lesser dragon camp.

The lesser dragons also noticed the millions of undead that was heading towards them. These undead were in a strange formation that they had not seen before, this really surprised the lesser dragons.

The lesser dragon army was horrified as it stared at the approaching army. Seeing these flying undead in the skies made their whole bodies tremble.

The lesser dragons quickly sent a letter to the Dragons, asking for immediate reinforcements. Then the lesser dragon army started to form a defensive formation. At this point, they had zero confidence in attacking. After seeing this army composed of millions of undead, only stupid oneswould have the courage to attack.

Zhao Hai’s speed was not fast, they took their time in approaching the enemy camp. Zhao Hai thought that if they were to give pressure to the lesser dragons, then they must make sure to affect them in the worst possible way.

At this time,  a loud Dragon’s roar was heard from inside the lesser dragon camp. Then ten Dragons appeared as they couldn’t bear it anymore and turned into their true Dragon form before flying to the sky. They stopped at the camp’s sky as they looked at the undead that were slowly closing in.

And then, a golden Dragon with two long knife-like curved horns opened its mouth and said in a thunderous voice, “What are you doing here, friend? Are you aware that this is the Dragon Race’s territory?”

When the Dragon finished talking, the huge cube formation slowly fluctuated. Then a Bone Dragon with a red mansion on its back slowly surfaced. The the Bone Dragon stopped about 100 meters away before a young man came out of the mansion. Naturally, this man was Zhao Hai, he looked at the Golden Dragon and sneered, “Of course I know that this is the Dragon Race’s domain. If this wasn’t the Dragon’s domain, then why would I even come. What’s wrong, you can’t recognize me?”

When the Dragon saw Zhao Hai, his pupils couldn’t help but shrink as he said, “Zhao Hai, you are Zhao Hai? You should be dead at sea. Did you kill the people that we sent to the Sea Dragons?”

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “You Dragons are surely arrogant. Do you think that nobody would be able to kill you? Hahaha, too funny! Not only did I eliminate your people back in the sea, I also eliminated every one of your clansmen in the Lyon Empire’s capital. From this day forward, the Dragons would be removed from the Continent!”

A huge roar suddenly came out of the Dragon’s mouth. He looked at Zhao Hai with red eyes and yelled, “You arrogant ant! You think you are strong just because you killed some Dragons? I want to see how you plan to deal with us!”

Zhao Hai sneered and said, “No need to keep talking, dog of the Divine Race. I am more than qualified to claim my superiority. Come see my recent collection.” Then more than forty Dragons flew out of the cube formation. These Bone Dragons had been lined up by Zhao Hai. All of them had fiery eyes that coldly stared at the still living Dragons.

Chapter 669: Rout!

When the Dragon saw the Bones Dragons, his eyes couldn’t help but shrink before his expression turned into anger. He knew that these Bone Dragons were his clansmen. They were killed and then turned into these undead creatures. For a majestic Dragon to become like this and were used to deal with their own Race, the arrogant Golden Dragon naturally wouldn’t be able to tolerate it.

When Zhao Hai saw the Dragon’s expression, he couldn’t help but laugh and said, “You can’t accept your people being turned to these Bone Dragons? Alright, I’ll change their appearances. I think you will like it.” Then he waved his hand as a black gas slowly engulfed the Bone Dragons. When the gas dissipated, the Bones Dragons looked totally different.

This time, the Dragon’s eyes shrunk again, and his anger flared up once more. This was because the Bone Dragons had become real Dragons. One couldn’t see any wounds in their bodies, their scales were also shining. They also had bodies that exuded pure strength. The Dragon knew that his people had become zombies, they still had their original bodily functions, but they were still undead.

This was also the reason why the Dragon’s anger had flared up. The mighty Dragons had been turned into toys by a Human, this was completely unforgivable!

The Dragon faced the sky and roared out loud before he said, “This is unforgivable! How dare you treat the Dragons like this! Face your death!” Then he flapped both of his winds and charged. The other Dragons behind him roared as well before following the Golden Dragon’s lead.

Zhao Hai actually laughed when he saw this and said, “You Dragons had always bathed on your unwarranted reputation. Get ready to become reduced to a mere mention in history!” The he waved his hand as 40 Zombie Dragons charged, clashing with the ten Dragons from earlier.

The 40 colossal Dragons that were fighting in the skies attracted the attention of all the lesser Dragons. They didn’t think that they would face someone that dared to challenge the formidable Dragons. In the entire Accra Mountain, there wasn’t anybody that would face a Dragon. In the continent, there wasn’t anyone who would dare claim that the status of the Dragons was fake. The lesser dragons had always thought that the Dragons were unparalleled beneath the Heavens. When the Dragons begin to act, there would be no on who would be able to stop them. And yet, there was this lunatic, a lunatic that actually managed to slaughter Dragons!

There was nothing wrong with this description, in the eyes of the lesser dragons, Zhao Hai was truly a lunatic that wanted to kill the Dragons. But the strength this madman had startled the lesser dragons, the Dragons themselves were quite shocked as well.

How much power can these Zombie Dragons really dish out? How can they be on par with real Dragons? However, when they clashed, the living Dragons had discovered that these Zombie Dragons weren’t weaker than them, they were stronger!

What was the feeling of being besieged by forty people that were stronger then themselves? At this moment, the living Dragons knew that the only thing they could do was to defend against the assault of the Forty Zombie Dragons. They were zero chances for them to counter-attack.

Zhao Hai didn’t idle, he looked down at the lesser dragons and coldly said, “You don’t need to just stand there, you join my undead army!” Then he gave a signal as Megan and Lizzy commanded the undead army to send divisions to assault the lesser dragon army.

The lesser dragons went into a commotion. They were afraid and had felt pressure when the undead came. But since they still had the Dragons on their backs to assume command, they believed that they can resist any attackers. This was the impression that the Dragons had given them after all these years. In their opinion, Dragons were invincible!

But from what they saw, the ten Dragons had no way to retaliate against the forty assaulting Dragons. It was only a matter of time before they lost their lives. So at this time, the pressure that Zhao Hai’s army brought to them have been amplified. They even had a faint sense of panic starting to well up from inside of them.

If this was in the past few days, the Dragons would’ve come and slapped the enemy two times, and stabilize the army. Unfortunately, those Dragons were being mauled by zombies right now, they weren’t in the capacity to calm the lesser Dragons.

Zhao Hai also made arrangements on this matter. In total, Zhao Hai had collected 42 Dragons between the battle in the capital as well as in the attack against the two border fortresses. At this point, 40 of those Dragons were fighting then ten Dragons of the other side. One of the Dragons was carrying his mansion, leaving him with one that was free to use. Zhao Hai sent that remaining Dragon to attack the lesser dragon army!

One has to recognize how ruthless Zhao Hai’s move was. These lesser dragons were completely afraid of the Dragons, seeing this one Dragon heading their way didn’t help their panic!

When the Dragon charged towards them, many lesser dragons began to scream, threw their weapons away and then turned around towards the mountain. They had completely lost the will and courage to fight.

Zhao Hai who currently sat on his house on the back of the Dragon, actually smiled. His high-profile manner earlier was a preparation for this. He wanted to make the enemy think that he was a madman. Even if one had the resilience of bamboo, they would still be terrified of a lunatic. This was because lunatics were completely unreasonable.

Slaughter was not something that Zhao Hai loved, he just wanted to achieve his own goals. And sometimes, in order to achieve these goals, slaughter was an unavoidable method. However, there were also moments where slaughter was not necessary.

When an army is afraid of an enemy, deserters would eventually crop up. And when a deserter comes out, more deserters would follow suit. These deserters would form a chain reaction and would finally end in the defeat of the entire army. This was the case for the lesser dragon army right now.

Their sole mental pillar were the Dragons, who gave them the courage to face against any enemy. However, if these Dragons were to disappear, then their mental strength would sharply drop.

The rout of the lesser dragons also affected the Dragons. This was a mental matter, it had nothing to do with strength. These Dragons also wanted to escape, but this kind of mentality further plunges them to the jaws of defeat!

A Dragon was killed, then turned into a Zombie Dragon, who charged towards its own ally. Then another Dragon was killed, which also joined the Zombie Dragons. This cycle continued until the courage of the remaining Dragons reached rock bottom. They had completely lost hope in living.

However, weren’t really left with no choice of retaliation. They still have their secret technique. This technique was called Heavenly Tempest. This was a type of sacrificial technique. The Dragons can use their flesh and blood as fuel, along with their souls in order to create a huge explosion. The might of this explosion was extremely strong, when a Dragon decided to self-destruct, it was possible for it to kill ten other Dragons. This technique was passed over to them by the Divine Race.

The remaining Dragons were now inclined to use this technique, but unfortunately for them, they were against Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai was a very practical person, he didn’t like to waste time. If he was against an enemy, he would kill them in one stroke, if there was no need to use tricks. What was the need to play cat and mouse? This game might look like one was playing around with a defeated enemy. But for Zhao Hai, this was just akin to teaching the mouse to the point where the cat doesn’t pose a threat anymore.

When one goes against the enemy with the mindset of playing with them, then it was possible that the one who would die was you. An act of desperation wasn’t a joke. A cornered rabbit can still bite you. As long as a bamboo was not killed, it can still pose threat to you, not to mention an enemy like the Dragon Race.

After the inferior dragons retreated, Zhao Hai didn’t pursue them but instead directed his whole undead army to clean the remaining Dragons. Just as the Dragons were prepared to take their own lives, they were suddenly drowned out by an army of undead before they themselves joined this army.

Zhao Hai and the others had conquered the camp on the foot of Accra Mountain quite easily. The next thing that they needed to do was to head up the mountain and attack the Dragon’s den, Dragon Peak!

The main reason why Zhao Hai and the others planned to have all of the lesser dragons rout was because there was a nearby Human settlement. The Accra Mountain was a haven for adventurers. Every single day, an innumerable amount adventurers went here in order to seek fortune. Their main purpose was to hunt and kill magic beasts, at the same time, they were also hoping to come across a dead adventurer’s belongings.

An adventurer was high-risk profession, especially for those that were in Accra Mountain. Although they were only on the outskirts of the mountain, there was still a possibility of meeting a high-level magic beast and get killed. Because of their life always being in a precarious state, these adventurers always brought their properties with them. And with the high rate of fatality in the mountain, there were tales of lucky adventurers coming across the properties of a dead person and becoming rich overnight. Although this situation was rare, it still managed to shake the adventurers of the continent. All of them started in participating in this scavenger hunt.

It was like lottery, everyone thinks that they were the lucky ones when the buy it, but the real prize can only be obtained by very few.

Because of the amount of adventurers going to Accra Mountain, they managed to build a huge community for them in a corner of the mountain.

This town was the closest supply point in Accra Mountain. There were a lot of people who came here every year to try their luck, making the town very prosperous.

However, the adventurers didn’t have a great time in the recent days. The Dragons controlled the Lyon Empire in a quick manner and had built a military camp at the foot of the mountain. The camp was not too far from the town, and most importantly, the lesser dragons had prohibited them from hunting magic beasts in the mountain. The adventurers in the town had no choice but to eat their reserve rations every day. At the same time, they were also hoping that the Dragons would revoke this order.

This was because the people that were in the town weren’t only those who were seeking wealth, there were also some criminals among them. This was due to the town being close to Accra Mountain, not even the Lyon Empire’s army dared to come here. Therefore, this place was also a haven for wanted people wherein they can enjoy their freedom. And even if the army came, they can just run towards the mountain and wait it out. They didn’t dare to leave the town and go to another lest they risk themselves being arrested.

Chapter 670: Being Ruthless

It is for this reason that there were a lot of people in this town. All of these people had seen a true Dragon get slaughtered, this was where the true legend began.

The reason why Zhao Hai intimidated the lesser dragons intro retreating was exactly this small town.

No matter who lived in this town, Zhao Hai didn’t intend to have innocents die in his war. Therefore, he used methods to collapse the minds of the lesser dragons so that they wouldn’t fight and cause a ruckus at the foot of the mountain. After all, a lot of Humans could get caught in the chaos.

Because the small town was quite near the lesser dragon camp, all of the adventurers were fortunate enough to witness Zhao Hai’s war against the Dragon race.

To be honest, this cannot be called a war, it was more inclined to be a one-sided slaughter. However, this slaughter was something that made the eyes of the adventurers light up. One must know that what Zhao Hai just killed were Dragons. These were beings that were deemed to be invincible by the continent. On this day, a Human actually managed to eliminate these invincible beings. Along with their bright eyes, their hearts were burning as well.

After Zhao Hai eliminated the ten Dragons, he didn’t stay, instead, he commanded his undead army and dashed through Accra Mountain. His cube formation didn’t change, the same cube was now climbing up accra mountain.

Upon seeing this, the adventurers in the town started to get daring. When Zhao Hai led his undead army to chase the lesser dragons, these adventurers also went out of the town and followed behind the undead army as they climbed up Accra Mountain.

They didn’t have the thought of picking up some cheap things. In their minds, if they weren’t able to see such a magnificent scene, then it would be quite a shame. As long as they can witness what happened in the mountain, then they can brag about it in the capital. And bragging was the most favorite activity of these adventurers.

Zhao Hai didn’t care about these adventurers, although he had discovered that they had followed behind him, he didn’t have the time to take care of them. If these guys wanted to follow, then they can do what they want. If these guys wanted to die, then Zhao Hai wouldn’t stop them.

At this time, Zhao Hai didn’t want to divert his attention. What he faces against were the Dragons. He might have been able to defeat a lot of them in the previous battles, but the Dragons were still existences that survived for tens of thousands of years. And they had nested in Accra Mountain in the same amount of time. Zhao Hai had no idea about their full strength. This was the reason why Zhao Hai didn’t become complacent when faced with these Dragons, it was not yet time to celebrate.

When Zhao Hai’s undead army entered the Accra Mountain, he can immediately feel the difference between here and the camp at the bottom of the mountain. Back in the military camp, there were only lesser dragons and not so much magic beasts. But when they were routed to Accra Mountain, there were magic beasts everywhere. Now, these magic beasts had become frantic, it didn’t matter which rank they were, all of them were throwing themselves towards Zhao Hai’s direction. In this case, Zhao Hai reckoned that the cube formation was not quite suitable in scaling the mountain. Therefore, Zhao Hai gave a command, collapsing the cube formation and turned it into fine sand as it poured over the mountain.

The crazy battle started, Zhao Hai has also come down from the back of the Bone Dragon and entered into Alien. The Bone Dragons were still flying in the sky since there were also flying beasts that needed to be taken care of. Those flying magic beasts weren’t weak, so Zhao Hai just let the Bone Dragons attract their attention while the main army were dealing with the beasts on the ground.

This was simply a screen killing. In the outskirts of Accra Mountain, there were no high-level beasts. Zhao Hai didn’t know what methods the lesser dragons used, but they had made all of the magic beasts in the mountain crazily attack Zhao Hai’s army. This made Zhao Hai’s movement difficult, very difficult.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t turn those low-level magic beasts into undead. It was because there was no need to do so, their levels were just too low and their bodies were too small. Although the magic beasts, blue eyed rabbits, long tailed chickens and the like, were frantically attacking the undead, how could they deal damage with their small strength. Even if the undead just stood there, these beasts wouldn’t be able to move them.

These beasts were just too small, and even if Zhao Hai were to make them into undead, they wouldn’t be very useful. At the same time, Zhao Hai also left those beasts for the adventurers who were trailing him. He hoped that these adventurers would take those magic beasts and leave Accra Mountain. In this way, the unnecessary casualties would be a little smaller.

Zhao Hai had disassembled the entire cube formation, but this didn’t mean that each undead was alone. They were still divided into squads of 500 people, coordinating with each other as they advanced.

Accra Mountain was just too big, and it would be impossible for Zhao Hai to let all of his undead go alone. If they were along and were to suffer multiple attacks by the Dragons, then Zhao Hai’s losses wouldn’t be very small. Therefore, Zhao Hai had them group into units of 500 each in order to deal with this problem. They would have enough power to block the Dragons then, after all, they were still 9th ranks and the Space’s undead were still able to think for themselves and know how to face the enemy.

However, this arrangement slowed their advance. After all, the amount of crazy magic beasts were colossal. Nobody knew how many magic beasts there were inside Accra Mountain, and all of those magic beasts were now crazily charging towards Zhao Hai. It was quite a scary sight, if the opponent wasn’t Zhao Hai, then they would’ve been unable to attack.

Zhao Hai and his army advanced step by step before the corpses of these magic beasts. Whether it be those who were flying, walking, or even digging holes, every single beast was going after the invading army. Zhao Hai had no other choice but to kill them in order to progress. Every patch of ground that Zhao Hai and his army walked on were completely painted with blood.

The adventurers who followed behind Zhao Hai were shocked at the number of magic beasts corpses that they had come across. Although these were common magic beasts of the continent and were things that might not even deserve killing, the sheer numbers present at this time truly made these adventurers startled.

However, these adventurers didn’t have any Space Equipments to keep the corpses. And the most important thing in their minds right now was to witness the battle and not to collect beast corpses. Therefore, most of them ignored the corpses and continued to scale the mountain, following Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai didn’t have the mood to pay attention to these adventurers. At this moment, Cai’er suddenly thought of something as she approached Zhao Hai and said, “Young Master, since these adventurers don’t want the corpses, how about we store them instead? No matter what, they are still meat. We cannot have only grain in the later war, otherwise, the soldiers would be malnourished.”

When Zhao Hai heard Cai’er, he turned his head towards the adventurers and discovered that the corpses were left in the ground. Some of them who came across higher levelled magic beasts only took their magic crystal before continuing forward.

After he saw this situation, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but sigh and said, “Alright, go send those corpses to the Space where they won’t rot. When we run out of meat later, then we’ll eat those.”

Green laughed and said, “We really don’t lack meat, but we might as well get more. What I’m afraid of was the Accra Mountain losing all of its magic beasts and become a dead mountain.”

Zhao Hai coldly snorted and said, “These magic beasts are under the control of the Dragons. If they weren’t killed right now, then the Dragons can command them to attack the Humans later on. That is the terrifying thing. Just think, blue eyed rabbits and long-tailed chickens blotting out the skies as they charge towards a Human army. That would be very dangerous, so why don’t we just use them as food?”[1]

Green and the others nodded, they knew that Zhao Hai was right in saying so. These magic beasts might look harmless but if they were to crazily attack the Humans one day, then they would become terrifying. Just thinking about a rabid rabbit charging towards you and then tearing away your flesh, that thought alone would make people shake.

Instead of waiting for that time, then Zhao Hai might as well deal with those magic beasts ahead of time. After all, they can also gain military rations along the way.

The reason why Green and the others were assured that the magic beasts would be killed was the fact the army that they commanded weren’t composed of people, they were all undead. And have you heard of a terrified undead? No. The undead had no emotions, even if they were faced with these numbers of magic beasts, even if they were to rush in front of a Dragon, all they would do was hold on to their weapons properly and then immediately attack, it was that simple.

The undead were undead, even if they were capable of thinking, they will never disobey their master. Zhao Hai’s command was to kill all of the enemies. Whether they be magic beasts or dragons, they will do it. Even if they were intelligent and were capable of rational thought, they still wouldn’t interrupt Zhao Hai’s order.

A group of people with no fear was terrifying. It was because of this that Green and the others were confident that these undeads could eliminate every beast that came to attack them. If this was a Human army, then it would be an impossible feat. In the face of overwhelming beast frenzy, they will be too scared to use all of their strength. In the end, they would only be drowned by the enemy.

Zhao Hai and the others didn’t fly directly towards Dragon’s peak but just pushed forward step by step. This was not because Zhao Hai was bloodthirsty and wanted to kill the magic beasts of the mountain ,instead, he was worried.

Zhao Hai had complete confidence in dealing with the Dragons. However, he couldn’t say the same if the Dragons were to escape. If Dragons were to escape, then they can just return to Accra Mountain and establish their magic beast army once more. When that time comes, Zhao Hai would have another headache to deal with.

* * *

I could recall the rat apocalypse in Coiling Dragon haha

Chapter 671: Transformation?

This kind of worry was not without reason. The Dragons had been in Accra Mountain for so many years. It can be said that the entire mountain had become their root. They didn’t care if people come and attacked the magic beasts, this was because the adventurers can only kill those inferior magic beasts, so it wouldn’t really affect their core strength. Moreover, if these adventurers were to come here to hunt and kill magic beasts, then the Empires of the continent wouldn’t place their attention to the mountain.

If the Dragons really turn the Accra Mountain into their exclusive place, then the Empires of the continent will definitely pay attention to it. This was because the geographical position of Accra Mountain was too important. The mountain was part of the Lyon Empire, a small region of it was part of the Buddha Empire, it was also bordered with the Dwarves and the Elves. In this case, if the Accra Mountains become a completely different kingdom, then these forces would definitely not agree to it.

Therefore, the Dragons allowed the Humans to enter and kill magic beasts in the mountain. Not only could it not affect their strength, they can also use this opportunity to observe and get information out of them. And they did this very successfully.

In the past, Zhao Hai didn’t want to be ruthless towards the magic beasts. But ever since he discovered that even the powerless blue eyed rabbits and long tailed chicken were frantically attacking him, Zhao Hai decided to remove them from the mountain. At the very least, they wouldn’t be a threat in the future.

The Dragon race’s control over the Accra Mountain was incomparably strong, one can prove this point just by seeing the blue eyed rabbits and the long tailed chickens. This can also be proven when one looks back in time to the point where the Dragons dealt with the Lyon Empire. The Lyon Empire’s main force was their cavalry, and their mounts were all taken from Accra Mountain. When the Dragons made their move against the Lyon Empire, these magic beast mounts rebelled.

However, the Dragons were unable to command the magic beasts of other people, or a magic beasts’ beast subordinates. They couldn’t just terrify those magic beasts, and even if they were terrified, they still wouldn’t frantically attack the Humans. This was also the reason why Zhao Hai didn’t fly directly towards Dragon’s Peak and just advanced slowly on the ground, attacking each and every magic beast that they had come across.

One the other hand, the adventurers that were following Zhao Hai felt that they were going crazy. Every inch of Accra Mountain was completely red, the blood of the magic beasts already gave the mountain a scarlet color.

Zhao Hai looked at everything with a calm expression. He wasn’t killing people this time, so he didn’t have much of a burden on his conscience. He felt the same as when a person slaughters a pig. Except for some special people, there weren’t a lot of people who would sympathize with the pigs. Most people would just think about how delicious the pork would be.

Although the magic beast attacks were very fierce, they didn’t have even a point of coordination. All of them were just rushing over to Zhao Hai. The arrival of these magic beasts only gave Zhao Hai’s side more food for the future.

Green looked at the frantic beasts and sighed, “It seems like our decision to deal with the Dragons is correct. If the Divine Race came and the dragons controlled these magic beasts, then the Human armies would certainly suffer huge consequences.”

While speaking about it, Green’s face couldn’t help but turn ugly. He was imagining how that scenario would turn out to be.

Kun sighed and said, “Right, the two seeds that the Divine Race had left behind were indeed terrifying. One was the Radiant Church, who used religion to control the population. And then there was the Dragon Race, who used their status to control an innumerable amount of magic beasts. If these magic beasts were like the magic beasts in other places, then they surely won’t obey the Dragons. But since the Dragons had lived in Accra mountain for too long, they were now regarded by the beasts as gods, even those who had no wisdom had sided themselves to the Dragons. If the Divine Race did come, then they would have an army that wasn’t afraid of death. With the strength of the Dragons as well as the logistical might of the Radiant Church, as well as the God-rank expert’s leadership, what kind of situation would we be facing?”

Zhao Hai sneered and said, “Even if we didn’t come and deal with the Dragons, we can still take care of them in the future, albeit being more costly in our part. But since we will eliminate them right now, this will only hasten the Radiant Church’s action, there wouldn’t be any major changes in our situation.”

Green and Kun both sighed, even if they defeat the Radiant Church and the Dragon Race, they would still suffer some disadvantages in facing the Divine Race. After all, those two forces were seeds that the Divine Race planted in the continent. Their influence and impact had already been felt and applied to the continent from their many years of operation.

Fortunately, Zhao Hai has the Space, which provided him with effective weapons in the form of the undead. Otherwise, whether it be the Radiant Church or the Dragons, they would be able to drown out Zhao Hai’s forces.

The speed that Zhao Hai advanced wasn’t fast, the magic beasts were just too crazy. It was possible that this flood of beasts wouldn’t stop. It was great that the undead didn’t get tired and weren’t lenient in killing the magic beasts. The cold slaughter was still going on.

While the slaughter was continuing, Zhao Hai and the others were now coming across higher level magic beasts. Compared to before, when they were mostly getting 1st-ranks, they were now getting 2nd and 3rd rank magic beasts.

While Zhao Hai and the others were paying attention to the magic beasts, they weren’t truly focused on the fight. Instead, they were discussing on possible methods that the Dragons would attack them later on.

Zhao Hai was quite worried about the attack of the Dragon Race. After all, this was Accra Mountain, the domain of the Dragons. Even with something like the Space’s monitor, Zhao Hai would still need to be careful.

At this time, Zhao Hai felt that the skies outside had slowly become dark. Zhao Hai stared, then was stunned when he figured it out. The skied had turned dark, it meant that a day has passed!

Upon seeing that the magic beast attack was still going on, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but breath in a cold air as he said, “We had been fighting for a day? These magic beasts are crazy. Did the Dragons drug them? Cai’er, what kind of drug is in these magic beasts?!”

Cai’er shook her head and said, “There’s no drug, Young Master. These magic beasts didn’t ingest anything. I already scanned the corpses that we had acquired before, they were all clean.”

Zhao Hai was stunned, he looked at Green and said, “This is too crazy. Can Dragons really control the beasts to this degree? I have to ask what is going on.” Then Zhao Hai called a Dragon over and said, “Can you go back to your Human form?”

The Dragon nodded, then his appearance changed and slowly turned into a person. This Dragon was the same as the previous ones that he had seen before. He was also wearing a robe that was made out of their own scales.

At this time, a prompt was then heard from the Space, “Transformation ability discovered in Cyborg beings. Extracting ability. Applying ability to all Cyborg-type beings. Application is complete.”

Zhao Hai gawked, he didn’t think that the Space could actually withdraw the Dragon’s ability to transform. At the same time, it also applied it to all the undead. Does this mean that the undead now have a Human form?

After thinking about it, Zhao Hai lost his drive to ask the Dragon about the state of the magic beasts. He took the Dragon and Alien to the Space. Then he came out of the Space and looked at Alien, “Alien, can you change into your human form?”

Alien’s human-like eyes looked at Zhao Ha,. then he shook his head. It seems like it didn’t know how to do it. So Zhao Hai turned to the Dragon and said, “What do you do when you want to go to your human form?”

The Dragon answered immediately, “Young Master, there’s no special method. As long as you think that you want to be in your human form, then that would be enough.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he turned to Alien and said, “Alien, just think that you want to be human. Understood?” Alien nodded, it seems like it understood Zhao Hai.

Then Zhao Hai saw that Alien’s figure started to shake, and then it shrank. The bones on Alien’s body shrunk as well. In the end, Zhao Hai can see a person with full body armor in front of him. The man was two meters in height, his armor was red and had spikes on them. One can understand at one glance that this person was strong. However, this person didn’t wear his headpiece, revealing his skeleton face.

Zhao Hai took a few laps to examine this man in front of him. He had discovered that Alien had turned into a real Human with a human structure. He didn’t have any tail or extra appendages. This made Zhao Hai feel quite happy.

However, when he saw Alien’s face, Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Alien, turn into a human, not a skeleton. Do it, quick, I want to see how you look.”

Alien nodded, then a white light flashed. After the light retreated, Zhao Hai saw a warrior wearing red clothes. This guy was very tall and looked quite strong. He had an ugly and terrifying face, he was also bad, he didn’t look like good person at all.

Zhao Hai looked at the new and odd Alien and said, “Alien, where’s your body armor? You can’t wear it in this form?”

Alien looked perplexed as he shook his head, then using spiritual communication, he sent, “I don’t know, Young Master. Isn’t it fine this way?”

Zhao Hai knit his brows, he was quite confused. At this time, the Dragon opened its mouth and said, “Young Master, it seems like Alien’s previous form was just like the Dragon Race’s battle form. Maybe this was the reason.”

Zhao Hai stared, then he clapped his hand and said, “So its like that. It seems like the undead can also get into three forms. This is good.”

Chapter 672: The Dragons didn’t Appear

Green and the others were happy as well. Although the strength of magic beasts were formidable, their builds were too big. And in their cramped situation inside Accra Mountain, their performance wouldn’t be as efficient as the Human form undead. So now that they had this ability, these undead magic beast would be able to display even more power.

Although Alien was still unable to speak and can only communicate over spirit transfer, this didn’t matter. It didn’t have any effect on its fighting strength.

Then Zhao Hai turned to the Dragon and then asked, “What is your name?”

The undead Dragon immediately replied, “Young Master, I’m called, Ao Sar.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Do you know why these magic beasts are still listening to the Dragons? What is happening?”

Ao Sar replied, “I do. Young Master, this is actually a secret technique that the Divine Race had left behind. This technique is called Divine Enlightenment. This technique is quite formidable, after being used on a magic beast, this magic would still manage to penetrate its descendants, making the subsequent generations loyal to the Dragon Race. No matter what we order them, they will obey, even if they are asked to commit suicide or slaughter their children. There are many uses of this technique, but it is still useless to magic beasts with high wisdom, and it also has little influence on people. At the same time, this technique uses up a lot of magic each time. But since the Dragons have been in the Accra Mountain for too long, all the magic beasts had been turned into loyal beings to the Dragons. It was precisely because of Divine Enlightenment that the magic beasts were all frantically attacking the Young Master’s army.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “So it turns out to be something left behind by the Divine Race. Can you also do this Divine Enlightenment?”

The Dragon nodded, “I can, all Dragons are capable of executing the technique.”

Zhao Hao gave a nod, “Then tell me the how you do it, let me see what this Divine Enlightenment looks like.” Then the Dragon complied, telling Zhao Hai how to execute this technique.

This Divine Enlightenment’s application method was based on light element magic, but it was not entirely light magic. It was a combination between light magic and blood magic.

When using the technique, one would use their own blood first as a guide before one casts the magic. This kind of magic would not only affect the magic beast, it would also manifest on its descendants. One could say that it was a kind of evil control magic.

Zhao Hai didn’t use the magic even though he had learned how to do it. He just wanted to understand the magic that were used by the Divine Race. Now it seems like the Divine Race were indeed powerful, they can actually combine different magic to make completely new spells.

Although the fight was still going on outside, Zhao Hai and the others didn’t rush out. It had continued for the whole day, they were even unaware that night had arrived. At this time, they felt somewhat hungry, so their had their dinner inside the Space.

Even if he left the undead outside, all of them were 9th ranks, Zhao Hai wasn’t worried about them.

While they were eating their dinner inside the Space, Zhao Hai and the others discussed the fight that happened during the day. Green took a sip of his wine and then said, “Where are the Dragons? The lesser Dragons should have already reported what just happened. Why were the magic beasts continuing to attack?”

Kun smiled faintly and said, “It isn’t really strange. The Dragons are unaware of the existence of the Space. In their minds, these undead were controlled by Dark Mages. The Dark Mage might be strong, but they couldn’t sustain commanding these undead for too long. I think the Dragons are trying to drain Little Hai’s magic by bombarding him with those magic beasts. When Little Hai’s mental power gets exhausted, the Dragons can just come and deal with him easily. Unfortunately for them, Little Hai didn’t need to expend energy in commanding the undead, he already has the Space to do that. The undead can fight as long as Little Hai wants.”

Zhao Hai gave a slight smile and said, “If the Dragons think like that, then that would be great for us. If we can kill all the magic beast in the mountain, then we would generally be taking care of the Dragons’ trump card. Even if the Dragons were to escape, they wouldn’t be a threat to us anymore.”

Green agreed, “It would be troublesome if the Dragons were to keep their magic beast army. Moreover, whether or not the Dragons survive this battle, their reputation is now ruined. After this, even the Humans wouldn’t be as scared of the Dragons as before.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “But I think the Radiant Church wouldn’t just be still upon seeing this. They would definitely have the the Divine Race act as soon as possible. Otherwise, the Divine Race wouldn’t have any allies if they were to delay. Our current exhibition has already informed the Radiant Church that they are no match against us.”

Kun nodded, “It looks like we need to prepare for even more battles.” The group sighed, the jovial mood of their dinner was now gone.

After finishing their meal, Zhao Hai and the others went to the Space’s villa and watched the crazy attacks of the magic beasts. At this point, the levels of the magic beasts that they were encountering had already reached 4th to 5th rank. However, even these levels had no impact to the undead army. It seems like in the eyes of the undead, all of these beasts were of the same level.

Upon seeing the continual magic beast assault, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but knit his brows and said, “From day to night, these magic beasts actually didn’t stop. At the same time, no Dragons can be seen. What kind of plot do they have?”

Green was frowning as well, “What are the Dragons thinking? Do they want to attack us this way? It seems to be the wrong way of doing it.”

Kun shook his head and said, “Don’t think about it too much. If they attack, then let them be. In any case, we are here to destroy them, eliminate them for good. There’s not much to think about.”

Zhao Hai nodded, but he still frowned, “But I still feel that there is something wrong. We can’t go on like this. I must make the undead deal with this as soon as possible.”

Naturally, nobody opposed to Zhao Hai’s decision. The Space had an uncountable amount of magic beast corpses, all of which can be turned into undead.

In the past, the levels of the magic beasts were too low. Although the Space can still make them into undead, their levels were really to low for them to be 9th ranks. After all, the difference was too far. Therefore, Zhao Hai didn’t turn those initial magic beasts in to undead. However, the beasts that they were killing at this point were 4th or 5th ranks. They were definitely worth turning into undead.

After deciding on what to do, Zhao Hai immediately came out of the Space and turned all of the dead magic beasts into undead, increasing the amount of undead in Zhao Hai’s army.

The Accra Mountain was extremely large, and it had many magic beasts in it, much more than Zhao Hai can count. At this point, the Space has about 10 million 1st and 2nd ranked beasts. Adding the amount of 3rd, 4th, and 5th ranks, the current count would reach 20 million. The lower ranks can be turned to army provisions, however, those with high enough levels were turned into undead. After this fight, Zhao Hai’s undead army would be much more powerful. This gave him more confidence in dealing with the Divine Race.

However, the main thing on Zhao Hai’s mind right now was his feeling of unease. It seems like something was going on, and he wanted to know about it as soon as possible.

On the other hand, the adventurers that were behind Zhao Hai had become dumbfounded. They can’t see any magic beast corpses anymore. However, the battle in front of them was still going on. There were still blood on the ground, the only thing missing were the dead corpses.

Zhao Hai didn’t have the mood to think about any of these right now. His army of undead was rapidly increasing. At first, it was the magic beasts who were attacking them, but now, Zhao Hai’s army were the ones who did the assault. Aside from the ground, the aerial battles had heated up as well. There were also a lot of flying beasts in Accra Mountain, and these flying beasts were now getting attacked by Bone Dragons, naturally, they didn’t stand a chance.

With the increase of undead, Zhao Hai’s rate of advancement had also increased. As they got closer to Dragon’s peak, 7th and 8th rank magic beasts had started to appear. Although these beasts weren’t numerous, their attacking power wasn’t something to scoff at. Even if the undead were able to deal with them, they still managed to drive them back for some time.

But still, Zhao Hai was unable to see any Dragons. This made Zhao Hai very surprised. The skies slowly turned to day, and at this point, the mountain had turned quiet. All of the magic beasts on Accra Mountain were dead.

Zhao Hai’s undead had now reached more than ten million. While Zhao Hai was continuing his slaughter up into the mountain, he was still quite puzzled as to why the Dragons still didn’t appear.

Before long, Zhao Hai finally arrived at Dragon’s peak. This place was the highest point in Accra Mountains. This place was an extinct volcano. However, even if it was extinct, it was still very hot. The place where the Dragons resided in was in the deep crater where a lake was situated in the bottom. On the inner walls of the crater, caves can be seen one after another. Those caves were the residences of the Dragons.

The terrain here had already been scouted by Zhao Hai’s staff. Therefore, Zhao Hai was very clear about the place. But what was not clear was the fact that the Dragons were still absent even if Zhao Hai was already at the mouth of their home.

After thinking about this, he immediately flew to the peak along with his undead army. He wanted to see what was going on. Did the Dragons already escape? This wasn’t very likely, it was not in line with the nature of the Dragons.

Chapter 673: Demon!

Green and the others didn’t come out, but they were still looking at Zhao Hai through the monitor. Zhao Hai commanded his army to assemble into cube formation as he slowly flew towards Dragon’s Peak.

Before long, the group arrived at the summit, however, Zhao Hai still cannot see any dragons. Zhao Hai was met with a completely empty Dragon’s Peak. He couldn’t help but stare blankly, did the Dragons actually leave?

Since he couldn’t see anything else, Zhao Hai immediately turned to look at the monitor to see if he can discover things there. Zhao Hai carefully watched the monitor, the caverns of the Dragons were still there, the things that the Dragons had collected were present as well. The only thing missing in the place were the Dragons themselves.

Zhao Hai immediately searched around using the monitor. He wanted to see whether the Dragons really left or if something else happened. He believed that there should be clues to be seen. Sure enough, Zhao Hai noticed that the lake under the crater was quite special. The monitor couldn’t see anything inside it. The same happened in the Devil Trench as well as the Soul Sucking Reef. Every place where a treasure was found seemed to exhibit this property. Was a treasure present in this lake as well?

After thinking about it, Zhao Hai immediately received the majority of his undead. Then he released some marine undead before he sat inside the Blade Scale Whale. Then the group dove into the lake.

Naturally, the monitor wasn’t able to see much into the lake. Compared to outside, the range of vision was too low, only about 500 meters.

Looking from above, the lake wasn’t very big. After Zhao Hai released the Blade Scale Whale, he could only release 100 undead creatures. If he had more, then they wouldn’t be able to enter the lake.

This 100 undead formed around Zhao Hai in a cube formation. As the slowly dived into the lake, Zhao Hai discovered something strange, the lake was actually very deep.

He was already inside the lake for about ten minutes. And in these 10 minutes, even if they dove slowly, they should have already covered several kilometers. And yet, the bottom was nowhere to be found.

This was just a lake, how could it be very deep? Zhao Hai became more curious as the dove down. He looked at the monitor and occasionally turned its view to all directions, only to see nothing. Zhao Hai didn’t care, he just continued to look at the monitor. Then suddenly, Zhao Hai felt something was wrong.

Then Zhao Hai understood, from what he can theorize, the surrounding waters had become much wider. This prompted him to look around much more seriously.

Sure enough, when he entered the lake, it wasn’t very big, he can even see the sides of the lake through the muddy waters. But now, he couldn’t see the sides anymore. The only reason for this was that the lake had widened.

Zhao Hai stared for a moment before he stopped his dive. Then he commanded the undead to look for the sides of the lake.

After a long time, Zhao Hai had finally figured out the shape of the lake. The area at the bottom of the lake was much wider than the surface. The shape of the lake was like an inverted bowl, with the mouth being the smallest part and it gets wider as it goes down.

Zhao Hai was now more curious about the lake. He commanded the Blade Scale Whale to continue the dive. At this point, Zhao Hai was convinced that he had already penetrated about 10 thousand meters into the lake, but it seems like there was no end in sight.

But what made Zhao Hai feel even more strange was the mere absence of magic beasts inside this lake. Not only magic beasts, there weren’t any plants here as well. This made Zhao Hai careful, this lake was truly out of the ordinary.

Zhao Hai carefully watched the monitor while also paying attention to his surroundings. There weren’t any magic beasts in the lake water, there weren’t any marine plants as well. The lake had now become quite clear, Zhao Hai can even see further than the monitor just by using his own two eyes.

The suddenly, Zhao Hai spotted something not far under him. There seems to be a layer of black gas. Zhao Hai found out that the monitor was unable to penetrate through that gas. Zhao Hai stopped, then he hardened his resolve as he commanded the Blade Scale Whale to go straight by the layer of gas.

Before long, Zhao Hai was surrounded by the gas. He also discovered that this gas wasn’t the bottom of the lake, instead, it seems to be shrouding something.

Zhao Hai knit the brows of his head, he felt that this layer was not simple. It can actually block the monitor, at the same time, it also seems to be concealing something inside the lake.

Zhao Hai decided to explore it by himself. He went out of the Blade Scale Whale and placed his hand on the layer. Unexpectedly, the layer allowed his hand to go through, but it also blocked the lake water from entering.

Zhao Hai felt great, he received the Blade Scale Whale before he entered the layer of gas. The layer wasn’t very thick, it was just too dark, making Zhao Hai unable to see anything. But just about two meters away, light can then be seen. Upon coming out of the layer of gas, the scene that Zhao Hai saw gave him a huge surprise.

Inside was a huge space, it might even be as big as the entire Accra Mountain. Inside this huge space was a similarly large magic formation. The formation had mostly occupied the entire space’s floor.

This magic formation looked mysteriously exceptional, it comprised of innumerable magic symbols. But what made Zhao Hai feel strange was that these magic symbols were all colored blood red, and it was connected to each other by flowing blood. Inside this magic formation were Dragons, about 10 thousand of them. All of which were in a static position on the formation. Their positions were very strange, it seems to form a strange pattern, something that looked like a devil’s face.

On the sides of the Dragons were countless amounts of lesser dragons, which were similarly just lying there. Along with the Dragons, all of them formed a huge devil face. At the same time, Zhao Hai also discovered a detail, both Dragons and lesser dragons were killed with a big wound on their necks. Their blood flowing into the magic symbols on the formation.

Zhao Hai was currently flying up above the formation. The layer of gas looked black when he was back in the lake, but now, it actually changed into the same color as blood. At the same time, red liquid was raining down from the layer of gas. When this red liquid fell to the ground, it immediately fused into the magic formation. It was quite strange because there weren’t any places that the liquid could flow into, all of them fused with the magic formations and just vanished without a trace.

Zhao Hai knitted the brows on his head again, he felt that this space was really strange. Although the entire place was bright, he could see upon further inspection that the light was also tinted red. This color scheme could actually make someone feel choked.

Zhao Hai placed his hand out and cought a drop of the red liquid and then placed it on his nose to smell it. Almost instantaneously, the smell of blood assaulted his nose. Zhao Hai’s expression immediately turned ugly, the red rain was actually blood!

Then Zhao Hai turned his head back to the formation as well as the amount of red liquid raining down. He couldn’t estimate how much blood this was.

Zhao Hai frowned, then he waved his hand as a clump of black gas came out and wrapped the Dragons and the lesser dragons. Zhao Hai wanted to turn them into undead.

At this time, a sharp screech was suddenly heard, then it was followed by a bellow, “Who dares!” Then a big bloody red hand reached out from a place not far from the layer of gas and blocked the black gas. Surprisingly it actually succeeded in doing so.

Zhao Hai gawked, his expression turned ugly, this bloody hand can actually defend against Zhao Hai’s dark magic. This showed that the owner of this hand was quite strong. Zhao Hai turned his head towards the hand and said, “Who’s there? Come out!”

“Hahaha!” An ominous laugh was heard, then a person came in from the other side of the layer. Upon seeing this person, Zhao Hai’s pupils couldn’t help but shrink. This person’s body was very tall and big, about 2.5 meters high. It wore beast skin garments but also had scales covering its body. It also had two curved horns on its head, something that looked like an argali’s horn. In each of its hand were six fingers, along with long and pointy nails that shone blue. On its back were a pair of big meaty wings that flapped constantly. It also had a tail, it was very long, about five or six meters. On the head of the tail was something that looked like an arrow point. The tail was constantly moving around, just like how snakes slithered.

At this time, Cai’er suddenly said, “Young Master, that’s someone from the Demon Realm. Specifically, from the realm’s most formidable beings, Demon Clan. In fact, the entire realm was ruled by these Demons.”

When he heard Cai’er, Zhao Hai’ eyes couldn’t help but shrink. He looked at the Demon and said, “I didn’t think that I’d be able to meet a Demon from the Demon Realm. How can you appear here?’

As soon as the Demon heard Zhao Hai, he couldn’t help but gawk. Then he laughed out loud and said, “I didn’t expect the continent to remember creatures like us. Hahaha. This is interesting, too interesting!”

Zhao Hai looked at the Demon and said, “Why can you appear here? Is there a spatial rift?”

The Demon looked at Zhao Hai and then laughed once again, “You’re quite intelligent. But you’re ruthless as well. You actually killed all of the magic beasts in Accra Mountain. Well, I think I need to thank you for that.”

Zhao Hai was puzzled, so he asked, “What do you mean?”

The Demon looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Well, in any case, you cannot escape, so it doesn’t matter if I tell you. There is actually no spatial crack here. However, the place where the rift was in in the Demonic Abyss. That was where we had set up a crack between the Demon Realm and the Ark Continent.”

Chapter 674: Blood Void

Although this was already speculated on the continent, hearing it from the mouth of a Demon still shocked Zhao Hai. It turned out to be true.

The Demon enjoyed Zhao Hai’s surprised appearance, he laughed and then gnashed his teeth as he said, “When we discovered the crack towards Ark Continent in the past, we sent people in order to investigate it. And we found out that the Ark Continent is much better than the Demon Realm. There is warm sunshine here, clean water, green grass, and endless food. For such a good place to be inhabited by inferior creatures is unforgivable. So we launched a war against the continent.”

Then the Demon’s face couldn’t help but change to hatred, “However, we didn’t think that the Ark Continent would have a strange law, disallowing God-ranked demons to come here. In the end, our Demon Race’s army got defeated by the lower lifeforms. But before returning to the Demon Realm, we left a spatial rift in the Demonic Abyss.”

After speaking about the spatial rift, the Demon’s face turned proud as he said, “That spatial rift wasn’t big, but it was quite carefully made that it would evade the notice of the Humans. This allowed us to investigate the situation in the Ark Continent. And then, more than a thousand years ago, His Majesty the Demon King decided to launch a second great war. In order to prepare for this war, a large enough spatial rift would need to be prepared. Therefore, for a thousand years, we prepared this Blood Void in order to enlarge the spatial crack. But if we want to use the Blood Void, we would need to have enough blood. Killing Humans would be detrimental to our plans, therefore we decided to use the magic beasts and the Dragons in Accra Mountain.”

After speaking up to here, the Demon looked at Zhao Hai and smiled, “For this plan, we dug out a huge space below Accra Mountain then established the Blood Void in this place. Digging the place up and establishing the Blood Void took us nearly a thousand years. And in the process, we discovered that the Dragons were subordinates of people called the Divine Race. And their purpose was to take the Ark Continent as well. So how could we make them succeed? The Ark Continent is ours, that is certain. We already have plans on how to deal with them, but you came and attacked the Dragons. You really are ruthless, but killing all the magic beasts in the Accra Mountain saved us a lot of trouble. Hahaha. To be honest, you’re quite good. If you were someone from the Demon Realm, then you would’ve gained a high position.”

Zhao Hai’s expression was quite difficult. He didn’t think that his action of eliminating the Dragons would actually help the Demons. Moreover, the Demons hadn’t been in the continent for a short time. They had been here for more than a thousand years.

The Demon looked at Zhao Hai’s expression, he got more excited as he laughed and said, “With all these blood, the operation has become a success. When the rift opens, an army from the Demon Realm shal arrive in the Ark Continent, killing the lower beings and occupying it for our own use!”

Zhao Hai coldly snorted and said, “Keep dreaming. Even if you can open the rift, what significance would that have? Your God-ranked experts are still unable to reach the continent. Do you want to rely on your army to conquer the continent? You’re being too naive.”

The Demon coldly snorted and said, “You’re the one being naive. Do you really think that your human armies can go against the people of the Demon Realm? We Demons grew up killing, every member of my race is an outstanding soldier. With just your Human army, how could you defend against the Demons?”

Zhao Hai snorted, “Hmph, I alone have an undead army of tens of millions. There’s no need for Human armies, I am sufficient enough to deal with your Demon Race.”

The Demon laughed and said, “Right, right, what you say is true. You really are quite strong. But you underestimate our Demon army. Your undead might be strong, but we have our own strong undead as well, at the very least, they can defend against your undead. Most importantly, you will die today. And with your death, your undead army shall vanish as well. So when our Demon army comes, how can the Humans cope with us, given how disunited they are?”

Zhao Hai snickered, “Are you really convinced that you can deal with me?”

The Demon laughed, “I know that you’re able to do Space Magic along with your undead magic. But what you don’t know is that the Blood Void not only opens spatial rifts, it locks space as well. Even if your undead are strong, you cannot call them over here. And although you are a 9th rank, we are 9th ranks as well. You cannot escape today.”

Zhao Hai coldly smiled and said, “That might not be true. To thank for your information, I shall allow you to be an undead and then join my own army.”

Then Zhao Hai waved his hand as large quantities of undead appeared inside the space. Then they threw themselves over to the Demons.

The Demons present looked at Zhao Hai releasing his undead with shocked faces. The lead Demon looked at Zhao Hai and said, “This is impossible. How can you summon undead? The Blood Void should have imprisoned the space here!”

Zhao Hai sneered and said, “Whether you can imprison my Space or not isn’t something for you to decide. If my Space can easily be locked, then I would’ve already died long ago.”

The Demon looked at Zhao Hai with grief, while blocking the undead, the Demon said, “Even if you can kill us, the Blood Void had already succeeded. It will show its effects and when our Demon army comes through the rift, you shall die.”

Zhao Hai coldly snorted and said, “I already knew that your Demon army would come. I just didn’t expect it to be quick. It doesn’t matter, the Ark continent is ours, and nobody can take it away.” Then Zhao Hai waved his hand as a clump of black gas flew out and surrounded the bodies of the Dragons and lesser dragons, turning them into undead.

The Demon looked at Zhao Hai’s action and couldn’t help but get more angry. He knew that even if the Blood Void succeeded, it still needs more blood in order to reach its peak. The blood of these corpses were enough to sustain that. If the blood of these Dragons were to get drained into the Blood Void, then the Blood Void would be bigger. But now that Zhao Hai had turned them into undead, the Blood Void would be smaller than expected.

However, the Demons were entangled by the undead, so they couldn’t do anything about it right now. The lead Demon clenched his teeth, he knew this operation cannot fail. Otherwise, the Demons would have no chance in conquering the Ark Continent.

At the thought of this, he gave a command to his fellow Demons. Then the other Demons surrounded him as they continued to block the undead. Then the lead Demon started to mumble a spell.

Zhao Hai knew that the Blood Void needed to be stopped, but the undead attacks did nothing. This formation seems to be invincible, there was no way to damage it. If this Blood Void continues, then the Demons would have an avenue to attack the continent. When that time comes, the Humans would certainly suffer some losses.

Therefore, Zhao Hai decided to move, he has the strength of a God, so he should be able to deal with these Demons.

But through this fight, Zhao Hai also discovered that the fighting strength of these Demons was quite strong. His undead were 9th ranks, their strength wasn’t something that common 9th ranks could endure. But these Demons were able to block the attacks of these undead, and were also able to do it for quite a long time. This was something that Zhao Hai didn’t expect.

Zhao Hai knew that he couldn’t delay this fight for much longer. His staff changed into a blood red sword, then his body moved and appeared on the side of a Demon. After that, he swung his sword towards its neck. The Demon responded quite quickly, his body immediately went down as the two horns on his head moved towards Zhao Hai. At the same time, the Demon’s tail went for Zhao Hai’s heart, like a snake with exposed fangs.

Zhao Hai coldly snorted, then he moved his sword and swung downward. This move was too fast that the Demon wasn’t able to dodge it at all. The Demon’s head was sliced by Zhao Hai, cutting it in half along the middle.

But what Zhao Hai didn’t expect was when his sword sliced the Demon’s head, it didn’t die right away. The Demon moved its hand and caught Zhao Hai’s sword, its tail continued on to penetrate towards Zhao Hai’s heart.

Zhao Hai gawked, he didn’t think that these Demons would actually have this much vitality. Its life force was so strong that it could still move despite already being killed.

However, Zhao Hai wasn’t afraid, he moved his hand and shrunk his sword into a shorter one, removing it from the grasp of the demon. At the same time, he also went to the side of another Demon, dodging the tail in the process. Then he went on and swung his sword to the other Demon.

Chapter 675: Seven Days

Zhao Hai didn’t bother himself with those Demons who were injured and were still moving. He believed that those Demons were already dead, they just kept their movements due to their abundant lifeforce.

Zhao Hai’s judgement was correct. These Demons were already dead, but since they lived in the Demon Realm all their life, their vitality was just too strong, so these fatal strikes weren’t able to kill them straight away. After counter attacking, these Demons should be motionless, this was a common deathrattle for Demons.

The middle Demon didn’t stop his incantation as he looked coldly at Zhao Hai. The incantation continued on, he didn’t move even a single bit. Even as Zhao Hai stabbed his sword through this throat, the Demon just looked at Zhao Hai. Blood was now flowing out of his mouth, but he still kept mumbling the spell. The Demon smiled at Zhao Hai and then used some of his strength and said, “Your actions are useless, the Blood Void wouldn’t stop as long as blood is present. The blood in here is already enough, and with our own blood as a primer, the Demon army will now come and avenge us.”

Zhao Hai looked at the Demon and said, “Your spell should be the self-destruct spell right? You’re just talking to me in order to pass time and include me in your explosion. Hehe, I know how strong you people are as well as how formidable the Blood Void is. However, you aren’t aware of how strong I am.”

The Demon’s complexion changed, his incantation was truly the self-destruct spell. This spell absorbs the strength of several people in order to create a very big explosion. Everything that he did before was to make Zhao Hai think that he was casting a spell in order to activate the formation. He wanted to use this method in order to kill Zhao Hai.

Actually, he was taking a risk. He knew that he wouldn’t be able to live, so he just planned to use his and the others’ blood in order to help power the formation. If he can kill Zhao Hai in the process, then it would greatly benefit the Demon Realm.

However, he didn’t know that Zhao Hai was aware of his spell. He also discovered that Zhao Hai was quite knowledgeable about the Demons. One has to know that when the Demons and the Humans fought the last time, the Demons still hadn’t invented this spell, so it was impossible for the Humans to recognize it. For Zhao Hai to know about it was truly a surprise for the Demon.

Zhao Hai looked at the Demon and said, “Do you find it strange, the reason why I know this? Well, I’m not going to tell you, think about it for the rest of your life.” Then Zhao Hai’s went back, leaving the area completely.

Naturally, the reason why Zhao Hai knew about this was Cai’er. Demons completely ignored the fact that plants were ever present in the Demon Realm. And at the same time, they were unaware of the existence of Cai’er.

Cai’er was a plant that had been watching the Demon Realm for many years, she might even know more about the Demon Realm compared to the Demons. Therefore, the Blood Void, as well as the self destruct incantation was something that she knew about.

This Blood Void was a truly powerful Demon formation, its might was quite strong for a magic formation of its kind. However, something unusually strange about this formation was that its power was exerted on someplace else.

This kind of magic formation was called a primary-secondary formation. It was a set of formation that had two parts, the blood formation and the void formation. The blood portion was the energy provider of the formation. It would collect blood and transform it into energy. Then the blood formation would then transfer the energy over to the void formation where the power is fully exerted.

Most importantly, this magic formation was irreversible, it cannot be stopped. In other words, as long as the formation is established and blood was supplied, this formation would start immediately. If the blood supplied was few, then the power would be small as well, otherwise, if the blood was in high volume, then the formation would be very formidable. With how much blood was supplied on this formation under Accra Mountain, Zhao Hai knew that it would be formidable, at the same time, the void formation was surely inside the Demonic Abyss.

After the Blood Void starts, it would take seven days before its full power can be exhibited. If someone wanted to destroy this formation in advance, then the formation would activate in advance as well. This made Zhao Hai decide to refrain from using his Bone Dragons to attack it. If he would destroy this formation, then the Demons would be coming in advance. If he just let this formation be, then he would still have seven days to prepare.[1]

The only reason why Zhao Hai attacked the Demons was to gauge how powerful they were. In the future, when the battle starts, Zhao Hai would have a basis on how strong a Demon army would be.

These Demons were truly fierce, they were 9th ranks, but in Cai’er’s words, the status of these specific Demons shouldn’t be high. They would at the very most be medium-rank. There might be a lot of these Demons in the Demon Realm, however, their army would surely be mostly comprised of low-ranked Demons, with the worst one being weaker than a Human 6th rank. But in general, a group of Human 7th ranks wouldn’t be able to contend with a group of low-ranked demons.

After hearing this, Zhao Hai’s heart couldn’t help but turn heavy. He thought that he would be fighting the Divine Race, but instead, it seems like he would be facing the Demons first.

But he didn’t regret his action in Accra Mountain, killing the magic beasts and fueling the Blood Void formation in the process. Zhao Hai knew that if he didn’t exterminate the magic beasts, then the Demons would still do it secretly just as what they did with the Dragons. The outcome of their method was no different to Zhao Hai’s plan to kill the magic beasts.

On the other hand, Zhao Hai was quite happy. He was happy to know about all of these, and the fact that he had seven days to prepare. Otherwise, if the Demons were to suddenly emerge from the Demonic Abyss, then many deaths would occur due to the Humans being caught off guard.

Just as the Zhao Hai left, the Demons exploded as well. However, Zhao Hai casted a protective shield over the formation, otherwise it might get destroyed and activate the formation in Demonic Abyss in advance.

The Demon explosion was quite strong, but since Zhao Hai was now a God-ranked expert, he didn’t bother to block. The Demons’ bodies weren’t spared and their blood fuelled the formation. Seeing all of these, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but sigh, he knew that because of this, the void formation would get stronger.

After lamenting on the fact, Zhao Hai’s body flashed as he entered the Space. Green and the others’ expressions were quite ugly while they were sitting on the villa’s living room. They were able to witness what just happened, they didn’t expect that the day for battle had come this quickly.

When Zhao Hai entered the living room, he turned his head to Green and said, “Grandpa Green, you should return to the Black Wasteland and prepare. Turn the entire place into something suitable for retreat. When the war comes, I’m afraid a lot of refugees would be forced to flee their homes. You must be ready to accept them.”

Green nodded, then Zhao Hai turned to Kun and said, “Grandpa Kun, you should head back to Golden Island and prepare as well. Have all the ships equipped for war. At the same time, have Golden Island be primed to be a stopover station.”

Kun also nodded, then Zhao Hai sighed as he retrieved his messenger fish. Then he talked to to it, “Your Majesty, can you hear me? Please answer if you can.”

Then the voice of the Mermaid Queen was heard, “I can hear mister, is there something wrong?”

Zhao Hai sighed once again, then he reiterated how he discovered the Demons as well as the matter with the Blood Void formation. After telling his story, Zhao Hai said, “I hope that Your Majesty would have her people prepare. Battle would come soon. When the time comes, the Fishman race can enter a channel that I would open that would lead you to the continent. I hope you can provide us with suitable support.”

The Queen didn’t think that the matter would come this fast, however, she still immediately replied, “Alright, Mister can feel relieved. I shall immediately arrange a Fishman army that can head to the continent right now.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he said, “Then I’ll have to thank Your Majesty in advance. I shall go and inform the others, so I need to leave the conversation first. Take care, Your Majesty.”

The Queen replied, “Mister, you take care as well. Your significance to the continent is quite huge. I hope that you can protect yourself well.’

Zhao Hai calmly replied, “Your Majesty can rest assured, I shall take care of myself. Then, Your Majesty, farewell.”

Then Zhao Hai retrieved his Messenger Fish and the took out another Fish. This messenger fish would connect to the Beast King. Zhao Hai immediately talked to the Beast King and told him about the situation, then he had the Beastmen prepare their army to fight at any time. The Beast King didn’t say anything and just agreed. The Beast King already made ample preparations, so he wasn’t too anxious about this matter.

The Zhao Hai called Billy and the Elf Queen, explaining everything to them as well. Then Zhao Hai came out of the Space and appeared inside Rosen Empire’s palace.

Zhao Hai didn’t plan to delay, he only has seven days to prepare. At this point, the Human nations were completely unaware of what was about to happen. One could say that they had zero preparation. With only seven days to prepare, this time frame was truly very short.

Because of this, Zhao Hai wanted to save as much time as possible. He would first look for the Rosen Emperor, convincing him of the events and then have him sign the beast skin scroll. After that, Zhao Hai would proceed to approach the other Emperors of the continent.

* * *

Took me a very long time to read this along with the previous chapter. In the end, they just don’t add up. In the past chapter, Zhao Hai seems to be uninformed, but here, he was.

Chapter 676: Rushing About

The place where Zhao Hai appeared on was outside the Emperor’s study. He can just appear inside, but Zhao Hai refrained from doing this in order to save the Emperor some face.

Although the Emperor’s study was quite ordinary, there were some protectors hidden inside. Even the eunuch who was guarding the door outside was an expert himself.

When Zhao Hai appeared, these protectors immediately centered their attention to him. The Eunuch outside the Emperor’s study looked coldly at Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai knew that this Eunuch was always with the Emperor, the Eunuch might look very ordinary, but in reality he was an 8th rank Assassin.

Moreover, Zhao Hai also knew that the fellow that was always with the Emperor was also a high-level expert. However, all of these matters were unimportant to Zhao Hai. He was not here to assassinate the Emperor, therefore, he bowed to the Eunuch and said, “I ask sir Eunuch to please tell Father-in-law that I needed his audience.”

The Old Eunuch naturally knew who Zhao Hai was, but since Zhao Hai appeared suddenly, he couldn’t help but get hostile. So when he heard Zhao Hai, he immediately returned the bow and said, “I ask the Emperor’s son-in-law to wait for a while.”

Then the Eunuch opened the door of the study and walked in. Before long, he came out again and gave a bow to Zhao Hai before saying, “The Emperor invites his Son-in-law inside.” Then he opened the door for Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai gave another bow to the Eunuch and said, “Thank You, Sir Eunuch.” Then he went inside the study.

The Emperor was standing inside the study with his back facing Zhao Hai. When Zhao Hai entered, he immediately bowed to the Emperor and said, “I have seen Father-in-law.”

The Emperor turned around and calmly said, “Little Hai, I always thought that you’re quite the discrete person. How come you came in this way this time?”

Zhao Hai understood what the Emperor meant, he was blaming Zhao Hai for being quite crude inside the Imperial Palace. Zhao Hai turned serious as he said, “Something quite sudden happened, so it’s quite urgent. I had no other choice but to use this method, I hope that Father can excuse me.”

The Emperor looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Alright, I know that you’re a sensible child. You wouldn’t do anything without proper purpose. Tell me, what did you come here for?”

Then Zhao Hai took out his beast skin scroll and then handed it over to the Emperor, “I’ll have Father read this first. Then I will explain it to you in detail.”

The Emperor nodded, then he received the beast skin scroll and slowly opened it. With a serious expression, the Emperor carefully read the contents.

After a short while, he placed the beast skin scroll down and looked at Zhao Hai, “Is this the reason why you dealt with the Dragons? Where are they now?”

With a straight expression, Zhao Hai replied, “They’re all dead. Not only them, all of the magic beasts in Accra Mountain has been exterminated.”

The Emperor gently knit his eyebrows and said, “You did all of that?”

Zhao Hai forced a smile and said, “Half of it. The other half is not in my credit.”

The Emperor was confused with this reply, he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “What happened? Tell me everything carefully.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he started the story when he fixed the Divine Artifact of the Dwarves, then it moved to how he retrieved the Beast God Spear, then onto when he helped the Fishmen, then to the Elves, and in the end, the Demons. Everything was said quite carefully.

The Emperor listened to Zhao Hai, and when Zhao Hai finished, the Emperor’s face was quite pale, he looked up at Zhao Hai and said, “So you’re saying that in seven days, the spatial rift in the Demonic Abyss would be opened and then a Demon army would come and invade us?”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he forced a smile and said, “I’m afraid that is what is going to happen. Moreover, there is no means to stop the Blood Void formation. If we destroy it, then the rift would immediately open. We can’t have the rift open ahead of time.”

The Emperor stood up, then he walked back and forth inside the study. After some time he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “And the Divine Race? You just said that there’s a possibility that the Divine Race would come.”

Zhao Hai bitterly smiled and said, “Yes father, its highly probable that the Divine Race would come, otherwise, the Dragons wouldn’t have made their move. It is because of this that I needed to deal with the Dragons. Originally, I wanted to come here after I had dealt with the matter with the Elves. Then after that, talk to the Emperors of the continent, having everyone work together in order to deal with the Radiant Church. And making us unite when the Divine Race arrives. However, it seems like that wouldn’t work anymore because of the appearance of the Demons as well as the motion of the Dragons. Even if the Demons weren’t present, we still couldn’t afford to have the Dragons take control of the Lyon Empire. .If that happens and the Divine Realm did come, we would be placed in a much more passive position compared to if the Dragons were eliminated.”

The Emperor looked at Zhao Hai, then he sighed and said, “So it turns out that you had been busy with this for a long time. I really didn’t think that the Demons and the Divine Race would take interest in our continent. It seems like a huge chaos is coming. You can rest assured, I shall immediately have my men prepare. Are you going to the other Empires now?”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Yes, the next one that I’ll go to is the Buddha Empire. The Demonic Abyss is situated there. I must have them prepare ahead of time. Father, please sign this beast skin scroll. I’m afraid that I won’t be able to convince the Buddha Emperor if I don’t have your mark.”

The Emperor nodded and said, “Alright, then I’ll sign it immediately so that you can get on your way.” Then he picked up his pen and signed the beast skin scroll. After that, he handed the scroll over to Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai took the scroll before giving the Emperor a bow and then vanished from the room.

After Zhao Hai left, the Emperor talked, “What do you think?”

A chilly voice answered, “Chaos has come.”

The Emperor nodded, then he turned his head and shouted a command, “Strike the Palace Drums, ring the Warning Bell!” The Eunuch complied and then left his position.

The Palace Drums and the Warning Bell were symbolic items of the Rosen Empire. Only during life and death situations of the Empire would the drums be used. At the same time, when the Warning Bell sounds and rings for 12 times, all the Nobles and Ministers of the Empire should already be inside the Imperial Palace. If one fails to arrive, then they would have their title revoked and then executed for treason. One could see from these scenarios how important those two items were.

Zhao Hai didn’t have the mood to care about this now. He had appeared outside the Buddha Empire’s Imperial palace. He didn’t appear inside the Imperial Palace, after all, he only had a few dealings with the Buddha Empire. His status here wasn’t as high as back in the Rosen Empire.

Zhao Hai knew that if he appeared inside the Imperial Palace, then the Buddha Emperor would surely come to dislike him. For Zhao Hai, this scenario was extremely detrimental to his cause. Therefore, he chose to appear right outside the palace.

After Zhao Hai arrived, he immediately went towards the reception. The reception was just like the one in Rosen Empire. There were two Eunuchs in charge of registering everyone who came to visit. At the same time, there were also some Eunuchs fluttering in all directions.

When Zhao Hai entered the reception, he immediately bowed towards the two Eunuchs, “This one has seen the Sir Eunuchs. This one is Zhao Hai, I’m here to seek an audience with the Buddha Emperor.”

The two Eunuchs knew about Zhao Hai’s status, therefore, they didn’t dare to ignore him. The two of them stood up and bowed to Zhao Hai as one of them said, “Are you the Buda Clan’s Patriarch, Mister Zhao Hai?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I am indeed Zhao Hai. Please do arrange a meeting with the Emperor. I came here for an urgent matter.”

The two Eunuchs didn’t dare to delay, so one of them immediately said, “Right, Mister can rest assured, we shall take this matter with haste. Please take a seat first, Mister.” Then one of the Eunuch wrote Zhao Hai’s name in the record as one of them immediately arranged for someone to inform the Imperial Palace.

The response of the two eunuchs wasn’t strange. Zhao Hai’s status in the Buddha Empire wasn’t low, after all, he has established a magic beast business with the Buddha Empire. At the same time, everyone knew that the Buddha Emperor has a good impression of Zhao Hai. He even hosted a banquet to welcome him, the Emperor was even quite happy when talking to Zhao Hai.

And most importantly, rumors has been circulating in the past two days. It was said that Zhao Hai had eliminated 40 Dragons inside the Lyon Empire’s capital. Zhao Hai has become the first Human to slay a Dragon in the current history of the Human race.

Therefore, these eunuchs didn’t dare to neglect Zhao Hai’s visit. Even if they had all the courage of their lifetime, they still wouldn’t dare to offend someone who had slain a Dragon.

Before long, a young eunuch came and bowed to Zhao Hai, “Mister, please come with me. The Emperor has invited you over to his study.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he walked towards the Imperial Palace along with that young eunuch. It didn’t take a long time before they arrived outside the Buddha Emperor’s study. The Eunuch who guarded the Emperor’s study immediately bowed to Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, come in. His Majesty is already waiting for you.” Zhao Hai nodded and then entered the room.

The Buddha Emperor was already standing inside, waiting for Zhao Hai to come in. When he saw Zhao Hai arrive, the Buddha Emperor immediately laughed and said, “Mister, why did you come? What made you so anxious that you had to make an urgent appointment?”

Zhao Hai bowed and replied, “I have seen Your Majesty. I came here this time in order to discuss about an important matter.”

The Emperor smiled and said, “Mister is too polite. Please sit down and then tell me.”

After Zhao Hai gave his thanks to the Emperor, he took out his beast skin scroll and said, “Your Majesty, please take a look at this first. Then I will tell you the details.”

The Buddha Emperor smiled, then he received the scroll and slowly unraveled ut. His response was similar to the Rosen Emperor. He had a shocked expression while he read the scroll. Then he looked up at Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, are the contents in here true?”

Zhao Hao nodded and said, “This is a crucial matter, so how can I deceive Your Majesty? This information only tells a small part of the story. The reason why I deal with the Dragons was because…..” Then Zhao Hai told the Emperor everything up to the Demon Race’s matter. When the Buddha Emperor heard that a spatial rift would open, and moreover, in the Demonic Abyss, his face couldn’t help but turn pale.

Chapter 677: Your Excellency, You Have No Choice But To Govern Us

What can seven days make?

If this question was presented to the commoners, then they would surely provide a multitude of answers. However, for an Emperor who would receive an attack on his empire, these seven days was just too short.

This was what the Buddha Emperor was thinking about right now. Seven days was just too short, he was stumped on what to do.

When Zhao Hai left the Buddha Empire, he then went to the Aksu Empire to tell Boris of this information. Although Zhao Hai and Boris had a grudge in the past, Boris was now quite angry towards the Radiant Church. Moreover, this was a Demon invasion, so no matter what, Zhao Hai still needs to tell Boris about it. After all, Boris was also an Emperor of a Human nation.

After he awkwardly told the news to Boris, Zhao Hai went back to the Lyon Empire. Zhao Hai knew what was currently going on in the Lyon Empire. The Empire was now in a state of anarchy. The Great Nobles were currently managing the Empire. However, in the minds of these Nobles, Zhao Hai was the Lyon Empire’s current ruler. Therefore, it was Zhao Hai’s tasks to manage the things in the Empire.

Zhao Hai didn’t teleport towards the Lyon Empire. Instead, after he came out of the Space, he rode on the back of a Bone Dragon and then entered the capital.

Just as he arrived at the capital’s skies, he immediately discovered that the place exploded into cheers. Zhao Hai looked downward and saw civilian people standing on the square and cheering at him.

Zhao Hai wasn’t expecting the situation, he didn’t’t think that the Lyon Empire’s commoners would like him this much. This made him confused, in his opinion, he didn’t do anything. So why would these people cheer for him?

Although the Dragons had ruled the Empire for a few days, but because of how overboard the lesser dragons had become, killing civilians whenever they want, it wasn’t strange that the civilians had already hated the Dragons.

But since the Dragons were very powerful, and were quite known to be invincible, the commoners were left not being able to resist. Now that Zhao Hai had eliminated the Dragons, the civilians were naturally very happy.

While riding the Bone Dragon, Zhao Hai flew directly to the Lyon Empire’s palace. As soon as he landed on the square, the Great Nobles immediately welcomed him. They originally weren’t in the palace, but when they heard that Zhao Hai had come, they immediately went to see him.

Zhao Hai looked at the nobles and then said, “Let’s go to the Great Hall, I have something to tell you all.” Then he turned to walk towards the Imperial Palace Great Hall.

These Nobles looked at Zhao Hai with no hostility, instead, all of them had a very happy expression. In their minds, for Zhao Hai to go to the Great Hall, this meant that he had accepted his own status, and that he would rule the Lyon Empire.

Moreover, the mere fact that Zhao Hai came back meant that his fight with the Dragons was finished. After seeing Zhao Hai being safe and sound, without a single scratch on his body, it showed the nobles that Zhao Hai did indeed have the overwhelming strength to face the Dragons!

These Great Nobles didn’t think that Zhao Hai could eliminate the Dragons. In their opinion, this task was impossible. Not suffering any losses was already good, so how was is possible to eradicate the Dragons.

When Zhao Hai headed to the Great Hall, these Nobles also followed behind him. Zhao Hai looked at the throne in the Great Hall and then sighed. He didn’t sit on the throne and just turned to look at the Nobles. These Nobles felt a chill when they met Zhao Hai’s gaze. They couldn’t help but get startled, they knew that Zhao Hai didn’t like them, so they just lowered their heads in obedience.

After scanning the Nobles, Zhao Hai said, “Did you know what you just did? You almost made the Humans fall into an irredeemable place just because of benefits. I really want to kill all of you, I really do!”

The Nobles lowered their heads further. They can feel the killing intent in Zhao Hai’s words. If that killing intent was tangible, then they would have had trouble breathing.

Zhao Hai coldly snorted, then he turned his hand over and retrieved the beast skin scroll, then he threw it over to a Great Noble and said, “Look at it yourself and see if I am exaggerating.”

The Great Noble caught the beast skin scroll and looked at it. He read the contents of the scroll and when he was finished, he was coldly sweating when he looked at Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai coldly snorted, then the Great Noble couldn’t help but bend his waist. Then the scroll was handed over to the next noble who had the exact same reaction as the first one. The scroll was then passed over to the Great Nobles inside the Hall before the scroll returned to Zhao Hai’s hands. At this point, the Nobles in the hall were having pale expressions. The word ‘frightened’ was an understatement.

Zhao Hai swept his gaze across the hall and then sighed, “There’s no use in scolding all of you right now. I’m not familiar with the Lyon Empire, so I cannot be the Emperor. With how things are going, I don’t have the time to be a ruler. You have seven days to prepare.” Then Zhao Hai told them about his encounter with the Demons back in Accra Mountain.

The mouths of these Nobles were gaped open as their eyes stared straight at Zhao Hai, it seems like they had turned into idiots. They didn’t think that a calamity has come. The Demons would arrive to the continent soon. This was the Demons, beings who would kill humans without even blinking. How could this be!

Zhao Hai looked at the expressions of these Nobles and coldly snorted, making these Great Nobles recover their senses. All of them looked at each other, they didn’t think that matters would come this quickly. There were seven days before the Demon army arrives, what can they do in these seven days?

Zhao Hai snorted and said, “Seven days, think about what you would do in seven days. It would be impossible for me to stay in the Lyon Empire for all this time. I shall be heading to the Buddha Empire in order to assist them with resisting the Demon Army. As for the Lyon Empire? It would be left to your discretion. Whether you want it to crumble or to return to its former glory before the Dragons arrived, I don’t care. All of these shall be left to all of you to take care of.”

And just as Zhao Hai finished talking, the Great Nobles knelt in front of him as the oldest one of them said, “Your Excellency, you have no other choice but to govern us. We know that we had made a mistake, but we truly didn’t expect the situation to reach this degree. We ask Your Excellency to remain. We want you to be the Lyon Empire’s rules, please stay here.”

The other nobles expressed their agreement.When he saw these people, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but feel a headache. He does not have the time to manage an Empire at this time. The Demons were about to appear and he needs to be in the frontlines of battle to block them. This would give the Rosen Empire and the other powers to make their proper arrangements.

Zhao Hai looked at the Great Nobles and sighed, “I really dont’ have the time to manage the Lyon Empire. The Demons are coming soon, and I need to head towards the Demonic Abyss right now in order to find a way to block the Demons. Only in this way would the continent be able to have a little more time to prepare.”

The Nobles looked at each other, they knew that what Zhao Hai said was true. But at this time, the Lyon Empire needed Zhao Hai. After the matter with the Dragons, the Great Nobles weren’t exactly well regarded by the population. No matter which one of them were to become the Emperor, the civilians would naturally disagree. And a chaotic Lyon Empire wasn’t what they need right now, seeing that the Demons have come.

At the same time, Zhao Hai also knew that what the old Noble said was true, he couldn’t help but have a headache. Zhao Hai was aware that the Great Nobles had already lost popular support. This was because they were largely responsible for the Dragons’ quick occupation of the Lyon Empire. The commoners had hostile feeling to these fellows, and if one of them were to get the throne, then the entire Empire would definitely thrown into chaos. On the other hand, if Zhao Hai were to take the seat of the Emperor, then the populace would surely accept it.

Thinking about these matter did indeed cause Zhao Hai’s head to ache, he looked at these Nobles and couldn’t help but sigh, “I can be the Emperor and I shall go and announce it outside later. But after that, I shall be heading to the Demonic Abyss. The remaining matters would need to be handed over to all of you. However, I shall have someone supervise all of your actions.

When the Great Nobles heard Zhao Hai, they immediately burst into happiness. Zhao Hai doing this meant that he would just be an Emperor in name, while the nobles had the true power in their hands. However, this happiness wasn’t because of the power, it was because of Zhao Hai accepting the throne. If he still declined, then the Lyon Empire would be finished.

Once the Lyon Empire turned chaotic, the ones who would lose out greatly would be these Nobles. Although they were thousand year old clans, their roots were still in the Lyon Empire. They couldn’t afford to have the Empire be in a chaotic state.

Zhao Hai looked at the Nobles of this Empire, then he coldly snorted and said, “Wait a moment.” Then his body vanished. Before long, he reappeared along with two other people. On of them was a man with a stature that was tall and big, he was about two meters tall. The other one was a woman, tall and beautiful, but her complexion was quite pale, it seems like she was not quite healthy.

Zhao Hai looked at these Nobles and said, “I’ll be heading to the Demonic Abyss. The matters of the Empire shall be handed to all of you. This is Evan and Ruyen. If there’s something that you cannot decide on, then ask for their opinion. Understood?”

Chapter 678: History’s Most Unique Throne Ascension

Aside from Evan and Ruyen, Zhao Hai really didn’t have anybody else to call over. And since Evan had ruled over a Duchy in the past, he should have some experience in running a country.

Ruyen has done a good job in Aksu Empire all this time.  It was impossible for Zhao Hai to see her for a long time so her mood has not been that great. This affected her lifestyle and in turn she looked quite a bit sick.

In fact, Evan was already enough to manage the Lyon Empire, Ruyen wasn’t needed here at all. However, Zhao Hai had no choice, if Evan was alone, then these Great Nobles might continue to misbehave. But if Ruyen was here, then those Great Nobles would think that Ruyen was Zhao Hai’s woman, so they shouldn’t dare show their bad sides to her.

Zhao Hai knew that these Great Nobles didn’t want to offend him right now. If it weren’t for his strength, then these Nobles would’ve been shredded by the continent a long time ago. The only reason why the Lyon Empire remained untouched was because of Zhao Hai. Since he was the one who attacked the Lyon Empire, then the other nations gave him face in not attacking. But if Zhao Hai left, then these Great Nobles would meet an attack by almost everyone, dismembering the entire Lyon Empire.

If we set aside the reaction of the other Nobles of the continent, if the civilians were to know something, then the Nobles wouldn’t have a good future.

Therefore, these Lyon Empire Nobles can only rely on Zhao Hai. It can be said that if Zhao Hai establishes a country, these Nobles would be the first to flock to Zhao Hai’s side. This was because other than Zhao Hai, nobody would want to have them.

The reason why Zhao Hai didn’t make Laura manage the Lyon Empire was because she didn’t have the experience of running a country. Although Laura had been managing the Markey Family, and even some parts of the Buda Clan, it was still different from the Lyon Empire. Back in the family, there were nobody that could undermine Laura’s authority. In Lyon Empire, problems such as these Great Nobles were present, and Laura had no experience in managing these kinds of people.

Additionally, Zhao Hai had things to discuss with Laura, therefore, Laura cannot stay and manage an Empire. Megan and Lizzy can’t do it as well since they were needed to command armies when dealing with the Demons.

As for Megan and Ni’er, having them manage a country? This wasn’t the time for cracking jokes. Knowledge on management cannot be learned in a day, they weren’t any use at all. More importantly, Zhao Hai had Meg and Ni’er manage the Fishmen in the Space’s sea. Therefore, Zhao Hai had no choice but to invite Evan and Ruyen over in order to manage the Lyon Empire.

Sure enough, when the Great Nobles saw Ruyen, they immediately thought that she was Zhao Hai’s woman. Almost immediately, all of them bowed to Ruyen and said, “We have seen the Madam.” Ruyen’s pale face immediately turned red, but just as she was about to refute, Zhao Hai waved his hand calmly and said, “This is Grand Duke Evan, Ruyen’s father. You can handle everything yourselves later, but if there’s anything that needed consent, just approach them. They will find a way to contact me.”

The Great Nobles immediately complied, Zhao Hai looked at their faces and said, “Alright, then I’m done here. After I leave, I shall tell everyone that I’ll be acting as the temporary Emperor to the Lyon Empire. The overall management of the Empire shall be handed over to Prime Minister Evan. All of you shall help him manage the Empire. After I leave, all of you should do your best to have the Empire prepare for war in the shortest possible time. Since the Lyon Empire is known for its Magic Beast Cavalry, you don’t need to worry about this. I shall release some magic beasts that I acquired back in the lesser dragon camp. You may divide those magic beasts among yourselves. Understood?”

The Great Nobles immediately replied, “Yes, Your Excellency.” Zhao Hai nodded and then turned to leave the palace.

Outside the Great Hall, Zhao Hai released his Bone Dragon and then rode on its back. Under the gazes of Evan, Ruyen, and the other Nobles, Zhao Hai flew up.

Zhao Hai’s flight path wasn’t high, he just flew over the sky of the Lyon Empire’s capital. The civilians could clearly see him on the back of the Bone Dragon.

While he flew, Zhao Hai said, “People of the Lyon Empire, listen to me. I have already eliminated the evil Dragons, you don’t have to worry about them anymore. However, when I dealt with the Dragons, I had discovered a connection to the Demons. The Demons had made a magic array in order to open a spatial rift between the Demon Realm and the Ark Continent. In seven days, that spatial rift would open, that spatial rift is located inside the Demonic Abyss. I shall be heading there in order to meet the Demons head-on. I shall announce myself as the temporary Emperor of the Lyon Empire. But since I am going to battle, I shall be appointing Grand Duke Evan as the Prime Minister of the Lyon Empire. I hope all of you will cooperate with him in the future!”

This was the most unique ceremony in the continent’s history, the most unique speech in history, as well as the most unique throne ascension in history. It was the first time that someone took the throne and just left afterwards.

And along with Zhao Hai’s words, the Lyon Empire’s capital had erupted into chaos. However, undead suddenly started to appear, stabilizing the mood of the citizens.

Zhao Hai knew that the big Empires of the continent had started to move. And because of its special situation, the Lyon Empire would surely be the last one to prepare. Additionally, Zhao Hai cannot manage the Empire, the only methods that he can think about right now was this.

After seeing that the undead had managed to calm the populace, Zhao Hai said, “Everyone shouldn’t be afraid. The big Empires as well as the other races of the continent are already aware of this information. Everyone has united together in order to face this crisis. I hope that everyone would calm themselves.”

Although these civilians were scared, they couldn’t help but behave when they saw the undead. And as long as things proceeded peacefully, everything else would be fine.

After Zhao Hai said these, he had his Bone Dragon return to the Imperial palace. When he entered the Great Hall,  he immediately had the Nobles go out and appease the populace.

These Great Nobles didn’t dare make any mistakes at this point. They knew that since the Demons had come, then Zhao Hai would be unable to help them stabilize the current situation. And if they were to disappoint Zhao Hai, then he might be impolite towards them. Therefore, the Nobles issued their compliance and then immediately went out.

After seeing that the Nobles had left, Zhao Hai turned to Evan and said, “Uncle Evan, Ruyen, I’ll be handing the Lyon Empire over to you temporarily. I need to head towards the Demonic Abyss as soon as possible since I am still completely unaware of the situation there. I’ll have to ask you to guide the Lyon Empire in assisting the Buddha Empire and the Dwarf Race in preparing to defend against the Demon invasion. I’m afraid the Buddha Empire wouldn’t be able to handle it by themselves.”

Evan couldn’t help but knit his brows and said, “Is the situation really serious? The undead in your hand had already crossed ten million. And we’re already clear about how strong those undead are, do the Demons have as much experts?”

Zhao Hai forced a smile and said, “I’m afraid so, the Demon Realm is a lot bigger than the Ark Continent. With how bad the environment is there, the Demons have been constantly subjected to killing and fighting. And this time, they had come prepared, I’m afraid that the matter wouldn’t be easy to deal with.”

Evan frowned, then he sighed and said, “Alright, then you can leave the Lyon Empire to me. You be careful in the Demonic Abyss.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then his voice turned serious as he said, “Observe these Nobles well. I’m not completely confident in them. If anything strange happens, immediately inform me and I will immediately deal with them.”

Evan faintly smiled and said, “Rest assured, from what I can see in their expressions, they wouldn’t dare to misbehave. Except for us, nobody in the continent would dare to accept them.”

Zhao Hai coldly replied, “There’s still the Radiant Church. Don’t forget that the success of the Dragons was due to those Nobles. And I’m quite sure that the Dragons weren’t the ones who lobbied them. So it must be the Radiant Church, perhaps offering them with a lot of benefits. Although they were now aware of the Divine Race, we shouldn’t forget that a lot of Humans have sided themselves with the Divine Race in the last great war. We should prevent them from going to the Divine Race, especially when they learn how hard it would be in the frontlines.”

Evan knitted his brows and said, “Hard? Even if the battle would be no good, they shouldn’t just surrender to the Divine Race. After all, what could the Divine Race offer them?”

Zhao Hai sneered, “They can give them shelter. Although there aren’t any records of the Divine Race in the Human history, we shouldn’t forget about the existence of the Radiant Church. Also, the Divine Race has the strength to not be afraid of the Demons. If the Divine Race were to give them shelter, then it would not be impossible for those guys to agree. After all, the most important thing to those Nobles are their family and their status.”

Evan couldn’t help but agree, then he said, “Alright, you can rest assured that I shall be looking at their actions. There won’t be any problems.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he took out a messenger fish, “Take this messenger fish, you can use this to contact me directly. I shall be leaving a thousand undead for you to command. Remember, no matter what happens in Lyon Empire, always keep your own safety as a priority. Even if the Divine Race came, I believe that those undead could still keep them off for quite some time. That would give me time to pick you up.”

Evan nodded, then he received the messenger fish. At this time, Zhao Hai turned to look at Ruyen, who also looked back at him. Then Zhao Hai said, “Ruyen, you should understand why I haven’t been able to see you for all this time. After everything gets settled down, I shall give you what you deserve.”

Ruyen understood what Zhao Hai meant, her face couldn’t help but go red as she gently nodded and said, “I’ll wait for you.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he turned to nod at Evan and said, “Then I shall leave everything here to you.” After that, his body vanished as he entered the Space.

Chapter 679: Demon

Zhao Hai sat in the Space and gave a long sigh of relief. Then he glanced at the monitor. The monitor didn’t display the Lyon Empire, instead, it showed a fortress city.

This city is quite famous in the Buddha Empire, this was because it had a very interesting name, Demon City. Naturally, this wasn’t a place occupied by the Demons. Instead, this was a city that was closest to the Demonic Abyss. This place is completely different to the town back in Accra Mountain. The town on Accra Mountain rarely gets attacked by magic beasts. But in Demon City, the situation is different. At any time, it was possible for the city to be attacked by beings coming out from the Demonic Abyss.

Because of this characteristic, Dark Mages proliferated in this city. This was because the undead were the most common creatures that can be found inside the Demonic Abyss. If Dark Mages were to subdue several of them, then their abilities would be improved. This was the reason that it’s called Demon City.

Even when the Radiant Church was at its peak period in the continent, they still wouldn’t easily dare come to Demon City. There were just too many Dark Mages here. Therefore, the Radiant Church has no other choice but turn a blind eye towards this city,

For the Dark Mages in Demon City, this place was their Holy Land. In their hearts, this was a sacred place, while the others pinned that title to the Calci Family.

Compared to the family-style management of the Calci Family, the Dark Mages in Demon City had more of an alliance. They were all living in Demon City, relying on hunting dark creatures for a living. Therefore, it was even thought that the Dark Mages here were stronger compared to the Dark Mages of the Calci Family.

While Zhao Hai came to visit the Buddha Emperor, he also had Cai’er use the Blood Ghost Staff to investigate the terrain in and around this place.

There were still many businessmen and adventurers here, however, one could notice that the population was now quite skewed towards the Dark Mages and the army of the Buddha Empire. Almost all of the civilians were evacuated.

Zhao Hai inspected Demon City. Probably because of its year-round battles, the walls of the city looked very thick and heavily damaged. One could even see blood on the walls. Compared to the walls of other cities, this one surely did seem to be more murderous.

At this time, Meg brought a cup of tea over to Zhao Hai. When she saw Zhao Hai’s complexion, she grieved as she said, “Young master, you should take a rest. Let me give you a massage.”

Zhao Hai turned his head towards Meg, he smiled faintly and said, “What are the others doing? Why are they not here?’

Meg went behind Zhao Hai and gently massaged his head, at the same time, she answered, “Elder Sister Laura is examining the overall commodities in our storage and is discussing matters with Patriarch Billy regarding its distribution. At the same time, Megan and Lizzy are studying the map.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he held Meg’s hand and said, “Alright, I’m fine really. Come and take a seat with me for a while.”

Meg nodded, then the went around the sofa and sat behind Zhao Hai, snuggling gently on his bosom. Zhao Hai held Meg’s soft body and upon smelling her delicate fragrance, began to relax his nerves slowly.

Meg also felt Zhao Hai becoming more relaxed, she placed her ear to Zhao Hai’s chest and listened to his heartbeat, then she said with a soft voice, “Young Master, can we win?”

Zhao Hai replied with a serious tone, “Of course we can. Our destiny can only be decided by ourselves, nobody can control our lives.”

Meg nodded, then she said, “Young Master, after repelling the Demons and the Divine Race, what should we do next? Will we go back to the Black Wasteland and live in seclusion?”

Zhao Hai coldly snorted and said, “Why would we live in seclusion? If we did repel the Demons and the Divine Race, then we would follow them to the Demon Realm and the Divine Realm. We need to cause them irreparable damage so that they wouldn’t think about returning to the Ark Continent. Otherwise, they would recover and then try to invade the Ark Continent once more. We can’t live forever and we would have our own children soon. If we die and leave our offspring here, we cannot have them suffer attacks from the Demon Realm and the Divine Race once again.”

Meg’s face turned red, she sat up and looked at Zhao Hai, “Young Master, why don’t you answer my question properly? And what are you talking about, children?”

Zhao Hai faintly smiled and said, “Look, we have been married for quite some time, but we still haven’t had a child. I’m just looking after Grandpa Green and Grandma Merine’s worries. They had always wanted a new heir to the Buda Clan.”

Meg blushed and rolled her eyes at Zhao Hai. However, she didn’t leave, instead, she leaned towards Zhao Hai’s body and said, “I really hope that everyone would be happily together all the time, not thinking about many things. Brother Hai, why do people do this? Why would the Demons and the Divine Race want to invade us?”

Zhao Hai forced a smile and said, “No other reason but ambition. In the eyes of the Divine Race, the Ark Continent is a source of troops. Naturally, when they control the continent, they would be treating everyone here as slaves. Then the slaves would join their armies and fight their enemies. On the other hand, the Demons see the continent as a huge cake. The living environment of the Demon Realm is extremely terrible, therefore, they want to occupy the Ark Continent. Unfortunately, the Demons are used to slaughter, so they didn’t even think about a peaceful method in order to reside in the continent. Instead, they wanted to kill every single creature in the continent in order to make way for their own population to move in. At the same time, I also think that the Demons are afraid. From what I learned when I met the Demon in Accra Mountain, they have been investigating the continent for more than a thousand years. Therefore, they must have learned about how the Humans were suppressing the other races. And since the Demons were also a foreign race, then it was natural that the Humans would suppress them as well. If they were to come peacefully and get suppressed by the Humans, then they might as well kill off everyone in the continent.”

Meg was confused, “Young Master, didn’t Cai’er say that the Demon Realm is much larger than the Ark Continent? Then once they take the continent, wouldn’t they have problems in accommodating everyone?”

Zhao Hai coldly snorted and said, “Of course, but there was no use in thinking about other people. As long as the high-ranked Demons can live here then all is good. These low-level Demons can be neglected then. This is the rule of the Demon Realm. Once you have a high rank in the hierarchy, then you would get anything that you want. If you are a low-ranked Demon and then managed to get something good, then you would have to hand it over to a higher-ranked Demon. Otherwise, it would only bring you disaster. To put it bluntly, the lower-ranked Demons are the high-ranked Demons’ slaves.”

Meg nodded, “So it’s like that. How about the amount of soldiers that would come here? Does Cai’er know?”

Zhao Hai nodded and smiled bitterly, “How can Cai’er not know? One could say that Cai’er is the most informed person with regards to the Demon Realm. From what she can estimate, the army that would arrive would have no less than 50 million soldiers in it.”

Meg was greatly surprised, “50 million? That much?”

Zhao Hai forced a smile and said, “And that number only counts the number of Demons that would come. We didn’t include the number of magic beasts that would join them. At the same time, there are also Dark Mages among the Demon Army, completely capable of summoning undead. If a battle happens, their numbers wouldn’t go down too fast. We really have  met a difficult opponent this time.”

Meg’s complexion changed dramatically, “What do we do?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “It’s fine. You can rest assured that there’s no need to worry. If they have 50 million troops, then the continent has its own army as well. And for those who can summon the undead, let’s see how they fare against me. There’s no need to be afraid, everything will be fine.”

Meg nodded, then Zhao Hai turned his gaze towards the monitor. There were no changes in Demon City, there were some Dark Mages and adventurers that left, but the majority of them still stayed behind. They wanted to help the army of the Buddha Empire in fighting off the Demon army.”

These Dark Mages and Adventurers clearly understood that the Demons wouldn’t spare anyone in the continent. If they leave today, sooner or later, they would still face the Demons. These Dark Mages and Adventurers were also people who liked to live beside the blade of a knife. So after knowing that the Demons were coming, not only did they stay, the also prepared to fight against the Demons.

Also, the Buddha Empire had sent word that as long as they make meritorious deeds in the battle against the Demons, then they might gain themselves a hereditary noble title. This prize was too tempting for the Adventurers and Dark Mages.

One must know that a hereditary title was completely different to an ordinary one. It would be impossible for ordinary nobles to pass their title to their children. For example, when Mages who were given their titles die, their status would be gone. Only if they had a child with good talent and becomes a great Mage, then that child would have the right to apply for inheriting the title.

The Buddha Empire had truly placed sufficient capital this time. They didn’t have much troops in the vicinity of Demon City. And in a short period of seven days, it would be impossible for them to assemble an army for reinforcement. Therefore, the Buddha Emperor made a decision, provide the Adventurers and Dark Mages with benefits of great titles so that they would stay behind and defend the city. These people had lived in this place all year round, so they should have the right abilities to defend against the Demon army.

It was because of this that large quantities of Adventurers and Dark Mages had remained and decided to fight the Demon Race together with the Buddha Empire’s army.

However, the Buddha Empire can only gather about two hundred regular troops in these seven days. If we add the Adventurers and Dark Mages, then it might reach about four hundred thousand. Although these numbers were quite strong, it was still impossible if they were to defend against the Demon Army. Therefore, Zhao Hai decided to head towards Demon City and take personal command of the defenders!

Chapter 680: Protecting the Homeland

Wei Gan was a Dark Mage who had lived in Demon City for a long time. He wasn’t from the Calci Family, once can say that he had nothing to do with the Calci Family at all. However, one shouldn’t think that he’s just a simple character. More than a thousand years ago, Wei Gan’s ancestors were formidable Mages of a huge empire, their family even held the title of a Duke.

However, it was just a pity that the Empire that his family held loyalty to was extinguished by the Lyon Empire. Since their family were loyalists to their Empire, the Lyon Empire took their title away. Moreover, they were also suppressed everywhere. In the end, their family couldn’t endure it anymore and ran away to Demon City.

In every empire, there would always be a place where the strongest people gather. Take the Lyon Empire, for example, formidable characters would flock towards the town on the foot of Accra Mountain. For the Buddha Empire, that place was Demon City. Demon City was very suitable for Dark Mages to live in. Therefore, the Gan Family decided to settle down here. And even if Demon City was inside the Buddha Empire, the Empire’s power was actually weak here This made it possible for the family to find their place.

However, Demon City was just unsafe to begin with. About some hundreds of years ago, a dark creatures and undead suddenly ran out of the Demonic Abyss and made a large scale attack on Demon City. The city was close to being overwhelmed, and even if the defense was successful, a lot of Dark Mages had fallen in the process. At that time, the Gan Family wasn’t spared form the losses. In the end, the family didn’t manage to stabilize their footing and slowly lost its power over time.

In the current time, the Gan Family was reduced to a few dozen Dark Mages. But even so, Adventurers and other Dark Mages still didn’t dare to underestimate them. Because of the Gan Family’s long history, their dark magic spells were quite formidable. And most importantly, the Gan Family had always treated the Demon City as their home, greeting everyone in the city as though they were family members. Every single inhabitant of the city was very respectful towards the family. If ever some kind of conflict arises, the Gan family would even be asked to mediate.

Wei Gan was only an ordinary Dark Mage in the family. He wasn’t the Patriarch nor was he the successor. He was just any ordinary Dark Mage.

The Buddha Empire had already told the city about what would happen. At the same time, the Empire had also started to gather up some troops and sent them here. They also invited the Adventurers, Dark Mages, and Dark Mage families to stay and defend the city together.

This was where the Gan Family didn’t disappoint the Buddha Empire. They were the first ones to lobby the Adventurers and Dark Mages to stay inside the City and help with the defense. In the end, the majority of the strength of the City remained.

Not only this, the Gan Family also sent their members in order to help the army guard and patrol the walls. Because of the Dark Mages’ sensitivity to the dark element, the patrol went very smoothly, saving the army a lot of effort.

One could say that Demon City’s topography was very strange. When constructing Demon City, the main goal of its infrastructure was to defend against the Demonic Abyss. As for the Demonic Abyss, since it had the word ‘abyss’ in its name, then it was no wonder that it was very deep. As to how deep? Nobody knows. Everybody who came to deeply explore the area weren’t able to return to tell the tale.

So how big was the Demonic Abyss? If one were to look, the Abyss appeared just like a giant crack in the world ten thousand li(.5km) long, with the widest opening spanning more than 2000 li. There was also a gentle slope on the ground just outside Demon City, the other places were steep cliffs where magic beasts weren’t able to crawl on. Most importantly, a dark mist covers the Demonic Abyss all year round, making people unable to clearly see anything.

It was precisely because of this that Demon City existed. If one were to speak about the continent’s oldest cities, then Demon City would surely be up there. It was even said that the city had existed for as long as the Demonic Abyss itself. But in any case, whenever war erupts in the continent, almost nobody came to touch Demon City. This was because the city didn’t have regular armies defending it. Most who were inside the city were Adventurers, Mercenaries, and Dark Mages. This made the city something that looks like it didn’t belong in this world. For many years, the same composition of people were defending the city, Therefore, people from the continent had quite a complicated view towards this place.

On this day, Wei Gan was on the wall, staring blankly at the distance. His current position right now wasn’t in the city’s eastern wall, which meant that he wasn’t facing the Demonic Abyss. It was a wall that faced the continent, so it should be quite safe. However, Wei Gan still needed to inspect the place because the Buddha Empire had sent word that people from the Demon Realm had already infiltrated the continent. This meant that they might take the city at any time.

Wei Gan looked at the surrounding army. These troops weren’t the Buddha Empire’s most elite cavalry. These people knew why they were here so they all had a very serious look on their face.

At this time, Wei Gan noticed a dark spot in the horizon. It was flying towards the city, he even thought that it was a creature of darkness.

The Gan Family’s dark magic held some differences to the continent’s dark magic, this gave the members of the Gan Family much more sensitivity towards dark energy. Therefore, when Wei Gan felt the dark energy coming out of the dark spot, and that the direction of the spot seem to be heading towards Demon City, he immediately thought of the Buddha Empire’s warning. His heart immediately started to beat as he shouted, “Everyone, a dark creature that come from the mainland is heading here. Prepare yourselves!”

Although the army that the Buddha Empire sent weren’t the most elite Iron Cavalry, these people were still elites in their local military. Before these soldiers came here, they were also instructed to cooperate with the Dark Mages since these people were very sensitive towards dark creatures. Seeing that the Buddha Empire were giving high regard to the Dark Mages in the city, the army immediately stood up when they heard Wei Gan’s voice. The magic cannons were then prepared as well as the ballistas.

Just as they got ready, the dark spot in the distance suddenly flew faster towards them. These people became nervous, especially the artillery troops. They were anxiously looking at the dark spot. Since the magic cannons and the ballistas were their only defensive weapon, the flying enemy would surely target them first.

The dark spot continued to slowly grow larger, and as soon as the people on the wall recognized what the dark spot was, all of them were shocked. It didn’t matter if they were from the Buddha Empire’s army or the Dark Mages, their expressions were the same. The dark spot turned out to be a Bone Dragon, and on the skull of the Dragon stood a very ordinary looking Dark Mage.

But who in Demon City wouldn’t be able to recognize who this person was. Perhaps they might not recognize his face, but his reputation surely rang in their minds. This was Zhao Hai Buda, Lyon Empire’s Emperor, and the continent’s strongest Dark Mage!

Zhao Hai was now widely accepted as the strongest Dark Mage in the continent, every single citizen in the various empires already knew about this point. He managed to kill Dragons, unearthed the conspiracy of the Demons, and even became the Emperor of the Lyon Empire. Every single Dark Mage almost looked at him as a God. For them, Zhao Hai was a deity that was aloof as he overlooked them.

Zhao Hai had rested well inside the Space. After seeing Laura and the others, he immediately went out. He had already taken a look at the situation in Demon City. Seeing that there weren’t any serious matters going on, Zhao Hai decided to come out in a far away place and then rode a Bone Dragon towards the fortress city, enjoying the wind that was hitting his face.

Zhao Hai didn’t immediately enter the city, when he saw the wall, he had the Bone Dragon go down to the ground outside the city and walked down from it. After storing the Bone Dragon, he walked slowly towards the city’s wall.

The defenders on the wall immediately reacted. An officer shouted towards the soldier at the gate, “Quick, open the gate, hurry up!” Then just as the officer rushed towards the gate, he noticed that someone had come faster than him, it was Wei Gan.

Wei Gan, who was just a common Dark Mage, was actually quicker than him, a 7th rank Warrior. This made the army officer look at him in a strange manner, wondering if Wei Gan was both a Mage and a Warrior.

Naturally, Wei Gan wasn’t a Warrior, he was only a Mage. The reason why he was so quick was because he was too excited. When the army arrived, he had head that Zhao Hai would also be personally coming in order to take command. This made all of the Dark Mages excited, they can actually see Zhao Hai with their own two eyes. This was a very extraordinary matter. However, people were still quite doubtful about this fact. After all, who was Zhao Hai? He was the Patriarch of the Buda Clan and was also the Emperor of the Lyon Empire. Although they knew that Zhao Hai was able to kill Dragons, would such a person still risk himself in order to come to Demon City?

For the people in Demon City, Zhao Hai was a distant person, one who wouldn’t stain his hand in a messy situation like in Demon City. Most of the people in Demon City didn’t actually expect Zhao Hai to come, they just thought that the Buddha Empire only said this in order to comfort their hearts. The main reason why these people stayed in the city was because they needed to protect their home. No matter what words the higher ups say, these people would still stay behind.

They weren’t doing this in order to protect the Human Race, nor was it because of their dedication towards the continent. For them, waging war with the Demons was just a way to protect their homeland.

Chapter 681: Influential Figure

Zhao Hai stood under the city’s gate, he didn’t want to act too high-profile, it just wasn’t his character. Although he was now the Emperor of the Lyon Empire, he knew absolutely nothing about the Empire at all. Because of this, he really didn’t think of himself as the Emperor, he was more like a stabilizer, temporarily acting as the Emperor because of the present situation.

At the same time, he also didn’t deem himself to be an influential person. In his mind he was just like any other person on the continent, doing what anybody would have done. The only reason why people were unable to do things that he can do was because they didn’t have the help of the Space.

Zhao Hai might not be aware, but he was actually an extremely influential person on the continent. From what the continent knew, Zhao Hai was a Foreign Prince of the Beastmen as well as a Foreign Elder of the Dwarves and the Elves. In fact, Zhao Hai was also given the title of Foreign Admiral by the Fishmen, but this information was withheld by the Mermaid Queen.

Thess many statuses on one person was unprecedented in the continent, something that might not even be repeated in the future. This made Zhao Hai an very influential figure in the continent. Perhaps it was only Zhao Hai who has yet to discover this point.

The gates of Demon City slowly opened. What made Zhao Hai surprised was the first person to come out, it was a Dark Mage. This person looks like 40 years old, he wore a somewhat new Dark Mage robe, he had a grassy hair and a thin beard. The person was also quite thin, he looked just like that weird uncle that everyone has. This person had a flush on his face along with shining eyes, he actually gave Zhao Hai a bit of a scare.

This person was naturally Wei Gan. He was too excited, he didn’t think that he would meet his idol while defending the city wall. His heart was extremely happy to the point that he began to lose control of his body.

Under Zhao Hai’s gaze, this strange uncle ran very fast toward him. Then the man plopped to the ground, and under Zhao Hai’s surprised expression, he kissed Zhao Hai’s shoes.

This made Zhao Hai stare, then he immediately pulled the Dark Mage up and said, “Mister, there’s no need to do that. Who are you?”

When Wei Gan discovered that Zhao Hai was asking for his name, he immediately bowed to Zhao Hai and said, “Paying respects to Mister Zhao Hai. This one is called Wei Gan, a mage of Demon City’s Gan family. I represent the Gan Family in welcoming your arrival. If it is possible, please pay us a visit.”

Wei Gan was very excited, he really wasn’t expecting Zhao Hai to be a guest in the Gan Family. In his opinion, even if Zhao Hai only promised visit, then it would already be the greatest honor to the Gan Family.

Zhao Hai looked at Wei Gan. In fact, he already knew the things that Wei Gan has been doing since Cai’er has been monitoring the entirety of Demon City. Zhao Hai was afraid that there were people controlled by the Demons here. It wouldn’t be good if there was a Demon collaborator inside the city when the battle starts. But unexpectedly, there were no Demon controlled people inside Demon City. Especially in this Gan Family, they were the ones that advocated for the defense against the Demons the most. Therefore, Zhao Hai had a very deep impression towards this family.

Zhao Hai immediately smiled and said, “So it turns out to be Mister Wei Gan. I already know about what your Gan Family had done, so I must thank you in behalf of the people of the continent. You can rest assured that I would pay a visit to the Gan Family. However, I need to pay a visit to the defending army first. I have some things to discuss with them.”

Wei Gan didn’t dare to stop him, he immediately replied, “I won’t dare to stop Mister from doing his business. But please make sure to pay a visit to the Family. We will welcome you at any time. I will now go back to inform the family.” Then he turned around and ran back to the city with a speed that even a Warrior wouldn’t be able to stop him.

Zhao Hai looked at Wei Gan’s departing back and couldn’t help but smile. He thought that this Mage from the Gan Family was quite interesting. At this time, the army officer has arrived in front of Zhao Hai. The officer then gave Zhao Hai a salute and said, “We welcome the arrival of the Lyon Emperor Zhao Hai. I am the defender assigned to the East Gate, Leonard.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Captain Leonard is too polite. There’s no Empire here, so you can just call me Zhao Hai. We’re now allies, jointly fighting against the Demon Race.”

Leonard didn’t’ expect that Zhao Hai was very easy to speak to, he immediately replied, “Alright, Mister Zhao Hai. Mister, come with me, I already sent word to the General. I’ll be taking you to the General’s residence.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he took a step towards Demon City. At this moment, a horse carriage flew from inside Demon City. This carriage was quite spirited but it still managed to keep stable. It stopped in front of Zhao Hai as its driver got down and said, “Mister, please board the carriage.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and then boarded the carriage. Then the carriage turned itself around and rushed back to the city. Leonard didn’t dare to neglect Zhao Hai’s arrival as he lead 20 other subordinates and escorted the carriage on the back to the city.

Zhao Hai wasn’t surprised about this reception, although he didn’t regard himself as a Monarch and an influential person, he was after all the Buda Clan’s Patriarch. In Demon City, this status should’ve at least gained high regard, giving him some allowance when it comes to authority.

Before long, Zhao Hai and the others had arrived at the General’s residence. The General’s residence was actually just a normal house. Since there was no military outpost here, what the General used was the residence of a former Merchant in Demon City. Because that Merchant has returned to the Buddha Empire,  his house was requisitioned and became the General’s temporary place.

As soon as the carriage arrived, Zhao Hai didn’t even need to open the door as it was opened from the outside. Zhao Hai stared blankly as he saw a middle-aged man in military uniform holding the door of the carriage open.

Then that middle aged person gave Zhao Hai a salute and said, “Buddha Empire’s General Besmir welcomes Mister Zhao Hai to Demon City.”

Zhao Hai walked out of the carriage and returned the salute, “General Besmir is too polite. There’s actually no need to open the door for me.”

Besmir smiled and said, “It is only proper for me to open the door for Mister. Mister has been running around the continent, contacting each power personally. Compared to Mister’s effort, me and the others can only bow down in shame. Mister, please come with me.” Zhao Hai quickly replied, “Alright.” Then he walked towards the General’s residence alongside Besmir.

This temporary residence was not big, just a house and a courtyard. Besmir invited Zhao Hai to sit inside the residence’s living room. At this point, the living room looked a lot more like a battle command center. There were stretches of map hangin on the wall as well as a big table at the middle of the room. This big table also had a map. This map showed Demon City as well as outside of it, the verified areas of the Demonic Abyss.

This Demonic Abyss map was naturally incomplete. But the map of the surrounding areas was already helpful for the upcoming fight.

Zhao Hai nodded at Besmir’s methods, he turned to Besmir and said, “General is very diligent. May I know the plans that the General has come up with?”

Besmir didn’t expect Zhao Hai to be straightforward, having just arrived to Demon City. However, Besmir also knew that it wasn’t time for small talk, so he immediately lead Zhao Hai to the map. Then Besmir said, “Mister, look here, this terrain is very crucial in protecting the Demonic Abyss. This is due to the gentle slope, although it isn’t that steep, it can still hinder an army’s advance. I intend to use this slope to carry out layers and layers of blockade to resist the Demon Army. What does mister think about this?”

Zhao Hai looked at the map, gently knitting his eyebrows. To be honest, there weren’t any major issues to Besmir approach. However, that plan didn’t take into account the large number of demonic creatures that would be coming out of the abyss. If a large amount of creatures come out, then this layers upon layers of blockade would eventually be overrun. At the same time, this plan would also dilute the number of personnel on each point, which was also detrimental in defending the city.

When Besmir saw Zhao Hai frown, perhaps  not contented with what he heard, his heart couldn’t help but beat faster. Zhao Hai was an existence that he cannot afford to offend. In fact, even the Buddha Emperor wouldn’t dare offend Zhao Hai. Therefore, when Besmir saw that Zhao Hai seemed to be dissatisfied with the arrangement, he immediately became afraid.

Zhao Hai was divided on whether to expose the numbers of the Demon Race or not. He was afraid that if he revealed the number of invaders to Besmir, then it might topple the General’s confidence in defending the city. However, if Zhao Hai didn’t tell the General the enemy’s numbers, how could Zhao Hai convince him to change the plan?

Zhao Hai thought about this for a while, then he opened his mouth and said, “There are no problems with the General’s arrangement. However, I think the General seems to have overlooked something. That is the quantity of the Demon Realm’s army.”

When Besmir heard Zhao Hai, he couldn’t help but stare for a moment. Then his expression turned ugly, he looked back at the map which made his expression change even more, he turned his head to Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, are you saying that there would be a large number of Demon Realm invaders?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “General, think about it, if the Demon Realm wanted to invade the continent, then would they only send a small number of soldiers? First, let’s not discuss about how big the Demon Realm is, but in Ark Continent, if one were given the power of the entire world, how big would their army be? The number of Demon Realm soldiers certainly wouldn’t be smaller than that. At the same time, the combat power of the Demons is quite strong, when I met a 9th rank Demon last time, he didn’t die even when I managed to slice his head open, he even managed to make a counter attack. This kind of combat resilience is astounding. Therefore, I think that the General should just withdraw the army and defend the city. And while the General defends the city, the external defenses will be handed over to me.”

When Besmir heard Zhao Hai, he immediately understood. Zhao Hai had a lot of strong undead, this fact was already known to the continent. He also didn’t doubt the fighting capability of Zhao Hai’s undead. Besmir just overlooked the power and numbers of the Demon Realm army, now that Zhao Hai said it, he also felt like there were problems in his plan.

Chapter 682: Unimportant Person

Besmir understood that Zhao Hai wanted him to withdraw his army, minimizing the losses to the defending troops. At the same time, Zhao Hai would use his undead army to bear the brunt of the attack, after all, they were also strong enough to do so.

Besmire wasn’t a fool, considering the manpower present in Demon City, it would be impossible for them alone to block the Demon Race. The previous time that the Demons attacked, it took the power of the entire continent to drive them back. Ninth rank experts joined in the resistance back then as well. Those 9th ranks even used forbidden sacrificial magic in order to seal up several spatial rifts. It was said that those 9th ranks were much stronger than the 9th ranks in the present time. And more importantly, a lot of forbidden magics have been lost from that day forth. If one were to compare the proficiency of magic today and in the past, then one could say that it might not have improved, and in terms of forbidden magics, then it might be even worse.

The reason why Besmir thought about all of these was because magic was something that was constantly being developed. It was just like how Earth developed from using cold weapons into using firearms, from using stone tools into using metal ones. However, that progress took thousands of years. The Ark Continent underwent the same process as well. After a long period of research, the continent’s progress was also quite amazing.

As far as people were concerned, the magic of the continent tens of thousands of years ago wasn’t as complicated as it was now. That magic back then was just powerful, especially the forbidden magics, it had the power to move mountains Although forbidden magics can still accomplish this at the present time, one shouldn’t forget the fact that only very few Mages were able to use forbidden magics.

People who had studied history discovered that tens of thousands of years ago, promoting to 9th rank was much easier than it was now. At that time, there were even news that people had been ascending to the Divine Realm. But after that, there were no information of people ascending for tens of thousands of years.

Although this point made people confused, their research yielded them with no results. In the end, the researchers just reckoned that the magic elements present in the continent right now was much thinner compared to back then. But was it really like this? Nobody knows.

However, even if forbidden magics were very rare in the present time, the continent had actually taken another road when it comes to magic. Some low to mid-level magics have become stronger compared to back then. There were also a lot of Mages right now, so if one would really compare, then the current magical level wasn’t that worse compared to before.

But while people can say that its no worse than tens of thousands of years ago, nobody would dare say that it was stronger. If it took the entire continent to repel the Demons last time, then it would also take the entire continent to repel the Demons now.

Although Besmir didn’t know about the situation of the Demon Race, he was quite smart, he knew that the spatial cracks in the past had appeared by accident. The Demons weren’t aware that those spatial cracks would appear, they were also very ignorant when it comes to the Ark Continent.

But now, it was different, the Demons had been aware of the Ark Continent for tens of thousands of years. Although they were defeated and had the spatial cracks sealed, the Demons still waited for many years in order to invade the Ark Continent.

The previous Demon invasion can be said to be done in haste, they just didn’t have time to prepare. But now that they were prepared, there was no way to solidly compare the two events. Therefore, blocking the Demons here would certainly prove impossible. Besmir’s purpose here was to delay the Demons for a couple of days, giving the continent time to gear up.

When he heard Zhao Hai’s plan, Besmir couldn’t help but nod and said, “Alright, then we’ll be doing it according to Mister’s plan. Does mister have any more ideas?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “I don’t. However I’ll be heading to the Gan Family and then going to the Demonic Abyss to take a look. I want to clear all the undead and magic beasts there before the Demons arrive otherwise they might aid the Demons in their invasion.”

Besmir stared, then he knit his eyebrows and said, “Mister, that is too dangerous. I suggest that you don’t go.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “General can rest assured, I already had managed to explore several Forbidden Areas of the Continent. I had been to the Northern Icefield as well as the Carrion Swamp. The Demonic Abyss shouldn’t be any different from those.” Then Zhao Hai turned around and walked towards outside.

When Besmir heard Zhao Hai, he couldn’t help but stare. There were few people who were aware that Zhao Hai went to the Northern Icefield, however, the fact that he had explored the Carrion Swamp wasn’t well known. Zhao Hai’s exploration of the Carrion Swamp was what made Besmir astonished.

The people of the continent had always speculated that the Buda Clan had a secret territory somewhere. Otherwise, where would the family’s good products come from? However, up until now, people weren’t able to find it. But if one adds Zhao Hai’s statement that he had explored the Carrion Swamp, seeing how well he was doing, and the fact that the Black Wasteland was still owned by the Buda Clan, Besmir immediately thought that the Buda Clan’s mysterious territory was actually their first territory in the continent, the Black Wasteland.

What was this? Is there something good out there in the Black Wasteland? It depends on which hands it falls into. Other Dark Mages can control thousands of undead, and it was known that Zhao Hai can control undead that numbered in the millions. If he can do this, then why can’t he grow something in the Black Wasteland?

Zhao Hai didn’t care about what Besmir was thinking. The reason he told Besmir about this fact was because he was already prepared to reveal the Black Wasteland to the entire continent. At this point, there was no use for him if he were to take the Black Wasteland as his secret.

After Zhao Hai left the General’s residence, a carriage driver immediately bowed towards him and said, “Mister, I am the General’s personal carriage driver. I have been given the task of taking you wherever you want.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I want to go to the Gan Family, do you know the way?”

The carriage driver immediately replied, “Of course, Mister, there’s no place in Demon City that I am unable to find. I ask Mister to please board the carriage.”

Zhao Hai nodded and went into the carriage while the driver held the door open for him. Then the carriage immediately soared towards the Gan Family. In Demon City, there were only few people who don’t know of the Gan Family. However, the family’s residence wasn’t very special. There were no special structures anywhere, it looks just like an ordinary residence with a very ordinary courtyard.

As soon as the carriage stopped in front of the Gan Family’s residence, the carriage driver immediately got down from the carriage and went to two Gan Family members who were guarding the gate. When the two Gan family members saw the carriage driver, they immediately recognized him, one of them said, “Barn, I didn’t expect that you’d come. We really can’t accommodate you, do you know who we’re expecting today? It’s mister Zhao Hai. Therefore, the family can’t really receive visitors now.”

Barn smiled at the two people and said, “I was given an order by General Besmir, starting today, I will be acting as Mister Zhao Hai’s carriage driver. Today, Mister Zhao Hai asked me to take him here to see the Gan Family.” After Barn said that, he quickly opened the door as Zhao Hai walked down from the carriage.

The two people from the Gan family were shocked, then didn’t think that Barn would actually be Zhao Hai’s carriage driver. Although Barn’s driving skills and carriage were the best in Demon City, they still didn’t expect Zhao Hai to sit in Barn’s carriage. They thought that Zhao Hai would be visiting the Gan Family on board the General’s special carriage.

Actually, this arrangement was made by Besmir. He wasn’t actually very stingy in handing his carriage over, however, he was given information by the Buddha Emperor that Zhao Hai preferred to be low-key if possible. Making a huge show wouldn’t be to Zhao Hai’s liking. Therefore, Besmir decided to have Barn take Zhao Hai around. Naturally, this arrangement was very well liked by Zhao Hai.

After seeing Zhao Hai come out, the two immediately responded, they took steps towards Zhao Hai before bowing, “We have seen Mister Zhao Hai. Mister, please come in.’ Then one of them escorted Zhao Hai in while the other ran as fast as he could to report the matter to the family. Naturally, the first one to be informed would be the Patriarch of the Gan Family.

Zhao Hai wasn’t surprised about this situation, he turned his head towards the doorman and said, “Hey, are you very familiar with Barn?” The Gan Family member didn’t think that Zhao Hai would be very polite. He couldn’t help but gape his mouth, unable to speak.

Zhao Hai looked at the person’s expression and smiled faintly, “Don’t be anxious, just answer my question, I won’t eat you.”

The Gan family member recovered, his face couldn’t help but turn red as he apologized, “I’m very sorry Mister, I have been rude. Right, I am very familiar with Barn. He grew up inside Demon City and his parents were adventurers. But one time, his parents went to the Demonic Abyss to explore, only to never come back. After then he became a beggar in Demon City before working for other people when he grew older. Afterwards, when he had the money, he bought himself a horse carriage, becoming Demon City’s best carriage driver. With him having grown up in the city, there were nobody who bullied him, making him enjoy a good life. When the news about the Demon invasion came and civilians were leaving, Barn decided to stay behind. He said that although he couldn’t fight and help in resisting the Demons, he would still offer his carriage to help the army with transportation. General Besmir felt grateful for Barn’s decision so he decided to have Barn be his residence’s attendant.”

Chapter 683: Slaves

Zhao Hai quietly listened to the words of the Gan Family member. If Zhao Hai was an influential person in the continent, then this Barn was a very small and unimportant person. In his entire life, Barn could only become a carriage driver, besides slaves, he was among the lowest ranked people in the continent.

However, Zhao Hai was actually touched by this unimportant person. He didn’t have the strength yet he still offered his efforts to defend his home. If the continent were to have a lot of people like this, then the continent would never fall. It wouldn’t be a slave to the Divine Race nor would it be eliminated by the Demons, Zhao Hai had a firm belief of this point.

When he heard the doorman’s words, turned towards the carriage and looked at the scenery. Standing nearby the carriage was Barn, peacefully standing there while looking at the surroundings. It seems like it didn’t matter to Barn whether he had seen this scenery before or not.

Zhao Hai felt like Barn was like 1900 in the move ‘The Legend of 1900’. Ever since childhood, Barn didn’t leave Demon City, the same as 1900 who didn’t leave the ship. Their lives were reflections of each other. The outside world was too big, and because of this, both of them were afraid. This made them decide to just stay in their own world. It also made Zhao Hai reflect on his life back on Earth, when he was just an ordinary nerd.

The Gan Family member was confused as he looked at Zhao Hai. He didn’t know why Zhao Hai stopped. Moreover, he was looking at Barn with a very strange gaze. However, the Gan Family member didn’t say anything, with his status, he didn’t have the merit to disturb Zhao Hai. Not only him, even if the Gan Family Patriarch were to see Zhao Hai, he would still need to respect Zhao Hai’s actions.

Then Zhao Hai turned his head towards the doorman and said, “Let’s go.” He had made a decision, he would lead Barn to the outside world. He wanted Barn to see another world other than his own, even if it meant that Barn would know about the Space.

Although it was said that the Gan Family’s residence was common, it wasn’t small. Just after Zhao Hai walked through the first courtyard, he suddenly heard some footsteps in the distance. Then as the footsteps got louder, several people appeared. These people were wearing mage’s robes, it seems like they are the core members of the Gan Family.

On their lead was 50-year old Mage. He didn’t have a very magnificent robe, and the staff on his hand seems like it was made out of beast bones. His hair was somewhat gray but it was actually very neat. If one were to see Wei Gan and see him as embarrassing, then this person exudes the presence of seriousness.

However, instead of seriousness this old Mage had a very excited look on his face. When he saw Zhao Hai, he immediately walked towards Zhao Hai and knelt, “Mister, please forgive me for being unable to personally welcome you. I ask mister to excuse my bad manners. I am the Patriarch of the Gan Clan, Tywin Gan.” The Mages behind him knelt down as well. This action gave the doorman an extreme fright. When the core members saw Zhao Hai, they didn’t just salute, they actually knelt. The doorman was afraid that he had been very disrespectful.

Zhao Hai didn’t expect these people to go overboard with their greeting. He immediately helped Tywin up as he said, “Why would Patriarch Tywin give me such an overboard greeting? This Zhao Hai won’t dare accept it.”

Tywin bowed down and said, “Mister can surely accept it. If mister can’t then nobody could. Our Gan Family is willing to be Mister’s slaves, I hope mister can agree.”

Zhao Hai stared, being a slave was completely different from being vassals. Vassals have their own autonomy, it would be fine as long as they obey their master’s orders. However, slaves didn’t have the right to autonomy. In the future, they would need to obey Zhao Hai’s every word. They would do what Zhao Hai wanted them to do.Zhao Hai couldn’t understand, why would they suddenly decide to become his slaves?

Zhao Hai didn’t agree immediately, instead, he calmly said, “Patriarch is too polite. I will not accept for now. Can we go in and discuss it first?”

Tywin immediately replied, “Of course, we have been disrespectful. Mister, please come in.” Then he led Zhao Hai towards through the courtyard and then to a lobby. Then he asked Zhao Hai to sit down while all of them stayed standing.

Zhao Hai looked at them and calmly asked, “Might I know why your Family wanted to become my Clan’s slaves?”

Tywin settled his own emotions down and seriously replied, “I’ll be totally honest to Mister, after this Demon Race matter gets finished, we won’t be able to stay inside Demon City anymore. We had stayed inside Demon City for a long time, but we still haven’t made any close friends. Even if we side with the Calci Family, we still can’t be assured of our future. Therefore, we decided to side with Mister. You are the continent’s strongest Dark Mage, so we want to rely on you for survival. And since we don’t have the abilities to be vassals, we are willing to be your slaves.”

Zhao Hai looked at Tywin, he can somewhat understand the sorrows of this small clan. Therefore, Zhao Hai nodded and said, “How many people currently belong to the Gan Family?”

Tywin immediately replied, “We have a total of 17 Dark Mages in the family. Seven 4th ranks, three 5th ranks, three 6th ranks, two 7th ranks, and two 8th ranks. There are also 32 other members along with 10 slaves.”

Zhao Hai nodded, the number was not a lot. He turned his head to Tywin and said, “You really want to be my Clan’s slaves? You can think about it more.”

Hearing that Zhao Hai seems to be willing, Tywin quickly said, “We are willing, very willing. Mister, rest assured, we already discussed this with everyone.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Alright, I agree. Starting today, you shall call me Young Master. Call all your family members as well as slaves, I shall be sending them to a safe place. The Dark Mages would have to remain, I need you somewhere else.”

Tywin immediately responded, “Yes, Young Master. We will arrange it right away.” Then he immediately told the Dark Mages behind him to arrange the things that Zhao Hai had ordered. Then Tywin stayed to listen for further instructions from Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai looked at them and said, “Most people in the continent only know that I am a Dark Mage, but they didn’t know how I became one. Since you have become my slaves, then I shall be open about you about these. After this matter, I shall tell you. In the meantime, I shall be using my Space Divergent Technique in order to send your family members to the Black Wasteland, that place is the true place of my Buda Clan. Then I shall be giving all of you potions, elevating your strengths to 9th rank. I’llbe leading you to the Demonic Abyss in order to eliminate all the magic beasts and undead there so that they cannot become part of the Demon army.”

Even if Zhao Hai hadn’t revealed too much, these small secrets were enough to make the Gan Family Dark Mages excited. Zhao Hai telling them things that ordinary people couldn’t know meant that Zhao Hai already treated them as his Clan’s slaves.

Although being a slave to another wasn’t the most glorious thing, it still depends on where one was a slave to. Slaves of an Emperor were still powerful people, and Zhao Hai himself was a monarch.

There weren’t a lot of people in the Gan Family and they didn’t have a lot of belongings. In a place like Demon City, one couldn’t really get that much belongings.

Zhao Hai arrived outside and when he saw the others he nodded, then he said to Tywin, “You arrange two people to go guide them. When they arrive at the Black Wasteland, someone will arrange their accomodation. Tell them to not be anxious and just follow instructions.”

Tywin nodded, then he immediately acted on Zhao Hai’s instructions. Before long, everything was arranged. Then Zhao Hai opened a spatial rift and took these people to the Black Wasteland.

Just when he had agreed to take the Gan Family as his slaves, Cai’er already went to inform Green and the others. There weren’t a lot of people this time, so Green shouldn’t have any problems in accommodating these people. Green had already arranged residences for tens of thousands of people, this matter should be very easy.

However, Green stil needed to take special attention to these people. After all, they had just become the Buda Clan’s slaves. Therefore, they should be given the same accommodation as the clan’s slaves. They were going to be arranged at Iron Mountain Fort.

Before long, the two Gan Family Dark Mages came back. Seeing that the two Dark Mages had arrived, Zhao Hai immediately turned to Tywin and said, “Have all of the family’s Dark Mages come here. I shall be giving you potions that would make you 9th ranks at the shortest time.”

They looked at Zhao Hai with surprised expressions, this was because Zhao Hai had told them that he would make them into 9th ranks. Although Zhao Hai had told them about this beforehand, they just thought that they had misheard him. Their strongest members were 8th ranks, and even them didn’t know when they’ll become 9th ranks. Therefore, what they got from Zhao Hai’s previous announcement was that they would just get stronger by a bit, and not become 9th ranks. But it seems like they had not misheard Zhao Hai, he really wanted to make them 9th ranks. Was this possible?”

Zhao Hai looked at their expressions and coldly snorted, “Don’t doubt me, even my undead are 9th ranks. Otherwise, where would I find the confidence to trash the Dragons?”

Tywin, who was still shocked, immediately recovered and bowed down, “Please forgive us, Young Master. We don’t dare doubt the Young Master’s words.” The other Dark Mages also bowed down to Zhao Hai, “Please forgive us, Young Master.”

Zhao Hai waved his hand and said, “Alright, don’t doubt me from now on. Your Young Master is a God-ranked expert, I just didn’t decide to ascend to the Divine Realm. I tell you this, the laws of this world can’t control me. I want to head towards the Demonic Abyss this time in order to promote my own strength. But since you had sided with me, then I shall increase your strengths. After all, I cannot manage everything in the continent, so I would have you be my representatives. And since you represent my Buda Clan, I can’t have you looking so weak lest you lose face for the clan.”

All of them were stunned, however, they couldn’t hide the excitement on their faces. They didn’t expect Zhao Hai to be a God-ranked expert. No wonder Zhao Hai dared to eliminate the Dragons. All of them were extremely happy, they didn’t think that they would actually serve a God-ranked expert. There was zero shame in becoming slaves to a God-ranked expert, in fact, it might even cause envy on a lot of people.

Chapter 684: Gan Clan and Barn

The reason why Zhao Hai dared to say these words to these people was because he has his own plans. He was not afraid that these people would reveal his secrets. He would make them into 9th ranks and then bring them to the Demonic Abyss in order to fight against the magic beasts as well as the undead. He wanted to do it in this way because he wanted to see the reactions that came with these people.

If they were sincere with him, then the advantages that they would gain wouldn’t be small. However, if they were insincere, then Zhao Hai would have no choice but to be impolite.

But Zhao Hai was just being too overly careful this time. Being a slave to the Buda Clan wasn’t a shame. In fact, having a God-ranked expert as well as an Emperor as a master was something that not a lot of people could have.

Zhao Hai withdrew a bottle of water, naturally, this water was Spatial water. This water can help the Gan Family members become 8th ranks. When they arrive at that rank, then they would consume God’s blood in order to become 9th ranks.

Zhao Hai gave the bottle over to Tywin and said, “This is a potion that can elevate your level. However, this is only effective up until you become 8th rank. When all of you become 8th rank, you come back to me.”

Tywin was shaking while he received the bottle of Spatial Water. For their family, this bottle was extremely precious. There were potions in the continent that would elevate the levels of Mages and Warriors, however, those potions were very expensive!

Even Great Nobles were reluctant to spend that money. In the minds of the Great Nobles, instead of spending a huge amount of money to buy that potion, they might as well spend that in training someone with high talent. It was because of this that potions that can upgrade levels became very rare in the continent.

After handing the potion over, Zhao Hai turned around and returned to the living room. He wanted to see how long these people would take in order to rank up.

One must know that this potion was much better than the one before. Zhao Hai believed that upgrading ranks this time would be much faster than back then with Laura and the others. At the same time, Zhao Hai also noticed that the low-ranked Dark Mages of the Gan Family weren’t in their current rank because of their lack of talent, but because of their young age instead. In fact, if one were to compare the Gan Family’s talent with the rest of the continent, then they can be deemed to be quite gifted. One must know that aside from the difficulty of reaching 9th rank, being an 8th rank was quite hard as well, there were even some small clans that didn’t have these 8th ranks. But the Gan Family, while being in Demon City, actually managed to produce two 8th ranks. This was sufficient evidence for their lineage.

There was not much control in Demon City, but in the same way, this made them isolated towards the supplies of the continent. If one were to see the Buddha Empire’s capital as a metropolis of magic, then Demon City would be that small village in the outskirts of the Empire, a small village that was regularly attacked by wild beasts.

When he saw Tywin and the others discussing about the potion and then cultivating, Zhao Hai came out of the living room, he wanted to see Barn. At this point, all of the Gan Family’s servants have left. Originally, Tywin wanted to keep some people here but Zhao Hai didn’t agree. This way, he didn’t have to worry about these people and even made it easier for him to walk around. More importantly, there wouldn’t be a lot of people who would come and give him greetings.

Barn was currently sitting outside his horse carriage, patiently waiting for Zhao Hai. Seeing Barn’s attitude, Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Barn, come here.”

Barn was sitting in his carriage while in a daze. He knew that there was only a small chance for this home of his to remain. This was the reason why he was in a daze, he has never left Demon City in his entire life. If he left this place, he wouldn’t know how to live, therefore, he chose to stay behind.

When Barn heard Zhao Hai, he immediately recovered. He looked at Zhao Hai who called him from the Gan Family’s gate. He stared for a moment before he quickly jumped down from the carriage and went towards Zhao Hai. Then he gave a bow and said, “Mister, do you need me for anything?”

Zhao Hai looked at Barn and said, “Barn, come with me, I have something to tell you.” Barn nodded, then followed Zhao Hai into the Gan Family’s residence.

After entering the Gan Family’s residence, Barn felt that it was empty. He had visited the Gan Family once or twice before, and he recognized almost all of the people in the Gan Family. However, he wasn’t able to see any of them when he entered this time. It was as if the entire Gan Family had vanished.

But Barn didn’t dare to ask as he followed Zhao Hai into the Gan Family’s living room. Then Zhao Hai sat down as Barn respectfully stood there. Zhao Hai saw Barn’s anxious face and couldn’t help but smile, “Barn, there’s no need to be nervous. I want to ask, are you willing to leave Demon City?”

Barn stared for a moment, he didn’t expect Zhao Hai to ask him about this issue. He couldn’t think of a good answer. He can just refuse and use the same reason that he gave the General, wanting to protect Demon City. However, he would be lying if he said so. At the same time, Barn had the feeling that he had been seen through by Zhao Hai. Therefore, he really can’t say that he wanted to stay in Demon City, willing to  fall along with the City’s demise.

Zhao Hai looked at Barn’s expression and smiled faintly, “Can’t think of a good reply? You don’t want to leave Demon City? After all, this is your home right? But as you can see, this place was also the home of the Gan Family, but now all of them had left save for the family’s Dark Mages. All of them had been sent away by me. Barn, if you want to leave, then I can send you to my Buda Clan’s territory, making you live a whole new life there. Also, I forgot to tell you, I am not talking about Golden Island, it is a different place. Are you willing to go?”

Barn stared, he really hadn’t thought this point through, he looked puzzled at Zhao Hai as he asked, “Why would Mister want to help me?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “No special reason, I can just see a certain person’s shadow on you. Barn, I know what you’re thinking. You have never left Demon City since you were a child, so you don’t know how you’ll live once you go outside. This made you afraid, so you decided to stay in the city. I can arrange for you to live in my Buda Clan’s territory, I can even have someone offer you a job or you can continue driving your carriage. You don’t have to worry about your life changing so much. You will be able to meet new people and also make new friends. So, do you want to go?”

Barn looked at Zhao Hai, then suddenly he made a serious question, “Mister, if I went there, can I continue to drive your carriage?”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare at this question, he didn’t think that Barn would ask this, Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “If you want to drive my carriage for me, then that’s no problem. However, you have not cultivated yet, this wouldn’t be good. After you go there, then I will make them teach you cultivation. After you have reached a high enough level, then you can drive my carriage.”

Barn knitted his brows and said, “This, Mister, I hadn’t cultivated before. And I’m not very young anymore. Wouldn’t it be too late for me to start cultivation?”

Zhao Hai actually laughed and said, “There’s never too late Barn. Rest assured, whether you learn magic or battle qi, as long as you are willing to practice, then I can make you into an expert in a short period of time. What now? You want to go?”

As soon as Barn heard Zhao Hai, his two eyes lit up as he answered, “Mister, is that true? Then I’m willing!  I want to go!”

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “Alright. Barn, to be honest, you are completely unable to provide help here even if you choose to stay behind. I shall be sending you to the Black Wasteland, people will be there to arrange you to your place. Right, do you want to go along with your carriage?”

Barn’s face expressed his excitement as he said, “You can do that mister? That’s fantastic! Thank you very much!”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Starting today, just call me Young Master. Now go and drive your carriage towards the back door.” Barn nodded and then ran outside to get his carriage. Zhao Hai told Cai’er about Barn’s situation and then had Green and the others arrange a place for Barn to live in. Before long, Barn arrived then Zhao Hai used the Space to send Barn and his carriage towards the Black Wasteland.

After completing all of these, Zhao Hai looked at the Gan Family’s situation. Majority of them had already reached 8th rank, the other two were on the cusp of breaking through. But, Tywin was very faithful to Zhao Hai’s order, he waited until all of them became 8th ranks before going to see Zhao Hai.

It was already noon when all of the family’s Mages reached 8th rank. After that, they all went to the living room. Zhao Hai looked at the group and nodded. He took out a red vial of liquid and said, “This potion shall boost you from 8th rank to 9th rank. In a while, some people would come and invite me over for a meal in the General’s residence. When I come back, all of you should have already reached 9th rank. After that, we’ll depart towards the Demonic Abyss.”

All of the Mages nodded, then at this time, a voice was suddenly heard from outside, “Is Mister Zhao Hai in? General Besmir is inviting Mister Zhao Hai over for a meal.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he turned his head to the Mages and said, “All of you work hard.” The Gan Family nodded, then Tywin went and escorted Zhao Hai to the gate.

Waiting outside the gate was a team of cavalry. When they saw Zhao Hao come out, their captain immediately gave a bow and said, “The General is inviting Mister Zhao Hai over to dine.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Alright, let’s go. Barn has become my servant and has already left. Later on, you don’t need to arrange a carriage for me, I can walk by myself.” Then with an intention, Zhao Hai summoned Alien. He sat inside Alien’s body before heading towards the General’s residence.

Seeing Zhao Hai leave, Tywin turned to the others and said, “Did you hear the Young Master? Immediately go and cultivate. If Young Master comes back and someone is still not 9th rank, then I will be giving out punishments.”

Chapter 685: Historical Novel like the Three Kingdoms?

Zhao Hai calmly stood on the Bone Dragon, behind him were the people from the Gan Family. At this moment, these people were already 9th rank. They were currently feeling like they were in a dream, they couldn’t believe that they had become 9th ranks, it was completely unbelievable.

9th rank experts were considered to be the peak powers of the continent. And all of the Dark Mages in the Gan family were now 9th ranks, this gave them extreme excitement.

However, they didn’t dare to be complacent. They understood that this was given by Zhao Hai. If they dared to betray him, then Zhao Hai would definitely clean them up.

The didn’t believe that they were the only 9th rank subordinates of Zhao Hai. If Zhao Hai can make them into 9th ranks, then he could definitely make other people 9th ranks as well. If Zhao Hai had a lot of 9th rank subordinates and then the Gan Family decides to rebel, then aren’t they just courting death?

But most importantly, when they became 9th rank, they still weren’t able to fathom Zhao Hai’s level. This made Tywin and the others believe Zhao Hai’s previous words, that Zhao Hai was a God-ranked expert. A 9th rank and a God-ranked expert were just too different. Their disparity was leagues greater than the difference between an 8th rank and a 9th rank. Therefore, the Gan Family was very loyal and devoted to Zhao Hai. They were afraid that if Zhao Hai wanted them to die, then they wouldn’t even have the time to blink before they perish.

Zhao Hai didn’t have the mood to think about these right now. He was thinking about the Radiant Church’s reaction upon hearing about the Demon Race’s arrival.

The news about the Demon Race had spread quickly throughout the continent. This was also in line with Zhao Hai’s plan. He wanted the church to give this news to the Divine Race, prompting them to make their move ahead of time.

The people from the Radiant Church weren’t aware that Zhao Hai had so many 9th ranks in his hand. So after they received the news about the Demon Race, they would surely inform the Divine Race. After all, the Divine Race wouldn’t want the Demon Race to conquer the continent first.

Compared to the native population of the Ark Continent, the Divine Race should be more afraid of the Demon Realm. This was because the strength that was displayed by the Demons was no worse than the Divine Race.

It was impossible for the Divine Race to allow the Demons to eliminate the people in the Ark Continent, then just swoop in to claim the prize. In fact, Zhao Hai reckoned that the Divine Race was not interested about the Ark Continent itself, but its people instead. If the entire population of the Ark Continent were to get extinguished, then the Divine Race wouldn’t be able to gain anything.

Most importantly, the Demon Race’s launching point was in the Demonic Abyss, a place not too far from the Radiant Empire. In this case, the Demons would surely target the Radiant Church first. And since the Radiant Church alone couldn’t stop the Demon army, they would definitely call upon the Divine Race. After all, there weren’t any other people in the continent who would come into their rescue. Instead, the continent might even find joy in this encounter, these were the two invaders, they might as well fight each other.

In the case of the Demons, their spatial rift needed the Blood Void formation in order to activate. On the other hand, there doesn’t seem to be some magic that was being done by the Divine Race. this made Zhao Hai believe that the Divine Race really had the capability to take action. Perhaps they might even appear in the continent quite soon.

This was what Zhao Hai desired. If the Divine Race failed to arrive, then the Ark Continent would then face an enemy one after the other. On the contrary, if the Divine Race were to come, the situation would now turn into a three-way battle with the locals of the Ark Continent, the Demons, and the Divine Race, like in the Tale of Three Kingdoms. Between the Divine Race and the Demons, one of them wanted to get the Ark Continent for themselves, while the other wanted to enslave the natives. Although it seems like there was an avenue for zero conflict, the Divine Race wouldn’t just allow the people of the Ark Continent to enter the Divine Realm. In the eyes of the Divine Race, the Ark Continent was inhabited by savages, people who didn’t belong to the Divine Realm. What the Divine Race wanted to do was to keep the natives in the Ark Continent, making it like a pen. The sheep were the natives and the herders were the Divine Race. When the time comes that a sheep gets fat, the Divine Race would then come over and take it for themselves.

On the other hand, the Demon Race wanted to massacre the entire native population. This was something that the Divine Race wouldn’t agree to. They don’t really care about the pen, but if the sheep were to be touched, then they certainly would fight back. This was where the two came to contradict each other.

As long as they have this contradiction, then it would be impossible for them to cooperate and in the process, making the pressure on Zhao Hai much smaller.

And the most important thing was that the place where the Demons would arrive was not far from Radiant Empire. Behind the Demonic Abyss would be the Buddha Empire, the Lyon Empire, the Rosen Empire, the Aksu Empire, and then the Beastmen. With all of these in line, the continent would have a strategic depth in their defense. On the contrary, the Radiant Empire would be left isolated, without any backers supporting them. If the Demons were thinking right, then they would definitely target the Radiant Empire first, getting themselves in conflict with the Divine Race. This was the scenario that Zhao Hai wishes to happen the most.

Because of this, Zhao Hai started paying attention towards the Radiant Empire. But unfortunately, he can’t use the Blood Ghost Staff to conduct reconnaissance on the Empire. This was due to a strange situation happening in the Radiant Empire. When the Blood Ghost Staff went there, it seems like its range of vision had become very small. And it also seems like the Empire’s 9th ranks had been tasked to patrol the area. This made Zhao Hai unable to have his Staff wander off too closely. Otherwise, if those 9th ranks find out, then he would have to find more innovative ways to scout the enemy out.

However, this wasn’t a bad thing for Zhao Hai. This performance from the Radiant Church meant that the Divine Race has started to move quickly. As long as the Divine Race takes action, then it would be good for Zhao Hai’s side.

Zhao Hai’s current strength was very strong. It can be said that compared to the war tens of thousands of years ago, Zhao Hai’s capabilities had already surpassed the other powers. But one shouldn’t forget that the Demons had managed to prepare for ten thousand years aw well. Additionally, they were also very well suited for battle, every one of them were formidable fighters. This was something that gave Zhao Hai some worries, therefore, he wanted everything to be prepared as much as possible.

To be honest, Zhao Hai didn’t believe that the Buddha Empire would be able to defend against the Demons. Because of this, a plan for evacuation was already gone underway. The Buddha Empire would be turned to be a strategic defense position. Their generals would block the Demons as much as possible.

Naturally, this was in the premise that the Divine Race didn’t come. If the Divine Race arrives, then they would get into a skirmish with the Demons. When that happens, then the lives of Zhao Hai and the others would become better.

Zhao Hai was also quite worried that the Divine Race wouldn’t act. Although the Blood Ghost Staff wasn’t able to see the situation inside the Radiant Church, Zhao Hai knew that a plan of action was already underway by the Divine Race. But as to what plan this was, Zhao Hai had no clue. This matter being out of his vision was not very good, Zhao Hai didn’t like this feeling.

At this time, the Bone Dragon had already penetrated inside the abyss. Every single magic beast and undead that Zhao Hai came across weren’t spared. Those he can kill were killed, while the undead were absorbed into the Space, turning them into Zhao Hai’s soldiers.

However, Zhao Hai also discovered that the magic beasts and undead present here were relatively low-level. One must know that Zhao Hai and his team were already quite deep into the abyss. Where were the formidable creatures? Did they go back to the Demon Realm?

The Gan Family were behind Zhao Hai during the entire ordeal, and they had witnessed how powerful Zhao Hai was. While they were descending, Zhao Hai had released a batch of undead, sweeping everything in the way. Whether they be darkness beasts or undead, all of them were eliminated in a short period of time.

The Gan Family Mafes were also Dark Mages, moreover, they were very familiar with the Demonic Abyss and had used undead summoning to subdue the undead here. However, compared to Zhao Hai’s undead, their own undead had fallen extremely short. They now understood why Zhao Hai didn’t trust their combat efficiency, they were just too weak. If they didn’t rank up, then not to say Zhao Hai, even Zhao Hai’s undead would stump them then and there.

Soon, the group went deeper into the Demonic Abyss. This was a place where no person had explored before, this made the group even more careful in their advance.

Zhao Hai stood on top of the Bone Dragon as it went forward in a moderate pace. At the same time, the undead on the ground had kept on cleaning up the Demonic Abyss, missing absolutely nothing.

Then suddenly, Zhao Hai had noticed something interesting. He made the Bone Dragon slowly go down as they stopped a few meters above the ground.

Tywin and the others followed Zhao Hai’s gaze, they wanted to see what managed to attract Zhao Hai’s attention.

Looking down, Tywin and the others couldn’t help but get absorbed by the view. Under them was a sea of flowers. Flowers of various colors were everywhere, it looked very beautiful.

The Gan Family Dark Mages were very surprised to see this flower garden. They didn’t think that the Demonic Abyss would have such a place. Was beauty something that belonged to the abyss? Compared to an Emperor’s garden, this sea of flowers was just more attractive. This fact was quite inconceivable.

At this time, Zhao Hai’s undead had also arrived by the flower garden. However, they didn’t advance, they just stared into this sea of flowers.

Chapter 686: Man Eating Flower, Flower Devil Race

The reason why Zhao Hai stopped to see these flowers was because Cai’er just recognized what these were. The flowers weren’t flowers from the Ark Continent, instead it was one that was found in the Demon Realm.

This flower was a demon plant, simply because it was from the Demon Realm. It was a flower that gave Demons a headache. In fact these flowers were controlled by a Demon itself, it was called Man-eating Flower.

Just from the name alone, on could see what kind of flower it was. The attacking power of a single flower can reach the strength of 4th to 5th rank. If it was a large one, then maybe even 8th ranks would have to turn around and leave it be.

Cai’er had been low-key during her stay inside the Demon Realm. She didn’t attack Demons, on the contrary, her leaves can even become a food source for the Demons and the demonic beasts. Therefore, her reputation in the Demon realm was quite high. After Demons die, they would even bury their bodies under Cai’er’s vines, providing her with extra nutrients.

On the other hand, this Man-eating flower was different, since their attacking strength was formidable, they didn’t need Cai’er’s methods in order to survive. On each petal on these flowers were sawtooth like teeth. As long as a person or beast comes walking in, they would act like wild beasts and snatch them using its petals, like how a predator snatches their prey. Then the flower would chew the body into dust. Because of its sawtooth teeth, they can even grind a magic beast’s bone down to nothingness.

Although the flowers don’t look too tall, their vines were in fact very long. Moreover, these flowers were said to be perennial. They can also grow up to a meter wide. Their flowers were usually curled up and when the flower attacks, the vine would suddenly shoot out as the flower went in to take a bite.

If you think that the flower only had this as a means of attack, then you are wrong. It still had other offensive ways. They also had their vines that were so tough that normal swords wouldn’t be able to cut through it. Not only were these vines thorny, they were poisonous as well. Once one gets cut through the skin, then they would immediately get paralyzed in no time. This paralyzing effect was very strong that even most 7th rank magic beasts weren’t able to resist it.

And if you were able to cut those vines off, you still shouldn’t consider them as finished. This man-eating flower was very abundant in sap, and this sap was very corrosive. This corrosive effect can melt through your flesh and bones. It was so corrosive that once you ingest it, then it wouldn’t take too long before your entire body turns into a heaping pile of mush.

This mush would then become very helpful to the man-eating flower, becoming its fertilizer. Most importantly, the reproductive ability of this flower was very strong. Although the flower vine doesn’t grow fast, as long as it doesn’t get uprooted, then a flower would eventually bloom on top of it.

For these reasons, these flowers had become a difficult existence in the Demon Realm. Only the Flower Devil Race of the Demon realm can control these flowers. Naturally, it wasn’t just the flowers that they can control, at the same time, it can also cultivate them and spread them out. From the appearance of the flowers in the Demonic Abyss, it seems like they were cultivated by a Flower Devil.

Zhao Hai looked at the sea of man-eating flowers. He now knew why many adventurers fell inside the abyss. If one couldn’t recognize these flowers, then it would be very easy to be the flowers’ prey.

Tywin looked at Zhao Hai and asked, “Young Master, are there any issues with these flowers?”

Zhao Hai turned his head to Tywin, then he smiled faintly and said, “You will know when you see it.” Then he turned his hand and took out a magic beast corpse that he got from Accra Mountain, and then he threw it towards the sea of flowers.

When the magic beast was thrown down, the flowers immediately turned into something that can only be compared to sharks that had smelt the scent of blood. All the flowers immediately snapped towards the corpse, wrapping it inside them. Before long, the flowers withdrew, leaving nothing behind. Even the bones of the magic beast weren’t spared.

Tywin and the others looked at this in shock. They didn’t expect these flowers to have so much attacking power.

Zhao Hai looked all around before moving his hand, taking a man-eating flower directly into the Space. As soon as the flower entered the Space, a prompt was heard, “Carnivorous plant detected. This flower has a spiritual imprint of another. Removing spiritual imprint.”

Zhao Hai nodded, it seems like this flower was indeed raised by someone from the Flower Devil Race. Zhao Hai looked at the sea of flowers, since all of these were cultivated here, then the Flower Devil shouldn’t be too far. Zhao Hai wanted to find it.

However, Zhao Hai was also aware that this was not easy to do. The Flower Devils belong to a very special race in the Demon Realm. Their race can be said to be Plant Sprites like Cai’er, but they weren’t fully Plant Sprites, they were also part beast, it was very unusual.

They can turn into a person, able to walk in all directions while also able to become flowers, taking the place of a bud. Moreover, their lifespans were quite long, most of them can easily live for about a thousand years. And when they die, they would form into a seed, known as a Flower Devil seed. It didn’t matter if they were people or magic beasts, as long as this seed gets mistakenly eaten, then the seed would slowly germinate inside the body of its host. And when it finally digested the host’s body, a new Flower Devil would be born.

There weren’t a lot of Flower Devils in the Demon Realm. Moreover, they also needed to be adults in order to control flowers with strong attacking capability like the man-eating flowers. Usually, they would just control ordinary flowers.

Although adult Flower Devils were strong, they were very weak in their childhood. Flower Devils can breed as well. Their breeding method was very special, two Flower Devils would meet and then they would become flowers. After that, through pollination, another Flower Devil would be born between the two of them.

Zhao Hai looked all around but he still couldn’t see even a shadow of a Flower Devil. It seems like it had turned into its flower form. Zhao Hai didn’t become polite, he wanted to snuff this Flower Devil out.

Zhao Hai absorbed a huge chunk of man-eating flowers into his Space. Then no prompt came from the Space, so Zhao Hai took another chunk into the Space.

Finally, when Zhao Hai took his fifth chunk of man-eating flower into the Space, a movement can be seen in the distance. A flower suddenly changed and slowly stood up. Zhao Hai knew that this was what he was waiting for.

Zhao Hai sized this Flower Devil that was in the process of standing up. Its stature was tall and big, it was unexpectedly four meters high. It was wearing a long robe that was composed of flower petals. It was brilliant purple and looked very fancy. The Flower Devil’s face was red, and it had a hair that looked like a fresh flower that was in full bloom. This person had its eyes closed, probably not quite sober yet.

Zhao Hai stood there, quietly observing the Flower Devil. After a while, the Flower Demon opened its eyes. The eyes weren’t divided into sclera and pupil, instead, it was pitch black, looking just like two reflective gemstones. Due to it being fully black, it actually gave out a very evil feeling.

The Flower Devil looked into the distance and into Zhao Hai and his Bone Dragon. Then it opened its mouth and said, “How dare you take by children?! Hand them over now, or else, die!” The Flower Devil’s opened mouth made Tywin and the others shocked. The Flower Devil actually had sharp jagged teeth, it looked extremely horrible.

Zhao Hai looked at the Flower Devil and asked, “Are you a Flower Devil? What is your name?”

The Flower Devil couldn’t help but stare, its black eyes seemed to shine for a moment before it asked, “Are you from the Ark Continent? How come you are aware of our Flower Devil race?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “You don’t need to know that. Now, tell me your name, or else I won’t spare you.”

The Flower Devil laughed out loud and replied, “Empty boasts. Just because you are a 9th rank expert, you think you can deal with me? You are too naive.”

Zhao Hai looked at the Flower Devil and smiled, “Of course I can deal with you. You’re quite an easy target.”

The Flower Devil looked at Zhao Hai, then it coldly said, “A Human Expert, finding out about the Demon invasion, so he decided to stop it. Then I have something to tell you. You’re already too late. The Demon army will come soon, and there’s no other way for you to stop it.”

Zhao Hai looked at the Flower Devil and smiled, “I’m not here to stop it. There’s no stopping the Blood Void formation. The Demons back then told me about it, I’m only here to clean the place up.”

As soon as the Flower Devil heard Zhao Hai, his eyes suddenly flashed, then he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “You actually knew this much? Who are you? Why would you know about the matters of the Demon Realm.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “It doesn’t matter as to who I am. You only need to know that when the Demon Race comes, I would be the first one to stand up and defend the continent.”

The Flower Devil’s eyes showed a cold expression, then he gave a long hiss, seemingly giving a command to the flowers on the ground. The flowers all stretched up like snakes getting ready to pounce.

The Flower Devil looked at Zhao Hai and said, “You meeting me today can only be blamed on your bad luck. You shall die today. Flower Armor!” Then just as his voice fell, the man-eating flowers immediately flew towards him. Before long, his body was covered with an armor completely made out of man-eating flowers.

With this, the Flower Demon’s stature had become even bigger, reaching a height of about ten meters. But what made Zhao Hai shocked the most was that this armor actually performed just like the Flower Devil’s own body. There weren’t any awkward movements that can be seen, it moved fluidly just like how a normal being moves. It seems like the man-eating flowers had become part of the Flower Demon’s body.

Chapter 687: Flame Demon

Zhao Hai didn’t think that the Flower Devil would have this trick. And at this moment, the Flower Devil started to actually fly. This made Zhao Hai surprised, Cai’er who was God-ranked still cannot make her main body float. Zhao Hai didn’t expect the Flower Devil to be able to do what Cai’er can’t.

After the Flower Devil flew, it immediately waved his hand as man-eating flowers flew directly towards Zhao Hai and the others, looking just like pouncing snakes.

Zhao Hai smiled faintly, then he waved his own hand as several Bone Dragons appeared and threw themselves towards the Flower Devil. At the same time, the Bone Dragons also blocked the flying man-eating flowers.

Now it was the time for the Flower Devil to be startled. It didn’t think that Zhao Hai would actually be able to unleash formidable undead.

Just when the Flower Devil decided to hide, it suddenly discovered that it was already surrounded by undead. These undead formed a huge ball that rotated continuously. The Flower Devil stared, he didn’t know what to do. Then a spatial rift appeared and before the Flower Devil could react, it was quickly pushed into the rift by the undead.

When the Flower Devil entered the Space, a prompt was heard, “Plant-type Demon detected, unwilling to surrender, proceeding to subdue. Plant-type Demon surrenders. Detected special ability on plant-type demon. Withdrawing ability and integrating it into the Space. Space’s Manager can now use these abilities. Space’s plants now have a higher chance of gaining sentience. Plants in the Space now have much more defensive ability.”

Zhao Hai expected this result, therefore he wasn’t to surprised. He was already aware that the Flower Demon had a lot of abilities.

However, Zhao Hai still couldn’t ignore the abilities that the Flower Demon had given to Cai’er . From what he can understand, Cai’er can now fly, which may allow her to leave the Space. This was a good thing, it meant that Zhao Hai had gained another strong helper.

Naturally, Tywin and the others were unaware of all of these. What they saw was the undead surrounding the Flower Devil in a giant ball. Then after that, the Flower Devil disappeared. Although they couldn’t understand what happened, they didn’t dare to ask.

Zhao Hai waved his hand and stored the excess undead. Then he commanded the Bone Dragon to fly forward and go through the sea of flowers. After the man eating flowers, the amount of undead and dark beasts had increased. Zhao Hai was not polite, he absorbed all of them into the Space.

Zhao Hai and the others flew down even more. However, their speed had gone slower since the visibility had also gone shorter. Zhao Hai also discovered that even his divine sense was affected, he cannot sense things that were too far.

At this point, the power of the dark beasts and the undead got stronger and stronger. Even Zhao Hai’s 9th rank undead needed to exert some effort in order to clean them up.

In order to eliminate the beasts and undead inside the abyss as soon as possible, Zhao Hai decided to speed things up. Since he couldn’t see very far, decided to release more undead. At the same time, Zhao Hai also quickened their speed of advancing.

However, the Demonic Abyss has once again proven how bottomless it was. Just as Zhao Hai was thinking that there was no end, he suddenly felt a powerful aura in the distance. Zhao Hai stared for a moment before he stopped. Then a fierce roar was heard from in front of him as a fiery red light appeared. Zhao Hai immediately erected a magical barrier. If his movement wasn’t quick, then they might have been burned by fire.

Zhao Hai looked in front of him in surprise, he wanted to know where this heat came from. At this moment, a clump of red light slowly approached the Bone Dragon. Zhao Hao stared at the human-shaped monster that was made out of fire. This monster made a loud hissing sound as fire spewed out towards Zhao Hai’s direction.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare at the creature, he can feel how destructive its flame was. Zhao Hai waved his hand to produce a ball of water. Then he threw the ball of water to quench the approaching fireball.

Zhao Hai’s water wasn’t any common water, it was actually the Space’s glacial water. The coldness of this water easily trumps frozen ice. Once an average person touches this water, then they will surely be frozen to death.

The ball of water slowly approached the fireball. It wasn’t very big, compared to the fireball, it would be like a watermelon being hit by a walnut. But unexpectedly, when Zhao Hai’s ball of water came into contact with the fireball, the fire was immediately extinguished. At the same time, the water ball seemed to be untouched as it continued its trajectory towards the monster.

The monster seemed very surprised. It immediately roared and raised its hand to release a stream of fire to collide with Zhao Hai’s water ball. This time, the ball of water couldn’t block it as it vaporized under the constant barrage hot flame.

Zhao Hai knit the brows on his head, this Flame Demon was really hard to deal with. It was also at this time that Zhao Hai heard from Cai’er that the monster was named Flame Demon. It was another peculiar lifeform in the Demon Realm. In the Demon Realm, they can become God-ranked beings, with the majority of them having strengths much stronger than 9th ranks. Although the one in the Demonic Abyss wasn’t God-ranked, it was still something that shouldn’t be underestimated.

It seems like the Demons had gone big with their move. First, it was the Flower Devil, and now it was a Flame Demon. Who knows what else was waiting for Zhao Hai.

At this rate, Zhao Hai can only use Bubble in order to deal with this Flame Demon. However, Zhao Hai didn’t want to bother Bubble right now since the little blob was still learning about how to refine items. It wouldn’t be worth it to have Bubble stop what he’s doing just to deal with this Flame Demon.

In fact, Zhao Hai can just kill this Flame Demon, but he also thought that the Flame Demon would be useful for the Space, therefore he wanted to capture it.

Just as he was thinking about this, he suddenly felt something move in the Space’s sky. Zhao Hai stared for a moment before he thought about the little thing that he gained along with the crystal jar. It was something that looked like a small sun. After arriving at the Space, the small sun went to the skies and stayed there. At this time, that same small sun transmitted the feeling of wanting to go out.

Zhao Hai gawked, he couldn’t help but think back to Bubble. If Bubble was the source of myriad water, then couldn’t this little sun be a source of myriad fire?

After thinking up to this point, Zhao Hai made an intention as the small sun appeared in front of him. Then Zhao Hai waved his hand and had the little sun charge towards the Flame Demon.

The Flame Demon suddenly sensed something dangerous coming from Zhao Hai’s direction, so it didn’t delay as it immediately turned to run away.

However, its speed wasn’t faster than the small sun. In just a short moment, the little sun already arrived by the Flame Demon and entered its body. The Flame Demon immediately stopped and roared out loud before it slowly turned silent. The Flame Demon’s body slowly shrank before it completely vanished, leaving the little sun floating there. It seems like nothing changed from the sun’s appearance. But Zhao Hai can feel that the little sun was quite happy, it was as if it had just eaten great food.

After that, Zhao Hai absorbed the small sun back into the Space the he urged the Bone Dragon to go further into the Demonic Abyss. On the other hand, Tywin and the others couldn’t help but turn stupid. They were very shocked by Zhao Hai’s attacks. Zhao Hai was using special methods in order to deal with the enemies. Although it seems like Zhao Hai’s methods weren’t eye-catching, they still couldn’t hide the strength that Zhao Hai had.

Zhao Hai didn’t care about the Gan family’s reaction. He was now more curious about the situation with the Demons. He was now convinced that there was something inside the Demonic Abyss.

However, after flying for some time, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but be disappointed. They haven’t met anything, it seems like the Demons have exhausted everything that they had.

At this moment, Zhao Hai suddenly stopped moving forward. He felt that something was wrong. He had been moving forward after he defeated the Flame Demon. But although the scenery in front of him was changing, he still felt that he wasn’t advancing at all.

Zhao Hai immediately called Cai’er over to see what was going on. What he got from Cai’er was information that he wasn’t moving all this time judging from what she saw from the monitor.

This made Zhao Hai feel confused. This was because he had always been flying, but Cai’er actually told him that he didn’t move. What was happening here?

Zhao Hai calmed his mind, he closed his eyes and then felt everything around him. With this, he found out a lot of floating things that seemed to surround him. These seemed like filaments but Zhao Hai wasn’t sure if they really existed, they feel more like energy projections than actual objects. From what he can see, it looks like these hair like things were giving Zhao Hai’s surroundings a strange feeling.

Zhao Hai quitely felt these floating energy filaments, he wanted to know what these were. Zhao Hai can feel that these things had no offensive ability, it cannot hurt him. However, these filaments were also giving Zhao Hai a dangerous vibe. This contradictory feeling surprised Zhao Hai.

Chapter 688: Best Wife Candidate: Succubus

Zhao Hai calmed his mind as he felt the energy around him. He wanted to know what these things were doing and what their use was.

However, Zhao Hai found himself unable to find anything out. Besides what he felt, there was nothing else, just the Bone Dragon and the others, hovering mid-air.

Zhao Hai continued to feel out these energy filaments. Although they don’t have any physical effects, its seems like they were doing something akin to a stick hitting water. Ripples were going outwards as the filaments waved around. The ripples were extremely faint, if Zhao Hai didn’t have his God-ranked divine sense, then he wouldn’t have sensed them.

Zhao Hai carefully examined the ripples and was quick to discover that they were special types of spiritual force. It was quite peculiar, not only was it hard to detect, their effect was manifested quite quickly. As soon as the ripples touched Zhao Hai’s mind, they would immediately get absorbed and then disappear.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but feel very strange, this mental attack was too weak, but he immediately found out that something was wrong. Then suddenly, the opposing party’s fluctuation increased. At the same time, the more the other party exerted this force, the more comfortable Zhao Hai felt.

However, Zhao Hai was not happy with this, in fact, he was quite startled at this point. He was now convinced that these ripples were up to no good and were responsible for Zhao Hai’s strange situation. And then, Zhao Hai understood that he had been trapped in an illusion.

After he had thought up to this point, the Space immediately issued a prompt, “Host is receiving an advanced level hypnosis attack. Host’s form separated from hypnotic state. Space has increased its own hypnosis ability.”

Zhao Hai’s mind went blank, then he opened his eyes. It was not long before he discovered a Demon not far away from him. She was a very attractive Demon, she wore bewitching leather clothes, one could clearly see that this leather was made out of the skin belonging to a very advanced level beast. The leather was black, it didn’t have any speck of hair on it and had a texture of a diver’s suit. The leather tightly fit her body and was very perfect for her own form. The Demon’s skin had the same color as wheat and her facial expression was exquisite. She had silvery-white hair which was quite long. At this time, she was about ten meters away from Zhao Hai and the others.

The Bone Dragon wasn’t moving at all, it was just quietly floated in the air. Then Zhao Hai turned to Tywin and the others, it seems like they were still unable to notice this female demon in front of them.

Zhao Hai turned his head back to the female demon in surprise. This woman was too powerful, to the point that she can actually place Zhao Hai in an illusion. If Zhao Hai didn’t become suspicious and was saved by the Space, then he would have suffered consequences.

At this time, Cai’er talked while inside the Space, “Young Master, that’s a Succubus. Their race has the most powerful spiritual attack in the entire Demon Realm. Young Master, it seems like you are in deep trouble now.”

Zhao Hai was confused at what Cai’er said, “Trouble? What trouble? I have broken her attack, therefore, I can just kill her whenever I want. How can that be trouble?  Is it because I’m still in an illusion?”

Cai’er gave a smile and said, “Of course not. Young Master is certainly out of the illusion. However, the Succubi are the hardest people to deal with in the Demon Realm. Moreover, their race had a very unusual rule. When an adult Succubus attacks using her mental power and her enemy manages to break free, then she would have to marry him. Of course, this isn’t the only way that Succubi get married. However, all married Succubi would have a crystal piece on their foreheads, increasing the potency of their mental attacks. Young Master, from what I can see, this adult Succubi in front of you is still undefeated, meaning that she is still unmarried. Now that the Young Master has broken free of her attack, then I’m afraid that this Succubi would have to marry you.”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare blankly, he would never expect this in a thousand years. Then he asked Cai’er, “Is that really the case? Is there nobody in the Demon Realm that can defeat this Succubus? From what I can see, her mental attack is indeed powerful, but it isn’t to a point where nobody else can defeat it.”

Cai’er smiled and said, “Of course they aren’t invincible, otherwise, the Demon realm wouldn’t have been ruled by the Demon Race. However, these Succubi are very careful. In addition to their mental attack, they still have other ways to harm their enemies. If they aren’t confident with their mental attack, then they certainly wouldn’t use it. After all, the assassination techniques of the Succubi were also very formidable. Additionally, they weren’t the kinds of people who would stir up trouble with existences that they wouldn’t dare to provoke. Because of this, marrying a Succubus by withstanding their attack wasn’t a very easy matter. A lot of Succubi married their husbands voluntarily instead of being compelled to marry their opponent. At the same time, it is also impossible to force a Succubus to marry someone. If the Succubus is forced, then she might commit suicide. But before she dies, she would curse the other party, leaving an unerasable mark on him. After that, the person would then be hounded by the other Succubi. One must also know that the Succubi held great influence in the Demon Realm, a lot of them married very powerful people in the hierarchy of power and influence. Moreover, their unreasonable passion was also quite known. Once one person get married to a Succubus, they would no doubt be held as someone worth respect. And when their husbands die, Succubi wouldn’t even hesitate to kill themselves. Because of this, everyone in the Demon Realm wanted to have a Succubus as their wife. Not only are the Succubi proficient in assassination, their mental power would also increase after being married. And most importantly, all Succubi are very beautiful. They are the most ideal wives in the Demon Realm.”

This gave Zhao Hai a headache, then he asked, “What if I just refuse to marry her after I break her mental attack?”

Cai’er shook her head, “That would not be a good idea. The temperament of the Succubus shouldn’t be underestimated. If you chose to not marry her, then she would kill herself in front of you, marking you with the unremovable curse as well.”

Zhao Hai felt his head get more painful, he didn’t think that he would meet such a hard to deal enemy. If the Succubus were to discover that he had escaped from her attack, what reaction would she have?

After thinking about this point, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but gain hope, he turned to Cai’er and said, “Cai’er, I’m not from the Demon Realm. Then wouldn’t she refrain from marrying me?”

Cai’er shook her head and said, “That is impossible, Young Master. It didn’t matter what race you are, as long as you break a Succubus’ attack, then she would marry you. It didn’t matter if you aren’t a Demon, even if you are a magic beast, she would still marry you.”

When Zhao Hai heard this, he couldn’t help but stare. He hadn’t heard of a race as terrifying as this. They were completely not in line with common sense. How could all of these be possible?

Zhao Hai was thinking of methods to make the Succubus believe that he was still under her attack. He wanted to get out of this trouble, marriage wasn’t an easy thing to decide on.

At this time, Cai’er actually chuckled and said, “Congratulations, Young Master. You just gained another wife. The Succubus just discovered that you had freed yourself from her attack.”

Upon hearing Cai’er, Zhao Hai’s mouth couldn’t help but twitch. Then he looked up at the Succubus who had also opened her eyes. She was currently looking at Zhao Hai, her wheat colored cheeks seemed to have developed a blush.

One couldn’t deny how beautiful this Succubus was, especially now where she was being timid and shy. But after thinking about their race’s peculiar rule, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but force a smile.

When the Succubus saw Zhao Hai’s expression, her face couldn’t help but get redder. She shook her head and then fixed her hair before she sternly looked at Zhao Hai and said, “From what I can hear during your conversation with the Flower Devil, you should be knowledgeable about the Demon Realm. Do you know what I am?”

Zhao Hai wanted to say that he didn’t know. But when he saw the Succubus’ expression, he couldn’t help but nod. On the other hand, Tywin and the others had just recovered. All of them couldn’t help but freeze when they saw the beautiful woman in front of them.

When the Succubus saw Zhao Hai nod, she couldn’t help but relax. Then she looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Then do you know about the rule of our Succubus race?”

Zhao Hai had no choice but to bitterly nod. He didn’t know if it was an illusion or not, but he can feel that the other party can ascertain whether he was speaking the truth or not. He was afraid that once the Succubus discovered that he lied, then she might kill herself immediately.

If it was an ordinary enemy who killed themselves, then Zhao Hai wouldn’t even bat an eye. But after Cai’er told him about the custom of the Succubus race, he couldn’t afford having this Succubus kill herself. Therefore, he had no choice but to bitterly smile at this time.

The Succubus looked at Zhao Hai and said, “So you are aware. Then from today on, I shall be your wife.”

Zhao Hai forced a smile and said, “But first you should know that I already have several wives. And I love them very much.”

The Succubus actually coldly snorted and said, “I don’t mind.”

Zhao Hai was left with nothing to say. He didn’t think that the other party would give such a nonchalant reply. At this point, Tywin and the others couldn’t make sense of what just happened. This woman in front of them seem to be an enemy, but now she has become Zhao Hai’s wife. They didn’t know if they should prevent her approach or just stay there. All of them felt that they had gone stupid from all that just happened.

Chapter 689: The Weakness of the Undead

In the end, Tywin and the others decided to refrain from moving. This was because even Zhao Hai himself didn’t make a move. They decided that it wouldn’t be good if they were to make any unnecessary actions.

Zhao Hai looked at the Succubus that stood right beside him in the Bone Dragon. Then he said, “You have to think carefully, I am the focal point of the Ark Continent alliance, the first one to go up against the Demon Realm. If you really want to marry me, then you would be enemies with your own people, every Demon, and all of the Demon realm.”

The Succubus looked at Zhao Hai and coldly snorted, “If you must kill all the Demons, then I would even help you sharpen your blade.”

Zhao Hai gave a short hmph, however, he didn’t say anything, he knew that it wasn’t the time to talk too much at this point. So he just asked, “Are there any more Demons ahead? And why are you here? Isn’t the Blood Void supposed to be indestructible?”

The Succubus looked at Zhao Hai and said, “We are here to guard the void formation. Although the Blood Void can still activate after being destroyed, it would still be much better if it operates in its full potential. There aren’t a lot of people here, aside from the Flower Devil, Flame Demon, Me, and the dark beasts and undead, there aren’t other people. However, there are ten Demons in the formation itself. If you go forward, the undead and dark beasts would go all out in stopping you. Ten of those dark beasts and undead are 9th ranks, the others are all 8th ranks. They are tasked to delay you as much as possible from destroying the void formation. However, I think you’re not here to destroy the formation. Otherwise, you would have destroyed the blood formation back then.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly as he nodded and said, “Your right, I didn’t want to destroy the Blood Void. Instead, I’d rather wait for it to finish and get more preparation time that way. After all, there aren’t very much difference between launching now and launching later. Right, I still don’t know your name.”

The Succubus looked at Zhao Hai and said, “I’m called Berry. If you destroy the Blood Void ahead of time, the power of the rift would be reduced by a tenth of the original.” Berry’s voice had become mellower compared to before, her cold disposition seems to have vanished.

But Zhao Hai didn’t pay much attention to it now. He was currently pondering about what a tenth of a difference can do. Will he have to destroy the formation now?

In the end, Zhao Hai decided to refrain from destroying it. Once he attacked the Blood Void, then it would immediately start. However, Demon City was still unprepared. Although a tenth couldn’t be underestimated, Zhao Hai deemed it to be negligible in when compared to the time for preparation.

Even if the rift were to be reduced, the sheer size of the Blood Void rift would still be quite large. A difference between a million demons and 900 thousand Demons seemed to be insignificant in the long term.

Berry looked at Zhao Hai and said, “You really don’t want to destroy the Blood Void?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “Destroying it is useless. This time, I only came to eradicate all dark beasts and undead in the abyss. I want to prevent them from being an addition to the Demon army. What can a tenth of a difference really do to us? What significant difference would there be between a million Demons and 900 thousand Demons?”

Berry’s eyes flashed while she looked at Zhao Hai, then she sighed and said, “You really don’t understand the Demons. They had been waiting for that day, for many years. For you, 1 million and 900 thousand might not have much of a difference since you are the enemy. However, for 100 thousand Demons to see the Ark Continent in advance is a very big factor for the Demons. People would fight to the death even for just a spot of being able to see the Ark Continent a day ahead.”

Zhao Hai can understand what Berry meant. If one were to tell people who lived in darkness that they can see the sunlight, then they would be extremely desperate in order to be the first one in the line. Between Zhao Hai and the Demons, the significance of a tenth was completely different.

Zhao Hai sighed, then he didn’t speak anymore. He urged the Bone Dragon to go forward. He wanted to complete his original plan of coming here, eliminating all the dark beasts as well as the undead.

Just as Berry said, Zhao Hai didn’t meet any significant resistance as he went forward. All that they had come across were more dark beasts and undead.

Zhao Hai relaxed, then he turned to Berry and said, “You have become quite close to me back then, why haven’t you used your assassination techniques and went for a mental attack instead?”

When Berry heard Zhao Hai, her face couldn’t help but turn red, “I was already near you when you were fighting with the Flame Devil. However, I knew that our assassination techniques would alarm the Bone Dragon before I arrive. Therefore, I decided to trap you here using my mental attack until the Blood Void activates.”

Zhao Hai nodded, he knew that since Berry was aware of his conversation with the Flower Devil, then she should’ve been present when he fought the Flame Demon. However, the two fights had shown Berry how strong he was. Therefore, Berry had no choice but use their mental attack. However, she didn’t expect that she would lose.

Zhao Hai stopped asking about this matter. He turned his gaze towards the distance and said, “They should be coming about now.” Zhao Hai was referring to those ten 9th ranks.

As expected, just as Zhao Hai said that, ten black spots appeared in the distance. The black spots slowly grew as it approached Zhao Hai. Among them were eight dark beasts and two undead creatures who were emitting a strong aura.

The dark beasts are just special magic beasts, so they didn’t get too much out of Zhao Hai’s attention. On the other hand, the undead made Zhao Hai intrigued. He didn’t expect that the undead would be able to reach 9th rank naturally. This was the first time that he saw a true 9th rank undead.

The two undead had human forms. Their bodies were equipped with worn out battle armor. They were also holding damaged great swords. Their image conforms to what Zhao Hai expected 9th rank undead would be.

However, these two undead creatures gave Zhao Hai a peculiar feeling. Zhao Hai felt that he was facing actual people instead of undead. Compared to what he felt with the Space’s 9th rank undead, these two undead had a more formidable aura.

Zhao Hai curiously looked at the two 9th rank undead and said, “Are you naturally evolved undead? Why would you listen to the words of the Demons?”

“Demon consciousness. Unsurpassed honor! Kill!” Zhao Hai thought that the opposite party wouldn’t reply. He really didn’t expect that they would say anything, even in broken sentences.

Zhao Hai waved his hand as he commanded the undead on the ground to fly up. Then he had this group of undead form a small cube formation in front of Zhao Hai. After that, he commanded them to fight the 10 9th ranks.

Zhao Hai didn’t care much about these undead, he wanted to see how these 9th rank dark beasts and undead from the Demon Realm fight. From Zhao Hai’s calculation, aside from the 9th ranks, there should be about 1 million undead as well as about 2 million dark beasts.

However, he didn’t kill the 8th rank dark beasts this time, all of them were absorbed into the Space. Additionally, the 8th rank undead were also taken into the Space, changing them into Zhao Hai’s own undead army.

Before long, the 10 9th ranks had managed to eliminate about a hundred of Zhao Hai’s own 9th rank undead. But instead of being angry, Zhao Hai was actually glad. He discovered that these naturally formed 9th rank undead seemed to be much more powerful compared to the 9th ranks that were produced by the Space.

This made Zhao Hai puzzled at first, but he quickly thought of the reason. One was artificially promoted by the Space while the other was made after innumerable years of existence. In these years, the undead should have encountered a lot of battles, making its fighting experience constantly improve. It seems like battle experience was more important to these undead than what Zhao Hai originally thought.

Although the undead of the Space were similarly 9th rank, they were still far behind those who were forged through constant battle. Because of this lack of experience, the Space’s undead were unable to utilize all of their strength. It was like having powerlifter fight, he might be strong, but it was extremely possible that he would lose against a similarly strong but experienced fighter.

However, there was no way for Zhao Hai to have an immediate solution to this problem. The undead in the Space were truly lacking in genuine battle experience. Moreover, before becoming 9th ranks, most of them had strengths that were incomparably low. This caused a disparity in their thoughts and actual strength. The only solution that Zhao Hai thought of was to forge them through constant battle during the war. Only when they can accumulate experience would they be able to perfectly control their strength.[1]

Now that the Demons were on their way and the Divine Race not far behind, huge battles would surely happen in the future. Zhao Hai would use this opportunity to have his undead acquire ample experience. That way, Zhao Hai can then command an invincible army. Whether it be the Demons or the Divine Race, Zhao Hai would not be afraid anymore. He would even march into the Demon Realm and the Divine Realm in order to eliminate future problems!

* * *

Or you can just let them fight each other inside the Space. cmonbruh

Chapter 690: Miscalculation of Time

It didn’t take too long before the fight finished. Although Zhao Hai’s undead suffered when faced with the same 9th rank power, they were completely dominating those who are less ranked. After all, 8th rank and 9th rank were totally different from each other.

After all the dark beasts and undead have been cleaned up, Zhao Hai continued to fly ahead. And before long, they arrived at a valley inside the Demonic Abyss.

At the valley, the first thing that Zhao Hai noticed was the spatial rift. Coming out from the rift were clumps of black gases. Fortunately, this rift wasn’t big, it was only less than a meter long and a half meter wide. Aside from small people, no bigger creatures can emerge at this time.

With the spatial rift as the center, a huge magic formation was erected, shooting out white radiance now and then. This was the void formation of the Blood Void.

Zhao Hai inspected the spatial crack, he wanted to see how different this rift was compared to the Space’s own. After looking at it for some time, Zhao Hai couldn’t see much of a difference. It was the same floating hole, like a hole in a transparent canvas.

Behind this rift was nothingness, one couldn’t see anything at all. Even light seems to get swallowed by it.

Upon looking further, Zhao Hai noticed that the rift was surrounded by ten Vile Demons.[1]

Zhao Hai was no stranger to Vile Demons, he looked at the ten of them and smiled, “Vile Demons enemies, you can rest assured that I am not here to destroy your formation. However, when you Demons arrive, be sure that I shall be there waiting.”

Zhao Hai’s attitude shocked the Vile Demons. They were puzzled at Zhao Hai, they couldn’t understand what Zhao Hai meant.

Zhao Hai looked at them and smiled, “There’s no need to be anxious. Usually, I call people with a different race than me, friends or brothers. However, you Demons wanted to invade my Ark Continent, so I had no choice but to call you enemies. But I am indeed sincere in not attacking the Blood Void. I know that there’s no way to stop the Blood Void, and I also don’t want it to activate ahead of time. Therefore, I shall be leaving you here and I will just wait for you in the surface.”

The Vile Demons stared blankly at Zhao Hai, then after some time, one of them said, “No matter who you are, you are worthy of our respect. We will defeat you in the battlefield, we’ll make you aware of how strong the Demon Realm is.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly, he already knew that although these Demons were battle freaks, they were also people who respected brave warriors. To be clear, they respect brave warriors, not strong experts.

Brave Warriors and Experts have their distinction. A brave warrior isn’t necessarily a strong expert. When faced with an enemy much stronger than yourself but still are willing to fight, then you are a brave warrior. These kinds of people were very well respected by the Demons. For this respect, the Demons would defeat you in an upright manner, there would be no tricks involved.

Berry was also quite surprised at Zhao Hai. She discovered that Zhao Hai actually understood the Demon Realm fully. This made her confused, she didn’t understand how a Human was able to know about the Demon Realm. This was too inconceivable. The Humans haven’t even entered the Demon Realm.

At this time, the head Demon turned to Berry and said, “Berry, why are you together with him? Do you want to betray the Demon Realm?”

Berry looked at the Vile Demon and said, “I didn’t betray the Demon Realm. I am just following the customs of my Succubus Clan. This person managed to break free from my mental attack. Therefore, according to the rule, I shall have to marry this person.”

When the Vile Demon heard Berry, he couldn’t help but gawk. Of course, the Vile Demon was aware about which rule Berry was talking about. He just didn’t think that Zhao Hai would survive Berry’s attack.

One must know that the Succubi held the most powerful mental attacks in the Demon Realm. Additionally, Berry is a 9th rank Succubus, her mental power was very well known in the Demon Realm. The Vile Demon didn’t think that she would actually lose to a Human.

The ten Demons looked at Zhao Hai with envy, then their leader said, “Congratulations, brave Human warrior. You actually managed to get yourself a Succubus as a wife. Human, we shall not attack you as well. Our fight might possibly destroy the Blood Void. You can leave now. Our Demon Army shall fairly defeat you in Demon City.”

Zhao Hai looked at the ten Demons, he couldn’t help but develop a slight appreciation towards them. However, it was a pity that they are his enemies. Zhao Hai was surprised when the Vile Demon said that the Blood Void might get destroyed if they decided to fight. It seemed like nobody wanted to activate the spatial rift ahead of time.

Zhao Hai looked at the eyes of the Vile Demons, then he nodded and said, “Alright, then I shall be waiting for you in Demon City. Farewell.” Then Zhao Hai commanded the Bone Dragon to fly out of the Demonic Abyss. The ten Vile Demons stayed true to their promise, they didn’t attack Zhao Hai.

Compared to when he entered, Zhao Hai’s speed of advancement was quite faster. Zhao Hai had calculated that after entering the Demonic Abyss and undergoing battles inside, two days had already passed by. Zhao Hai reckoned that it would only take them half a day to come out.

With this rate, Zhao Hai had already used up four days. In three days, the spatial rift would open and the Demon Race would arrive.

Zhao Hai stood straight on top of the Bone Dragon as he muttered, “Three days, three days.”

Berry looked puzzled at Zhao Hai as she said, “Three days? Are you expecting the Blood Void to activate in three days? That’s not right, from what I can remember, there is only one day left before the Blood Void activates.”

Zhao Hai stared, he quickly turned his head to Berry as words came flooding out of his mouth, “One day? How could it be one day? Doesn’t the Blood Void activate after seven days?”

Berry nodded, “Right, it takes seven days. The countdown starts the moment the blood formation gets moistened by blood. From what I can remember, five days have already passed since then. After a bit more than a day, the Blood Void would activate.”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but from upon hearing Berry. He kept thinking about why Berry would say that only a day was left. Did he go wrong somewhere?

Suddenly, Zhao Hai thought about where he slipped. He had missed the timing of the blood formation. He miscalculated how long the formation had been running before he arrived at Accra Mountain. The formation started the moment Zhao Hai began killing the beasts in the mountain, not when he discovered the formation.

If Zhao Hai took that thought into account, then the Blood Void really only had one day left to activate. In a day’s time, the Demons would be coming out of the spatial rift.

Zhao Hai regretfully tapped his own head. He didn’t think that he would miscalculate this matter. This shouldn’t be happening, it was his fault. He immediately had the Bone Dragon pick up its speed to return to Demon City as soon as possible. Upon reaching the city, Zhao Hai was met with the gazes of the Adventurers and Mercenaries. All of them looked at Tywin and the others in envy, they didn’t think that the Gan Family would be able to establish a relationship with Zhao Hai in a short period of time.

Zhao Hai wasn’t in the mood to act low-key right now as he flew directly towards the General’s residence. Upon reaching the front door, Zhao Hai didn’t hesitate to enter the room.

The guard in front of the General’s residence naturally didn’t dare to block Zhao Hai. Nobody dared to stop him. After all, Zhao Hai had the highest status here in Demon City. The whole city depended on Zhao Hai to defend against the Demons.

Zhao Hai proceeded to head towards Besmir’s room. At this moment, Besmir was looking at the map. When he heard footsteps and looked up, he didn’t imagine to see Zhao Hai. So he quickly straightened himself up and sid, “Mister, how did your expedition go? The layout of Demon City had already been set up. We’re just waiting for Mister’s undead to settle in.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright, as long as the General has adjusted, then I can feel relief. However, I had made a miscalculation this time. The Demons will be arriving much earlier than we thought. I’m afraid our current layout wouldn’t be good.But since you have already settled in, you can stay put. There’s no need to send word back to the mainland, I shall be taking care of it.”

Besmir stared, then his expression changed as he immediately asked, “Really? Mister, what happened?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “Now’s not the time to explain. I shall be handing the city over to you. The outside matters would be taken care of  by me. I’ll be sending word to the major Empires and Races of the continent. As long as you prepare yourselves, then you are good.”

Besmir nodded, he understood that it really wasn’t the time to be asking. He said, “Alright, then mister can rest assured, the city has already prepared. All the logistics and commands have already been given.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Then that’s good. I’ll be leaving first, I still need to inform the mainland.” Then Zhao Hai hastily left the General’s residence and returned to his own.

After arriving inside the Gan Family’s residence, Zhao Hai released a group of undead and turned to Tywin and said, “These are the undead that we have acquired in the Demonic Abyss. I also took the effort of strengthening them. You can take them under your command. Right, how many undead can you currently control?”

Zhao Hai didn’t know how much undead a regular 9th rank can control. Therefore, he had no choice but to ask. Tywin gave Zhao Hai a bow and said, “Answering the Young Master. Although we had become 9th ranks, we still aren’t accustomed to our new strength. So at this moment, each of us can only control about ten thousand undead. When we get fully adapted, then we can control 20 thousand undead each.”

* * *

It used to be ‘Evil Demon’ but I just made it as Demon, like the one back on Accra Mountain. But I decided to use Vile Demon just in case something crops up later. Lorewise, Vile Demons are the rulers of the Demon Realm.

Chapter 691: Preparation

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Even if that’s not a lot, it isn’t little either. Alright, then we’ll head outside the city and have you control these undead. After everyone subdues enough undead, I shall be heading to do other matters.”

Naturally, Tywin and the others didn’t oppose to this. After all, this was very good for them. They never thought that Zhao Hai would harm them anyway. At this point, they have become true followers of Zhao Hai. If Zhao Hai wanted to harm them, then he wouldn’t have made them 9th ranks. Zhao Hai had their complete trust.

Zhao Hai quickly led the group outside Demon City. Then he released large quantities of undead. Among these undead were the ones they obtained from the Demonic Abyss, there were both human-shaped and beast-shaped undead, but this didn’t matter for Dark Mages. Naturally, although the undead have been subdued, Zhao Hai can still override the commands of the Gan Family Dark Mages. As far as Zhao Hai knew, he was just commanding the undead to follow the Gan Family’s orders.

Since Zhao Hai ordered them, the transition of control for the undead came very smoothly. Otherwise, Tywin and the others wouldn’t have done it. After all, the undead were 9th ranks as well.

It didn’t take long before the undead were controlled. Zhao Hai looked at Tywin and said, “You are already quite familiar with the surroundings here. So I’ll leave the deployment of the undead to you. We should be done preparing before the Demons arrive tomorrow. I’ll be returning to the city in order to handle other matters.”

Tywin immediately replied, “Young Master, let me go back with you. I am very familiar with Demon City. I can assist you with the minute things, saving you the trouble of doing them.”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “You stay here. I’m just going back to your residence to take a rest, I’ll come back here later. You don’t need to worry about me.”

Tywin didn’t say anything more, he just nodded. After that, Zhao Hai returned to the city and then entered the Gan Family’s residence. Berry was still right by him.

When Zhao Hai entered the Gan Family’s residence, he turned to Berry and said, “Berry, if you are really determined to be with me, then I will lead to see my wives now. I shall not be impartial in treating you. I just hope that you can live together with them harmoniously. Can you do that?”

Berry looked at Zhao Hai and said, “You are the man that I chose. Naturally, I will listen to your words.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright, then I shall show you my biggest secret.” Then along with Berry, Zhao Hai’s body flashed as he entered the Space.

Berry couldn’t help but stare blankly at the scenery in the Space. Although the Demons had always thought about how beautiful the Ark Continent was, Berry still lived in the Demon Realm for all of her life. She had also seen Demon City, however, since the place was made in order to survey the Demonic Abyss, there wasn’t much to see. On the other hand, the scenery inside the Space was very beautiful, even in the Ark Continent’s standards. For someone who lived in the Demon Realm since birth, it wasn’t a wonder for Berry to be enthralled by the Space’s scenery.

At this time, the door of the villa opened as Laura and the others walked out. The women had already learned about the Succubus clan from Cai’er. To be honest, they were somewhat jealous. However, they weren’t stingy, they didn’t wish misfortune on this new arrival. Because of this, they had decided to treat Berry well.

Actually, Laura and the others’ reaction was something that Zhao Hai used to be surprised at. Zhao Hai had read a lot of novels back on Earth. And in all of those novels, women were always jealous whenever a new female arrives. However, it seems like Laura and the others didn’t seem to look jealous. This made Zhao Hai unable to understand what they were thinking.

Later on, Zhao Hai asked Laura why they weren’t jealous. But he was just met with strange looks from Laura and the others. Then Zhao Hai got his answer; in the continent, even a man with little skill would have more than one wife. In fact, if they were to think about it, with Zhao Hai’s status, his number of wives was actually very small.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile bitterly upon hearing this response. He had been stuck with his Earth mentality and was still unable to adapt to the Ark Continent. On Earth, everyone was unanimously leaning towards monogamy. On the other hand, in Ark Continent, it was simply normal for a man to have several wives.

Because of this, Zhao Hai wasn’t surprised when he saw his wives’ current response. He nodded to Laura and the others and then turned to Berry, “Berry, these are my wives, Laura, Megan, Meg, Lizzy, and Ni’er. You must go along with them later on. You’ll be living with them from now on too. They will also introduce to you everything that is here.”

Berry nodded, although she still had her cold expression, Zhao Hai can see that she had a look of dependence in her eyes.

Zhao Hai understood that this was a natural reaction from Berry. She has been living alone in the Demon Realm all her life. In this new environment, she couldn’t help but do her best to adapt. And now that she had Zhao Hai as her husband, it wasn’t strange for her to depend on him.

Zhao Hai smiled and Berry and said, “There’s no need to be worried here. This is my Space, as long as I don’t give my permission, nobody would be able to come here. Rest assured, there will be no problems here.”

Berry nodded, then Laura went towards her and said, “Berry, don’t worry, Brother Hai is a good person. Later on, we’ll be sisters living together. Come with me, I shall tell you everything there is in this mysterious Space.” Then she pulled Berry over towards the Villa.

Berry didn’t react too much as she followed Laura towards the villa. However, when they reached the entrance, Berry couldn’t help but stop. She looked at the villa and couldn’t help but change her expression, she turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, what’s this all about?”[1]

Zhao Hai stared, then he said, “What? Is there something wrong?”

Berry pointed towards the seven-colored flower that covered the entirety of the villa, her finger trembling while doing so. When Zhao Hai saw her pointing towards the seven-colored flower, he understood what she meant. Zhao Hai couldn’t help but chuckle as he said, “Oh, you mean Cai’er? You should be familiar with this plant, right?”

Berry nodded and said, “I’m quite familiar with it, however, why is the Holy Flower growing here? This flower only grows in the Demon Realm, how can it appear in this place?”

Zhao Hai faintly smiled and said, “Cai’er, come out and see Berry. Introduce yourself” Then Zhao Hai felt wings lightly flapping right by his face as Cai’er appeared. “Young Master, you always make me do a lot of things. I’m quite busy, you know? Unlike you who are living a relaxed life every day.”

Zhao Hai smiled and then turned to Berry and said, “Berry, this is Cai’er, the flower sprite of the seven-colored flower. She is also the main body of the seven-colored flower that you have been seeing in the Demon Realm.”

Berry stared at Cai’er as Cai’er looked back. Then Cai’er smiled and said, “What? Shocked, little Succubus? In your Demon Realm, you should have spotted my flowers everywhere. Hehe. Small Succubus, your kind had always underestimated my existence. I’ll let you know that I am the longest living being in the Demon Realm, and also the most influential. All of the seven-colored flower that you had seen are all my branches.”[2]

Berry was blankly staring as she listened to Cai’er’s words. After some time, she recovered and turned to Zhao Haim, “Brother Hai, is this true?”

Zhao Hai nodded and then smiled, “It’s true. The reason I know about the Demon Realm was because of Cai’er. Alright, you’ll find out about more things as you explore the Space later on. Let’s enter the living room for now, we still have some things to discuss.” Then the group entered the villa.

Upon entering the villa, Zhao Hai immediately cycled through his messenger fishes as he gave the various Patriarchs and Monarchs of the continent a message, informing them that the war would come earlier than they expected. At the same time, Zhao Hai also gave the Buddha Emperor instructions to prepare his citizens to migrate. Also, Zhao Hai ordered Evan and Ruyen to reinforce the border between the Buddha and Lyon Empire while allowing passage for the Buddha Empire refugees as well as to take care of them properly.

Of course, this wasn’t an easy thing for an Empire to do. But fortunately, Zhao Hai already made ample preparations. At this time, the Buddha Empire’s migration towards the Lyon Empire was already well organized.

One shouldn’t underestimate this mass migration. There were a lot of matters involved in such a movement. Especially in terms of food and lodging for the refugees.

Fortunately, Zhao Hai has the Space, supplying all of the much needed grain. As for lodging, the Lyon Empire doesn’t lack it. This made the job twice as efficient with half of the effort.

Although the Buddha Emperor wasn’t willing to evacuate his entire Empire, he also understood that the Demons couldn’t be easily dealt with. If he insisted for his people to stay, then the Demons would only kill them. Therefore, he had no choice by to agree to Zhao Hai’s plan.

At the same time, the Dwarves and the Elves had prepared themselves. Zhao Hai shifted all of the valuable Dwarf materials over to the Black Wasteland. However, the Dwarves weren’t planning to fully evacuate out of their mountain. They wanted to use the mountain to ambush the Demons. Naturally, those who stayed in the mountain were the Dwarven Warriors. The women and children were already sent to the Black Wasteland. There was no other way, after all, the Dwarves were inside the Buddha Empire, which was quite close to the Demonic Abyss.

The Elves did the same, those who had no fighting power were all sent to the Black Wasteland while the Elven Warriors stayed. They were prepared to use the forest in order to combat the Demon Race.

Zhao Hai was quite assured when it came to these two races. Their fighting powers weren’t weak, and additionally, they had terrain advantage, giving them huge benefits during the war. Zhao Hai wasn’t worried about them.

On the other hand, there were currently a lot of people in the Black Wasteland. It would take a long time for these people to be settled down. Fortunately, Zhao Hai has the Space. He can just easily transport Beastmen tents for them to live in, allowing the construction of houses to slowly proceed.

* * *

Its supposed to be “Elder Brother Hai”. However, I have this inclination that Berry is much much older than Zhao Hai. xD”

First time I knew this :/ As for the ‘influential’ part, I think it’s about how seven-colored flowers are the staple food in the Demon realm.

Chapter 692: Demon Dragon King

Zhao Hai was currently standing outside Demon City. Behind him was the city’s walls and in front of him was an army of undead. The undead looked like statues as they stood, unmoving.

Zhao Hai was currently on the back of the Bone Dragon along with Tywin. The undead on the field were all controlled by the Gan Family. Zhao Hai’s undead were yet to be released.

It has been a day since Zhao Hai communicated with the various Patriarchs and Monarchs of the continent. In the past day, Zhao Hai has been inside the Space, continuously talking to his messenger fishes, coordinating with the everyone and deploying various materials.

It was fortunate that Zhao Hai was able to make the Monarchs and Patriarchs listen to his instructions. These people also understood that if they didn’t follow through, then they would get eliminated by the Demons sooner or later. Therefore, they decided to fully cooperate in this huge operation.

Also, this alliance needed a leader. And since Zhao Hai held special status in all of these groups, he became the de facto leader. Because of his Space, Zhao Hai was able to move massive resources around, giving him the power to dictate when and where people needed to be. This made everyone consult Zhao Hai whenever an important decision needs to be made. At the same time, this also fulfilled the Dwarves’ prophecy, King of Kings.

Zhao Hai didn’t care much about these. To be honest, with regards to resources,  he really didn’t have too much of a problem about it. At this point, he had a lot of things in his hand. Adding that to the reserves of the Empires, then Zhao Hai found himself unable to fathom the exact number. On the other hand, Laura and Cai’er were already crunching the numbers as well as allocating everything in behalf of Zhao Hai. At the same time, Megan and Lizzy were conserving their strengths for the upcoming fight with the Demon Race.

On the contrary, Berry was not busy at all. She is currently working with Lizzy on how to command in battle while also familiarizing herself with the situation inside the Space.

The more Berry understood about Zhao Hai’s space, the more she found it to be mysterious. She already has a few ideas in her mind, however, she didn’t tell it to Zhao Hai at this time.

Zhao Hai was currently waiting in Demon City for the Blood Void’s activation. From what he heard while talking to Berry, the void formation would should be starting quite soon. At this moment, Zhao Hai wanted to see what it looks like when the formation starts.

Tywin and the others were also by Zhao Hai’s side. Their expression of anxiety couldn’t be hidden as they gazed towards the Demonic Abyss. They knew that the fight would start soon, they couldn’t help but feel anxious.

Zhao Hai turned his head towards the city walls and looked at the soldiers, they were anxious as well. Zhao Hai couldn’t help but sigh, although the war with the Demons happened tens of thousands of years ago, legends about the Demons were still prevalent in Human societies. It was told that Demons were overbearing, lusted for blood, and powerful. All of these descriptions had slowly crept up on these soldier’s minds, making them very nervous.

However, Zhao Hai couldn’t do anything much but wait. Zhao Hai sighed before sitting on the Bone Dragon’s head. Then he took out a small table, a bottle of wine, and a wine glass as he continued on with his thoughts.

When the soldiers on the walls saw Zhao Hai’s action, they couldn’t help but stare. Then their expression loosened. In their minds, Zhao Hai had already become the main pillar of support. Zhao Hai’s calmness had affected them as well, making the pressure in their minds slowly ease up.

At this moment, a very fierce vibration suddenly came from the Demonic Abyss. This vibration shook the terrain, making Demon City’s structures sway.

Zhao Hai seems to have not noticed this as he drank the wine in his glass and muttered, “You’ve finally come. I had been waiting for half of the day.”

Just as Zhao Hai said this, a more violent shaking happened, it was as strong as an earthquake. Then black fog started to come out of the abyss as it slowly covered the skies above it.

Zhao Hai looked at the black clouds as he smiled faintly and said, “Magnificent, good, very good.” Then a fierce rumbling came out as a shockwave came out of the abyss, eradicating everything around it, may it be stone, soil, or plants, turning all of them into powder instantly.

With an intention, Zhao Hai released countless amounts of undead. When the undead appeared, they immediately formed a large green shield in their bodies, protecting themselves as well as those behind them from the shockwave. Demon City as well as the base of operations outside became unaffected by the destructive wave.

And just as Zhao Hai drank from his wine glass, mushroom clouds suddenly came out of the Demonic Abyss!

Zhao Hai can only imagine one thing upon seeing these mushroom clouds, it was an image of a nuclear explosion. He didn’t think that the Blood Void would cause explosions strong enough to cause mushroom clouds to appear.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but mutter, “Is this an illusion? It must be, aren’t the Demons afraid of blowing themselves up?”

Although Tywin and the others were right by Zhao Hai’s side, they still didn’t hear what Zhao Hai just said. They were too enthralled by the mushroom clouds in front of them.

At this time, the Demonic Abyss suddenly changed. A small whirlpool started to appear in the middle of the mushroom clouds. Then this whirlpool continued to grow bigger and bigger as it started to revolve, absorbing all of the dark clouds before all of it vanished.

When the dark fog completely disappeared, Zhao Hai couldn’t’ help but breathe in some cold air. A massive change just happened in the Demonic Abyss. The abyss had become wider and more spacious. At the bottom of the abyss was a huge crack that was suspended half a meter above the ground. At the same time, groups upon groups of Demons slowly appeared from it, rows upon rows of Demonic beings from the Demon Realm.

After the changes in the Demonic Abyss, it has now become a wide flatland. The surrounding cliffs had completely vanished. With how large the flatland was, it was more proper to call it a plain.

It was an incomparably huge plain, and in the middle of it was a huge spatial rift. At the scale of this plain, an army of tens of millions would fit to be stationed here.

Zhao Hai didn’t expect that the effects of the Blood Void would be this significant. One must know that Zhao Hai took two days to fly towards the rift, all of that distance has been affected by the Blood Void. This showed how powerful the formation was.

However, the thing that surprised Zhao Hai the most was the fact that the Demons didn’t immediately attack upon coming out of the spatial rift. Instead, they started to build their base of operations on the flatland right beside the rift.

From the looks of it, it seems like they aren’t just building a camp. They were constructing a city. After seeing this development, Zhao Hai’s expression couldn’t help but turn gloomy.

If the Demons just attacked them after coming out, then Zhao Hai didn’t have anything to worry about. But now that they are constructing a city, this meant that they wanted to establish a base, intending to fight with the Humans for a long time. This wasn’t what Zhao Hai wanted to see.

Zhao Hai smiled faintly as he collected his drinking set, then he turned to Tywin and said, “You wait here.” When Tywin heard this, they immediately jumped down from the Bone Dragon and stayed in mid-air. Then Zhao Hai waved his hand as an innumerable amount of undead appeared. Zhao Hai gave a command, then the undead started to form into a cube before rushing towards the Demon invaders.

When the people on the walls saw what Zhao Hai did, they couldn’t help but gasp. At the same time, the Demons also saw Zhao Hai’s action. They immediately split into teams as some of them flew up to meet Zhao Hai’s approaching undead army.

As the two forces came closer and closer, Zhao Hai discovered that the other party was composed of flying beasts as well as winged Demons. All of them had grotesque looks, but one could see that they had extraordinary strength.

The two forces stopped when they were about a hundred meters away from each other. Zhao Hai directed the Bone Dragon as he slowly got out of the cube formation. At the same time, a small group also went forward from the other party.

This group was composed of Vile Demons. All of them were protecting a carriage that was in the middle of their formation. What pulled this carriage wasn’t actually a horse, but Dragons instead.

These Dragons were similar to those back in Accra Mountain. However, their bodies were pitch black as their scales flashed with the same metallic luster. They also have eyes that were red, leaving those who looked at it with a very bad feeling.

The two teams stopped when they were ten meters away from each other. Zhao Hai inspected the carriage, the carriage was actually just the lower half of the structure. There was a throne with beast engravings right on top of the carriage. Sitting right on the throne was a Vile Demon.

Although there wasn’t much difference to how this Vile Demon looked, one could still feel that he was more majestic than the others, just like how a alpha male lion looks like when it was just lying on the ground.

The Vile Demon was similarly inspecting Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai was wearing his Dark Mage Robe as he stood on the head of the Bone Dragon. In his hand was a blood red magic staff. Although his appearance was quite ordinary, his aura was telling a completely different thing. Zhao Hai’s imposing aura wasn’t any less than the VIle Demon himself.

The Vile Demon looked at Zhao Hai, then with his deep voice he said, “Are you Mister Zhao Hai?”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare, he didn’t think that the other party would actually know about him. He smiled faintly and said, “Right, I am Zhao Hai. I didn’t think that His Majesty, the Demon Realm’s Northwestern Monarch, the Dragon Demon King actually knew of my name. This Zhao Hai has been disrespectful.”

It was the turn of the Dragon Demon King to be surprised, he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “My Demon Race has been collecting information regarding the continent for tens of thousands of years. Mister Zhao Hai’s quick rise to prominence naturally couldn’t be ignored. Me knowing Mister’s name isn’t surprising. This one is just curious, Mister, how come you are completely well-informed of the things in my Demon Realm? I wonder if Mister can sate my curiosity?”

Chapter 693: Fight

When Zhao Hai heard the Demon Dragon King, he couldn’t help but smile faintly and said, “You Majesty, didn’t your subordinates tell you? I just got the Succubus Berry as my wife.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, the Demon Dragon King couldn’t help but stare for a moment before he laughed and said, “This King forgot. Hahaha. To be honest, this King is quite envious of Mister Zhao Hai’s luck. It’s not easy to subdue a Succubus to become your wife. Mister is truly lucky.”

Zhao Hai certainly would not tell the Demon Dragon King that it was Cai’er who told him all about the Demon Realm. To be honest, Zhao Hai was quite sympathetic towards these Demons. If they only chose to come peacefully, then Zhao Hai will not stop them. However, instead of doing things peacefully, they chose to do war. Although Zhao Hai disliked wars, he certainly wasn’t afraid of it.

Because of this, Zhao Hai chose to lead an army to resist the Demons rather than have Cai’er deal with them. If Zhao Hai were to make Cai’er deal with the Demon Race, he could just make her withdraw all of her branches there. In time, the Demon Realm would possibly enter an extremely severe food crisis.

Zhao Hai didn’t want to starve the entire Demon Realm, so he decided to just fight the Demons in a straightforward way. At the same time, he was also unwilling to expose Cai’er’s identity since it may have a bad influence on her branches.

Zhao Hai looked at the Demon Dragon King and smiled, “Your Majesty has a Succubus as a wife as well, there’s no reason for you to envy me. Right, Your Majesty came as a vanguard, there should be no need to build a city, right?”

The Demon Dragon King looked deeply into Zhao Hai and said, “Mister might know a lot about the Demon Realm, but this time you are mistaken. We decided to build this city so that we can have our own base in the Ark Continent.  No matter how much you natives would like us to go away, you would have no other choice but recognize the existence of our Demon Race.”

Zhao Hai shook his head as he smiled faintly and said, “We can actually recognize your presence, however, it seems like you don’t like us being here. To be honest, the Ark Continent is too small compared to the Demon Realm, all of you cannot just transfer over here. This made me wonder why you even wanted to wage war.”

When he heard Zhao Hai, the Demon Dragon King seemed to turn mad as he shouted, “Why we go to war? Why?! It’s because of lesser creatures being able to occupy such a beautiful land while we Demons get to experience such a hellish landscape. This land should belong to the Demon Race! Anyone who dared to stop us will die!”

Zhao Hai looked at the expression of the Demon King and sighed, he knew that talking would only get this far. He looked calmly at the Demon Dragon King and said, “Then it’s war!”

But before Zhao Hai gets to command his army, he gets interrupted by the Demon King who said, “Mister, wait. Do you really want to become an enemy to the Demon Race? Mister is a Dark Mage, your kind had always been suppressed in the Ark Continent. At the same time, your belief in the God of Darkness is no different to our faith for the Demon God. How about mister joins our side, and together we shall conquer the entire continent. With Mister’s strength, as long as you help us occupy the continent, then we would surely give you a very high rank.”

Zhao Hai stared at the Demon Dragon King, then after a moment he suddenly laughed, “I want to thank Your Majesty’s good intentions. However, this Zhao Hai already considers himself as a person of the Ark Continent. Although there are friction between the powers in the continent, all of us share the same resistance against being slaves or being exterminated. Even if the Demons or the Divine Race make out continent’s rivers turn red, we would still continue to fight on until the very end!” Zhao Hai expressed his thoughts, as well as the conviction of the entire continent.

The Demon Dragon King looked at Zhao Hai, his expression turned ugly as he said, “Mister’s words truly enraged this King. Then from now on, the entire Demon Race and I shall be your mortal enemies!” Then the Demon Dragon King waved his hand as the Dragons that were pulling his carriage issued a loud roar. After that, the Demons around the carriage charged towards Zhao Hai. It seems like they wanted to eliminate him here and now.

Zhao Hai smiled faintly as he waved his hand. The Bone Dragon retreated back as the other undead pressed on forward, blocking every attack coming towards Zhao Hai.

The Demon Dragon King slowly turned back as well. In fights like these, the superiors would naturally refrain from engaging in the initial clash. It just didn’t conform to their status.

Before long, the undead and the Demons clashed, their strengths were unexpectedly the same. When the Demon Dragon King saw this, he couldn’t help but knit his eyebrows. Although they had collected a lot of information pertaining to Zhao Hai, it seems like they still underestimated him. The Demon King didn’t expect Zhao Hai to be this difficult to deal with.

There were also some races in the Demon Realm who were able to control the undead. This was because the Demon Realm was a very good environment for the evolution of undead. Therefore, this made the undead of the realm very strong. Making them one of the main battle forces of the Demon Realm.

Naturally, the undead couldn’t be the true battle army of the Demon Realm. Although undead could be controlled by races, there was only one race that can command them with great complexity, and it was the Demon Realm’s Lich Race.

The Lich Race was very special in that they were extremely low in population. Moreover, they were quite mysterious. However, they were just the Demon Realm’s version of the true Lich Race.

The True Lich race were legendary beings of the underworld. They were creatures that only existed in soul form and couldn’t be harmed by physical attacks. All of them were innately talented in Dark Magic. In the past, there was a Dark Mage that was able to summon a true Lich. That Lich had wisdom that was no lesser than a Human. At the same time, it was also not willing to be under the control of a Human. This caused a backlash on its summoner. This was also the time where people came to know of their existence.

On the other hand, the Demon Realm’s Lich Race was actually just a type of Demon that possess half of a soul form. This meant that they were still susceptible to material attacks. However, their bodies still had a strange ability of going ethereal when an attack arrives, greatly minimizing the damage done to it. This ethereal form can only be achieved for a short time, and cannot be used continuously as well. Therefore, they were called the Demon Realm’s Lich Race.

The fighting strength of a Lich is no worse than a Vile Demon. The only reason why they weren’t rulers of the Demon Realm was because of their low population. It was estimated that the entire Demon Realm only had around ten thousand Lich.

The entire Demon Realm was so big, and for the number of Lich to only be ten thousand was something that baffled a lot of people. However, since each one of them were very strong, nobody dared to annoy them. Even the Vile Demons would act polite towards these beings. The Lich were able to control a large amount of undead. As to how much, nobody really knew. What they only knew was that a extremely formidable Lich appeared a long time ago. That Lich was able to control an astonishing 1 million undead and controlled them in order to annoy the Vile Demons. It was precisely because of its actions that the Vile Demons decided to sent troops in order to deal with the Lich.

In order to kill this Lich, the Vile Demons sent an army of 3 million. In the end, of the 3 million, only 850 thousand managed to survive. At the same time, the battle also made the Vile Demons lose 20 9th rank experts. This battle was a testament of how powerful the Lich were.

And while the Vile Demons were surrounding this Lich, they were also able to witness the prowess of the Lich’s undead. The undead were quite strong, majority of them had 7th to 8th rank strength. Additionally, these undead were unafraid to die in battle. This fearlessness was something that even the Vile Demons were unable to emulate. This event made the Lich Race untouchables in the Demon Realm.

In the beginning, the Demon Dragon King thought that the Demon Realm made the most powerful undead. After all, the constant battle in the Realm was the best catalyst in creating formidable undead. However, the Demon Dragon King eventually found fault in this belief. Zhao Hai’s undead were actually more formidable than the undead in the Demon Realm. They even managed to achieve 9th rank strength.

One must know that the Demons were beings that grew up in battle, this gave them formidable fighting power. Even if they were still 8th ranks, each Demon can easily exhibit 9th rank strength. 8th ranks of the Ark Continent were completely unable to contend with 9th rank Demons.

This time, since the Demon Dragon King acted as the vanguard of the Demon Realm, he was tasked with building the city in order to establish a foothold for the Demon Race. Because of this, not only was he given powerful Vile Demons to command, the other races of the Demon Realm also sent their elites for him to use. This made the vanguard army much more powerful than average Demon armies.

However, such an elite army actually fought to a draw with Zhao Hai’s undead. It was no wonder that the Demon Dragon King was surprised.

Zhao Hai looked calmly at the battle in front of him. He was using this battle in order to gauge the strength of the Demon Army. It was quite obvious that these Demons weren’t 9th ranks, but their strength was still very strong. They were actually able to fight evenly with the 9th rank undead. Although there was still a small gap between them, the mere fact that they lasted this long was already quite surprising.

While the battle progressed on, Zhao Hai’s mood had turned heavier and heavier. If this was the strength of their 8th ranks, then what can be said about their 9th ranks? It seems like the fight with the Demon Realm wouldn’t go smoothly as what he thought.

The two sides proceeded to strangle each other in the air. Zhao Hai’s undead always fought head-on with the opposing Demons. And these Demons were no stranger to this kind of battle. They even managed to make a formation in the air while fighting with the undead.

Chapter 694: This Enemy Is Hard To Deal With

The reason why Zhao Hai battled with the Demon Race right now was not to block them nor stop them from making their fortifications. Zhao Hai knew that this was impossible. He attacked this time in order to probe the Demon Race’s fighting strength.

In the end, it seems like the Demons were very strong. This was bad news for the continent. The stronger the Demons were, the harder it would be for the continent to fight back.

Zhao Hai continued to watch the battle. Although the fight was quite intense, there weren’t much losses in the Demon Race’s side. These Demons were very proficient in fights, they seemed to be complete veterans when it came to these, they rarely get injured. Even if they were unable to dodge an attack, they would still make movements to ensure that they would get minimum damage. Then after getting injured, they would immediately proceed to retreat from the front. It was evident that they were very used to these maneuvers. Not only was their bodies sturdy, their recovery was also quite quick. Therefore, it wasn’t very easy to kill one of them.

Zhao Hai could remember his previous fight with a group of Vile Demons. After receiving a mortal wound, they could even launch a counter-attack. While thinking about this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but feel apprehensive. If all of the Demons in the Demon Realm had this property, then it would be really scary.

The Demon Dragon King and Zhao Hai looked at each other from across the battlefield. Both of them knew that there wasn’t much to be had in today’s battle. Although Zhao Hai had a lot of undead, he was still unable to kill Demons at a faster rate. While the battle was going on, more and more Demons were still coming out of the rift. Since continuing the battle would useless, Zhao Hai had planned for his retreat.

Although the undead were called that way, it didn’t mean that they have true immortal bodies. Once experts of the Demon Realm arrived, then it might be possible for Zhao Hai to suffer huge losses. Since he didn’t want to go all out, Zhao hai smiled towards the Demon Dragon King and said, “Your Majesty Demon Dragon king, I shall be retreating for today. I will wait for you in Demon City.” Then Zhao Hai turned his Bone Dragon around and headed back to Demon City. When he left, the undead who were still fighting the Demons suddenly vanished. This made the Demons, who were planning to go all out fighting, stare. Even if they wanted to continue fighting, they already didn’t have an enemy to fight with.

When the Demons saw Zhao Hai standing alone on top of his Bone Dragon, heading back to Demon City at a leisurely pace, all of them thought of one thing, it was to rush in and kill Zhao Hai. And as they were going to execute their action, the Demon Dragon King suddenly shouted, “Halt! All of you go back with me.” All the Demons turned to the Demon Dragon King and stopped what they were about to do. Although they didn’t know why the Demon Dragon King stopped them, they knew that they couldn’t violate his commands. After all, the army rules of the Demons were extremely strict.

At this time, a Vile Demon flew towards the Demon Dragon King and said, “Your Majesty, why didn’t you make us chase? We still have a lot of people on our side. Moreover, more people would keep coming as time goes by. It is the best time to pursue. If we manage to kill this Zhao Hao, then we would gain huge merit towards the Demon Race.”

The Demon Dragon King looked at the vile Demon, he was quite fond of this subordinate of his called Loyola. He was a very brave warrior and was also a good commander, his only negative was his hot temper.

The Demon Dragon King looked at Loyola and replied, “Don’t forget about what’s important. We are here to build the city first. As long as we’ve built this city, then the Demon Race would be able to establish a footing in the Ark Continent. This would give us much more leverage in attacking the continent. On the other hand, what could we accomplish in chasing after Zhao Hai? From our investigations, not only does Zhao Hai have formidable undead, he’s also a 9th rank expert. Moreover, he is a rare Human that trains in both Battle Qi and Magic. With this in mind, are you really confident in dealing with him?”

When Loyola heard the Demon Dragon King, he didn’t make any other noise. He had personally fought in the frontline, so he was aware of how strong Zhao Hai’s undead were. Zhao Hai’s undead vanished because he received them, they weren’t defeated by the Demons. If they pursue, then Zhao Hai can just use those undead to suppress them once more. It was truly impossible to deal with Zhao Hai in this way.

The Demon Dragon King looked at Zhao Hai’s back and said, “If this person isn’t eliminated, then our Demon Race would surely have great big troubles. This matter should be reported to His Majesty.” Then the Demon Dragon King took his carriage and went back to the Demonic Abyss.

Although the Demon Dragon King was the monarch of the Demon Realm’s northwest, he wasn’t the Lord of the entire Demon Race. He was only a king in his own territory. In front of the Great Demon King, he can only be an official, this explains why the Demon Dragon King still had someone to call ‘His Majesty’.

Zhao Hai returned to Demon City under the cheers of the defenders. These people hadn’t heard Zhao Hai’s exchange with the Demon Dragon King, but they still witnessed the fight that happened. Although Zhao Hai couldn’t wipe out the opposing party, he was still able to completely match them. This made every person in the city very excited.

After all, Zhao Hai was just one person, yet the Demons were still unable to overwhelm him. This was truly something that can raise people’s morale.

In the past, these people only knew Zhao Hai’s strength through word of mouth, they hadn’t seen him make a move with their own eyes. This time, they had finally managed to see how powerful Zhao Hai really was.

When he saw the people in the city, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile faintly. Then when he turned his head to look at the Demon camp, his expression couldn’t help but turn heavy.

After some time, Zhao Hai turned to the guard closes to him and said, “The Demons wouldn’t be attacking for quite some time since they are still busy with their city. Stay here and monitor them, I’ll be taking a rest.”

The guards complied with thunderous response. Then Zhao Hai flew up and went inside the Bone Dragon’s mouth.

Everyone in the continent were aware that Zhao Hai tended to go inside his undead and live there. Therefore, when the guards saw Zhao Hao enter the Bone Dragon, none of them were very surprised.

Actually, Zhao Hai entering the Bone Dragon was just to conceal that he just went to the Space. After arriving inside the Space, Lizzy immediately came to welcome him as she said, “Brother Hai, this enemy is truly difficult to deal with. These Demons are quite strong. Moreover, their formation was something they developed across many years. Finding a formation to counter them would not be easy.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “They are truly difficult to deal with, they’re quite suited for battle. You must have seen it, although we managed to injure a lot of Demons, the number of their casualties aren’t very large. We didn’t manage to make them suffer enough losses. Also, their numbers would continue to swell up. This is quite troublesome.”

Lizzy nodded, Megan did the same as well. Then after some time, Megan said, “Big Brother Hai, the Buddha Empire’s evacuation would still need some time. Do we need to stop them here for long?’

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “i don’t know. The only action we can make is do our best here. I already reached an agreement with the Fishmen. They will be entering the Buddha Empire’s waterways, first is to help the refugees in their retreat. And the second would be to block the Demons if it becomes necessary. But even if we use the rivers to block the Demons, we still cannot stop their further advance. It seems like we can only rely on the Dwarf Mountain and the Elven Forest to block their advance.”

At this point, Lizzy frowned and said, “Is this fine? The Demons are very strong. Can the Dwarves and Elves really block them?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Rest assured, they can certainly block them. Don’t forget, the two of them have their own Divine Artifacts. More importantly, I’m quite sure that the Radiant Church had started to get anxious. They should be starting their move any time now.”

Lizzy agreed with this point. Although Zhao Hai couldn’t see what the Radiant Church was doing, one could still see that they had been anxious just by the state of their Empire.

Zhao Hai looked at the Demon Camp on the monitor and sighed, “The Demons have changed their methods this time. I can remember that in the records of the Dwarves, the Demons immediately attacked upon entering the Ark Continent. In the end, the Demons went to far and was beaten back by the various races. But this time, it seems like the Demons have gotten smart. They actually decided to build a city first. As long as this city gets built, then they would gain a stable footing in the continent, allowing them a safe place to retreat. This isn’t good for us.”

Megan frowned, then she said, “Wouldn’t it be better for us if we destroy the city?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “I’m afraid that won’t be easy. The Demons are settled on having this city. I’m afraid that with my current strength, we still couldn’t afford to destroy it.”

Megan looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Are you sure? We have about 20 million undead in our hands. Couldn’t they just overwhelm the city?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “Don’t forget, in addition to their strength, the Demons also have a self-destructing technique. If we push them too far, then they might decide to sacrifice themselves, taking several undead along with them. If we trade like that, we could easily deplete our number of undead. And what do we do when our undead gets depleted? I don’t want to use the continent to fill those numbers.”

Megan nodded, she understood what Zhao Hai meant. Although Zhao Hai had 20 million undead, this was their main battle force in resisting both the Demon Race and the Divine Race. Topping up those numbers with people from the continent wasn’t something that Zhao Hai wanted to see.

Lizzy nodded and said, “It’s best if we don’t destroy the city, this would give us even more time to prepare. At the same time, if the Divine Race really did come, then the Demons would be able to cause more trouble to the Divine Race..”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he turned his head to look at the two and said, “How about Laura and Berry? Are they busy?”

Lizzy nodded and said, “Elder Sister Laura is busying herself with the allocation of materials. Although she had Cai’er for help, the tasks that needed to be done is just too many. On the other hand, Berry was still enjoying the scenery in the Space. She kept staring at the unchanging grassland. I really don’t know why she liked that scene.”

Zhao Hai sighed and said, “The scene might be dull to us. But for Berry, it was the most wonderful thing that she had seen in her entire life. Cai’er had already told us about the situation in the Divine Realm. Cai’er’s leaves weren’t delicious, yet her leaves are still the most staple food of the Demon Realm. From just this point, we can imagine what kinds of days she had while in the Demon Realm. I’m sure she wouldn’t get tired of the scenery for a long time.”

Lizzy sighed, then Megan looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Big Brother Hai, Sister Ruyen has been going all out these past few days. It seems like her body is getting weaker and weaker every day. Go and see her. Otherwise, her body might really break down.”

Zhao Hai sighed, then he nodded as  his figure vanished and appeared inside the Lyon Empire’s Royal Palace. Ruyen was currently inside, processing documents. Although Zhao Hai already left, the Great Nobles still didn’t dare to neglect Ruyen’s presence. As long as something important cropped up, they would immediately have Ruyen look through it. Although this allowed Ruyen to have a grasp of the Empire, this made her very tired as well.

Zhao Hai looked at Ruyen, she was even thinner than when he last saw her. Zhao Hai’s heart couldn’t help but ache when he saw this, at the same time, he couldn’t help but look at Ruyen in a new light. Everyone was young at one point of their life, and everyone makes mistakes as well. For Zhao Hai, Ruyen’s hard work can already be considered to be the price that she paid for her past mistakes. Zhao Hai doesn’t want to see Ruyen torture herself anymore.

Zhao Hai also thought that he had been unfair to Ruyen. Among his women, the only one who didn’t know about the Space was her. This made Zhao Hai feel sorry, so he decided to tell Ruyen about the Space.

When Ruyen heard Zhao Hai sigh, she looked up. Upon seeing Zhao Hai, Ruyen couldn’t help but let out a breath as she smiled and quickly said, “You’re here.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he looked at Ruyen and said, “I just fought with the Demons. Neither of us lost or won. It seems like we can only use Accra Mountain as a defensive terrain to block the Demons.”

Ruyen couldn’t help but stare when she heard Zhao Hai. Then she immediately too a step towards Zhao Hai and said, “How are you? Are you injured?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I’m fine. On the other hand, you look like you couldn’t survive for another day. You already did a good job, don’t busy yourself too much. I’ll take you to a place where you can take a well-deserved rest.” Then he went and held Ruyen’s hand.

Ruyen was overjoyed when she felt Zhao Hai’s warm hand. Zhao Hai looked at Ruyen and smiled at her as their figures flashed and entered the Space.

Chapter 695: Billy’s Idea

In the past, Zhao Hai didn’t tell Ruyen and Evan about the Space. What they knew was that Zhao Hai was someone with a Space Divergent Ability.

When their figures appeared inside the Space, Ruyen’s mind couldn’t help but turn blank. They were currently in front of the Space’s villa, and Ruyen saw Lizzy and Megan.

When she saw them, Ruyen couldn’t help but pull her hand away from Zhao Hai. She was still ashamed in front of Lizzy and Megan, one was because of her status, and two, because of her past.

When Lizzy and Megan saw Ruyen’s action, they smiled but didn’t say anything. Zhao Hai turned his head to Ruyen and said, “Alright, Ruyen, you can take a rest here. Lizzy and Megan will tell you everything there is to know about this place. I still need to head out.”

Ruyen gave a nod before Lizzy and Megan pulled her over and telling her everything about the Space. Then Zhao Hai’s figure disappeared as he went out of the Space. This time, he wasn’t heading towards Demon City, but instead towards Dwarf Mountain. The Dwarf Mountain is inside the Buddha Empire, because of this, Zhao Hai thought that once the Buddha Empire’s army withdrew, the closest army to face the Demons would be the Dwarves.

When Zhao Hai arrived inside Dwarf Mountain, he was quick to notice that the atmosphere here was very different compared to the past. There used to be the sounds of Dwarves hammering here, there were also Dwarven Women, making armor and other things. But now, the place appeared very empty, there weren’t any Dwarf children or women present. The only ones left were Dwarves soldiers. When Zhao Hai appeared, he was immediately escorted by two soldiers towards Billy’s office. When Billy saw Zhao Hai, he immediately asked the latter to take a seat. After sitting down, Billy looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Why did you come? Did something happen?” Zhao Hao nodded, “The Demons have arrived and I had a minor scuffle with them. Neither of us won or lost.”

Billy nodded with a heavy expression. He knew how strong Zhao Hai’s undead were, and to think that Zhao Hai was unable to win, it seems like these Demons wouldn’t be easy to deal with.

Zhao Hai turned his head to Billy and said, “Patriarch, how are your preparations doing?” Billy gave a nod and said, “Preparations are doing well, moreover, with the magic beasts that you gave us, our communication with the Elves has gone much smoother.”

Zhao Hai nodded, after taking the Dwarf women and children to the Black Wasteland, Zhao Hai released large quantities of water element beasts in order to aid the Dwarves. With these magic beast, the Dwarves would have it easier to communicate with the Elves. At the same time, this also made it easier for the Dwarves to traverse the underground rivers of the mountain.

Billy looked at Zhao Hai and said, “The people from the Buddha Empire are still moving. It will take at least two months before all of them left. I’m afraid that relying on Demon City for defense wouldn’t be enough. We should try and find another solution.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I also think that Demon City wouldn’t be enough to slow the Demons down. Therefore, I plan to lay some ambushes on every city in the Buddha Empire.”

Billy nodded and said, “That isn’t wrong, but there are some issues. If you want to really ambush the Demons in the Buddha Empire, then relying only on the Buddha Empire’s army would be a good idea. The Buddha Empire is famous for their iron, this made their heavy armored cavalry very effective in battling in the plains How about getting the Beastmen to help the Buddha Empire in defending? And while the Beastmen and Buddha Empire cavalry are attacking the Demons in the field, we can also have some Blood Hawk Cavalry and some Hawk Beastmen attack from the skies. Adding your undead to all of these would be a very good way to tussle with the Demons going through the Buddha Empire. Moreover, this would also increase the depth of strategy in the battlefield. What do you think?”

Zhao Hai was shocked, he hasn’t thought about this point. Now that Billy reminded him, he can remember that he can now use the entire continent as manpower in this war. So why wouldn’t he unite the various forces, making sure that everyone shows their best performance?

After thinking about it, ZHao Hai couldn’t help but get pumped up. He was currently thinking about the feasibility of this plan. While the Beastman Cavalry are indeed strong, the Elves are also formidable archers, who also have their own aerial cavalry. If this aerial cavalry were to ride the Blood Hawks, then their speed should be no slower than the flying Demons. The Elven air force could surely disrupt the Demons in the skies while the Buddha and Beastman Cavalries clashed with the ground toops. At the same time, the Dwarves could also assist in defending Demon City, digging tunnels here and there, making offensive and defensive maneuvers many times more effective.

Nobody could blame Zhao Hai for not thinking about this before. One should know that Zhao Hai had not commanded such a huge battle before. Even though the forces in the continent were listening to Zhao Hai, all of them were also preparing themselves to defend the Demons. During the war, Zhao Hai would just issue his ideas and the others would just make the move. That is to say, Zhao Hai just told them the heading, and they just decide how to do it by themselves.

One could say that Zhao Hai’s capability can only be ranked as an officer, not an alliance leader of such a big alliance. He just didn’t have the talent to do that.

Billy’s idea completely woke Zhao Hai up. If they do as what Billy said, then they won’t only have the Accra Mountain as an option, new paths and strategies would be opened up.

Seeing that Zhao Hai was staying quiet, Billy didn’t speak. He knew that Zhao Hai was lacking in this aspect. However, he wasn’t worried about it since Zhao Hai was still quite young. Moreover, he already has the strength, given enough time, Zhao Hai would mature bit by bit, eventually being able to contend properly with the Demon Race.

After some time, Zhao Hai gained some ground as he looked at Billy and said, “Alright. Patriarch, I know what we should do. However, I would need to ask the Dwarves to dispatch some troops to send towards Demon City. No matter what, we cannot lose that place to the Demons very easily. If we lose it this early, then the Demons would gain more foothold in the continent.”

Billy nodded, “That’s not a problem. Rest assured, we shall have the troops prepared in a short time.” Zhao Hai nodded, then he said, “Alright, then I’d like you to dispatch about 50 thousand troops for Demon City. I’ll be heading to the Buddha Empire now and discuss things with the Buddha Emperor. I want to stop him from sending troops to Demon City. instead, I’ll have the Beastmen and Elves send some troops there instead. Those troops would be a huge help in defending Demon City and delaying the advance of the Demons. At the same time, we’ll have some troops propagate along strategic positions in the Buddha Empire. As for the smaller cities, we can just leave them.”

Billy nodded, “ The Buddha Empire’s situation is truly special. As long as we hold those strategic positions, then we would be fine. Small Cities aren’t just worth defending, instead, we can just have Buddha and Beastman Cavalries wander around selected areas.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Alright, then please prepare your army. I’ll go see the Buddha Emperor now then the Beast King and the Elf Queen. This time, I need to discuss things with them personally.”

Billy nodded, then he stood up to prepare his army. On the other hand, Zhao Hai’s figure vanished as he appeared in the Buddha Empire’s capital. Iron Knight City was actually more bustling compared to before. However, Zhao Hai knew that this wasn’t due to business, these ships were currently transporting people. One could say that the Buddha Empire’s capital had become a beast that had been struck by a sword, bleeding out, but instead of losing blood, it was losing its citizens. In the end, this city would be left empty.

Zhao Hai appeared right outside the Imperial Palace of the Buddha Empire. The Palace has now strengthened its vigilance. It was basically under martial law, there were teams of cavalry constantly patrolling the place.

When he got out of the Space, Zhao Hai immediately summoned his Bone Dragon and then rode it towards the Buddha Empire’s Imperial palace.

At this point, everyone in the continent was aware that the Bone Dragon symbolized Zhao Hai. Even if they didn’t know Zhao Hai’s face, they would still know it was him due to the Bone Dragon.

Zhao Hai’s status in the continent was now very high. He can come and go out of an Imperial Capital at will. Moreover, his words were already considered as Imperial Decrees by the various powers in the continent.

Zhao Hai’s sudden appearance in the Buddha Empire’s capital caused a commotion in the city. Both Warriors and Mages looked at him in reverence while Nobles looked at him with worry. They were afraid that Zhao Hai was carrying unfavorable news.

The Buddha Emperor was currently inside the Great Hall, handling several domestic matters. When transferring citizens, it was imperative that nothing went wrong, and this was a very hard thing to do. The Buddha Emperor hasn’t slept for several days, his appearance had become much thinner compared to before.

When Zhao Hai’s Bone Dragon landed on the Imperial Palace, court eunuchs immediately informed the Buddha Emperor. Upon hearing that Zhao Hai came, he was startled, just as the other Nobles in the Great Hall. They were all afraid that Zhao Hai had brought bad news. What the Buddha Empire needed right now was time in order to evacuate its citizens. If Zhao Hai brought bad news, then things would become even more difficult.

When he arrived at the Great Hall, Zhao Hai was immediately personally greeted by the Buddha Emperor. Upon seeing the Buddha Emperor come out, Zhao Hai immediately gave him a bow as he said, “I have seen Your Majesty.” Then the Buddha Emperor didn’t hesitate to pull Zhao Hai’s hand and said, “Is mister doing well? Why did you come visit? Did an accident happen in the frontlines? Mister can rest assured, in two days, the Empire would have about a million elite cavalry reinforcing Demon City.”

Chapter 696: Deploying Troops

When Zhao Hai saw the Emperor’s expression, he immediately knew what the other was thinking. He smiled at the Emperor and said, “There’s no need for Your Majesty to be worried, everything is going fine. Let’s head inside first.”

Upon hearing that there wasn’t anything wrong with the frontline, the Emperor nodded. Then they returned back into the Great Hall. There were also plenty of ministers present inside, all of them were anxiously looking at Zhao Hai.

After giving a salute to the ministers, Zhao Hai said, “The Demons have appeared in the Demonic Abyss. However, they didn’t attack Demon City immediately. Instead, they actually went and started to build a city.”

“Building a City?” What Zhao Hai said made the other people gawk. But then, they immediately understood the actions of the Demons, each and every one of their complexions couldn’t help but change.

Zhao Hai looked at those present and said, “Everyone, there’s no need to worry too much. I had a small contact with the Demons yesterday, none of us lost nor won. This means that I can stop the Demons there for quite some time. And since the Demons are busy with their city, we still have some time before they begin to launch attacks towards the continent.”

The crowd relaxed, then Zhao Hai turned his head to the Buddha Emperor and said, “Your Majesty, I want to ask you to refrain from sending too many troops to Demon City.”

The Buddha Emperor stared, then he knit his eyebrows and said, “Mister’s meaning is?” Then Zhao Hai replied, “Although Demon City is in a strategic place, its terrains isn’t suited for large scale battles. Moreover, the Buddha Empire’s elite cavalry isn’t really suitable to defend a city. Instead, they excelled in wide plain battles. Because of this, I came here to ask Your Majesty to not send too many Iron Knights to Demon City. Instead, we should divide them to various strategic points in the Buddha Empire. I shall also be asking the Dwarves, Elves, and Beastmen to help with the fight. We’ll be making the entire Buddha Empire into a giant battlefield. And establishing our own advantages here will be good against the Demon attack.”

The Buddha Emperor quietly closed his eyes. He wasn’t someone who didn’t understand military affairs. On the contrary, he actually started in the military, so he was very familiar with strategic decisions. The Demons had come suddenly and he wasn’t able to think much about them at all. So when he heard Zhao Hai, he couldn’t help but think about the matters of the war.

The Buddha Emperor wasn’t dumb, he knew that it was impossible for the Buddha Empire alone to block the Demon Advance. Otherwise, he wouldn’t have listened to Zhao Hai’s request to have the civilians be evacuated.

Because of this, the Buddha Emperor was in staunch agreement with regards to turning his entire Empire into a huge battlefield. His heart didn’t feel pain for those cities, he knew that all of these needed to be done. As long as the citizens are alive, then the Empire is still standing.

At the same time, he was also considering the feasibility of Zhao Hai’s plan. The Buddha Empire’s Iron Knight Cavalry was very well-known. Additionally, when they mounted the beasts that Zhao Hai brought, the Buddha Empire’s Cavalry, along with the Beastmen, can definitely take advantage of the Buddha Empire’s plains in order to resist the Demon advance. On the other hand, having Dwarf Infantry was also very good in defending Demon City. After all, the Dwarves were formidable melee fighters. One shouldn’t underestimate them just because they are short, the hammers in their backs can easily deal heavy strikes with each swing. Although there weren’t much news with regards to the Elves in recent years, it was also known that the magic and archery of the Elves were top notch. Having a mixed army like this would actually help in dealing with the Demon Race.

After thinking about it, the Buddha Emperor opened his eyes slowly and said, “Alright, then we’ll move according to Mister’s plan. I shall immediately send orders, sending one army troop to defend Demon City. In any case, they are already itching for a fight. My Buddha Empire’s soldiers aren’t afraid to die, all of them wanted to make the Demons pay for the price of invading the Ark Continent.’

Zhao Hai nodded, “Then I’ll leave you here to prepare. I’ll be meeting the Beastmen and the Elves next. We cannot delay in deploying troops.”

The Buddha Emperor stood up and gave Zhao Hai a big salute, “I represent the entire Buddha Empire in expressing our gratitude to Mister. If not for your effort in going back and forth between nations, then the Buddha Empire might have already been buried in history.”

Zhao Hai was then quick to reply, “Your Majesty is too polite, I’m just considering the fate of the entire continent. Your Majesty can rest assured, I’ve already arranged for your people’s stay inside the Lyon Empire. At the same time, the Aksu Empire has been short of people, for those who are willing to help with the manpower, I shall have them sent there by boat.”

The Buddha Emperor looked at Zhao Hai, he didn’t know what to say. He knew that without Zhao Hai, it would be impossible for the Buddha Empire to survive. They might already been conquered by the Demons by now. Moreover, the eastern parts of the Buddha Empire might have also fallen to the Dragon-ruled Lyon Empire.

Zhao Hai gave the Buddha Emperor a slight bow as he turned around to leave the Imperial palace. When Zhao Hai left, the Buddha Emperor immediately sent some orders, “Pass this order, have the armies near the Rising Sun City, Lower Bank City, South Plain City, Water Wheel City, Broad Flat City congregate. Have them form a defensive line along the river. The west bank cities would need to do the same as well. Mister told me that he would have marine friends assist us, so we should fortify the river locations. Run along the other branches of Iron Warhorse City and have armies stationed there as well. Control the logistics and have all those points interconnected with each other. Let’s make the Demons regret going through the Buddha Empire, we’ll make them bleed out with every step they make. With the capital as the center, we will have six strategic lines going outwards. The Buddha Empire will be the greatest fortress the continent has ever seen.”

The officials in the Great Hall issued a huge shout. The Buddha Emperor looked at them and said, “Mister Zhao Hai has been going all out in the frontlines. He is doing this not only for us, but also for the entire continent. We, the Buddha Empire, are not afraid of war. Since Mister Zhao Hai is willing to give his all to the continent, then the Buddha Empire shall help him by becoming an advantageous battlefield for the alliance. This is our home, there’s nobody more familiar with the place than us. We shall make the Demons understand that it was a mistake stepping in the lands if the Buddha Empire!” Overwhelmed with his emotions, the Buddha Empire even slammed the table right in front of him.

The Ministers in the Great Hall simultaneously shouted, “Long Live the Buddha Empire!! Long Live his Majesty!” The Buddha Emperor looked at tho officials and said, “The entire Ark Continent has entered a special period. Various brothers from the other races will be helping us. I want all of you to remember that from now on, all these races will be the friends of the Human Race. Spread my command, have all our brothers from a different race be treated with utmost hospitality. Anyone disobeying this rule will be punished heavily!”

The ministers acknowledged the order. Then the Buddha Emperor nodded and said, “Go and make your preparations. Tabulate the needed materials and then report back to me. We’ll be asking mister for help in this regard. Now go!” After giving a bow, the ministers proceeded to leave the Great Hall.

When everyone left, the Buddha Emperor slowly sat down on his throne. His eyes were shining brightly as he laughed by himself, “Hahaha, be quick, Demons. Let me see who is more formidable, you or my Iron Knights! Hahaha” After all that happened in the Buddha Empire, the fear and anxiety that the Buddha Emperor felt had been swept away. Instead, it actually provoked his arrogance. He suddenly reverted back to his attitude back when he was just an ordinary soldier, during the times where he was still hot-blooded and was charging his enemies in the frontlines. Ever since he had become the Emperor, this mindset had slowly withdrew. But now, it seems like it was reignited due to the upcoming war.

Zhao Hai wasn’t aware about this, he was currently inside the Elven Forest. When the Elves spotted Zhao Hai, they immediately sent a report to the Queen who invited Zhao Hai directly to the Royal Palace.

Upon arriving at the palace hall, Zhao Hai met the newly appointed Great Elder. He immediately gave a bow to the Queen and the elder before saying, “I have seen Your Majesty and the Great Elder.”

The Queen quickly replied, “Mister doesn’t need to conform to ceremony. May I know why mister made a visit this time?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I have an important matter to tell you, Your Majesty. The matter is like this….” Then Zhao Hai told the Queen the matter that he had discussed with Billy. “Your Majesty, I’d like it if you are to send troops to help defend Demon City. I have discussed this matter with the Buddha Emperor as well. What do you think?”

The Queen frowned, to be honest, she didn’t want the Elves to mingle with the others. However, she was also aware of how effective Zhao Hai’s plan would be. Therefore, she gave a nod and said, “Alright, then I shall send 5000 archers to be dispatched to Demon City.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Then Your Majesty has my gratitude. I won’t be staying here for long, I still need to go to the Beastmen. However, Your Majesty can rest assured, nobody would dare touch the Elves if they appear in the continent. Otherwise, I shall be the first one to punish them. And also, when I leave, I shall be leaving 5000 Blood Hawks to be the mounts of the Elves. The Blood Hawks are more suitable mounts for combat compared to the Voiceless Soundbirds. When Your Majesty has prepared your army, you can have them ride the Blood Hawk towards Demon City.” The Queen nodded and said, “Alright, then we shall be following Mister’s arrangement.” Zhao Hai gave the Queen a bow before he turned around to leave.

When Zhao Hai left, the Great Elder looked at the Queen and said, “Your Majesty, should we really dispatch troops this early? To be honest, with our current strength, we can sufficiently hold the Demons back inside the forest. On the other hand, why do we need to work together with the Humans?”

Chapter 697: Bustling About

The Queen shook her head and said, “Things aren’t as easy as that. Although the Elven Forest is indeed our Domain, but our population isn’t really that many. On the other hand, it is for certain that the Demons will come in huge numbers. Even if we can slow them down, we would also become grinded down by numbers. There is no problem with us working with the Humans. Also, if we stay here, and the Humans aren’t able to stop the Demons, do you think that we can stop them? That’s impossible.” The Great Elder nodded, she knew that the Queen was right. Compared to the Humans, their population was indeed to small. The Elves and the Demons have the same long life, but the Elves have the problem of procreation. This made their numbers quite small. If they were to have a battle of attrition with the Demons, then they would definitely lose.

The Queen turned to the Great Elder and said, “Moreover, Mister Zhao Hai already gave us his guarantee, there shouldn’t be any problems if we dispatch our troops. This is also a huge opportunity for all the races in the continent. If the Ark Continent can work together to resist the Demons and the Divine Race, as well as defending the Ark Continent, then the races would have an unprecedented unity for a very long time. Because of this, we cannot just hole up inside the Elven Forest.” The Great Elder nodded, the Elves weren’t people who didn’t have any problem.s Although they had been living good lives inside the forest, the Great Elder knew that there were still things that they lacked. Before they got in contact with the Dwarves, they were in fact living worse lives.

Zhao Hai wasn’t thinking about any of these right now, he was going see the Beast King. The Beast King had also been preparing for the past few days. At this time, the entire Beastman Prairie was already aware about the Demon Race. But since they were too far from the frontlines, the only thing they can provide would be living materials as well as preparing some area for the eventual Human refugees. Aside from that, there wasn’t anything that they can do.

The Beast King wasn’t very busy when Zhao Hai arrived, therefore, he immediately invited Zhao Hai over to this study. The Beast King looked at Zhao Hai and said, “How is it? How is the frontline?” Zhao Hai smiled at the Beast King and said, “The frontline is doing fine. This time, I came here in order to ask for some troops from the Beastmen.” The Beast King stared for a moment, then he said, “Really? That’s great! The Warring Clans have been itching for a fight. But unfortunately, we are just too far away from the Buddha Empire. So when will I send the troops?”

When he saw the Beast King’s excitement, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile and said, “There’s no need to go quickly. I only came here to ask you for troops. At this time, it would be great if you can prepare some people to help defend Demon City. And then….” Zhao Hai continued on to tell the Beast King about the plans regarding the Buddha Empire.

After listening to Zhao Hai, the Beast King repeatedly nodded and said, “Alright, that’s great. I’ll arrange for the troops right away. You said you needed an army to defend Demon City? I already have a race in mind. They’re quite fond of Humans and are quite gentle. However, they are extremely strong, and are one of the few infantry focused races in the Prairie. Although they have mounts as well, their speed really aren’t that good. Defending cities shouldn’t be a problem for them.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “That’s good. Then I’ll be returning to Demon City. When your army have gathered, go send me word and I’ll take them with me to Buddha Empire and Demon City.”

The Beast King nodded and said, “Alright, then just wait for information. The Beastmen had always wanted to try the strengths of those Demons. Thank you.”

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “Alright, then I’ll be leaving. There are still things that are needed to be processed in the frontline.” The Beast King nodded, then Zhao Hai returned to the Space.

However, he didn’t immediately go back to Demon City. Instead, he went to the Aksu Empire in order to see Boris. Although the army of the Aksu Empire has been restored, their veteran fighters were eliminated during the war with the Beastmen. This placed the Aksu Empire’s strength at the bottom of all the Empires. However, the Aksu Empire was still very cooperative now that the Demons were invading. They were providing goods to the others and was even willing to take in Buddha Empire refugees. Because of this, Zhao Hai felt the need to see Boris and discuss the new plan with him.

Boris and Zhao Hai were mortal enemies in the past, but now, the sentiment was different. They were now allies, moreover, the two haven’t met in person in the past, so there wasn’t any awkwardness between the two of them.

Boris welcomed Zhao Hai to his study, then after his people served them some tea, Boris looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Did Mister come because an accident happened in the frontline?” Zhao Hao was a bit startled, however, he managed to smile and said, “There’s no need to worry, the frontline is doing just fine. This time, I came to discuss a different matter.” Then he told Boris about what happened to the front line, then Zhao Hai looked at Boris and said, “Your Majesty, I know about the current state of the Aksu Empire. Therefore, I won’t be asking you to dispatch some troops. However, as the war in the frontline goes on, I may need to ask for assistance, so please prepare your troops just in case. If you need anything, then don’t hesitate to send word.” Boris nodded, “Alright, you can rest assured that the Aksu Empire will give full cooperation. My Aksu Empire might have made the wrong decision in the past, however, we won’t be repeating our mistakes this time.”

Zhao Hai gave a nod, then he said, “Alright, then my matters here has been settled. I’ll be heading to the Rosen Empire next to discuss matters with the Rosen Emperor.” Borise stood up and then bowed towards Zhao Hai, “Boris must thank Mister Zhao Hai. You and I are enemies, yet you decided to ignore that fact and help us. This makes me feel very guilty. Mister can rest assured, the Aksu Empire shall give its all in supporting this war.” Zhao Hai returned Boris’ bow and said, “Your Majesty is too polite. Yours and my enmity is no more than a dispute between Humans. This time, we must unite in order to repel the invaders. In the end, the Aksu Empire has already sided with the Ark Continent Alliance. I hope that Your Majesty takes care of the rear while also providing help to the frontline.”

Boris replied, “Mister can rest assured, I know how to do this.” Zhao Hai nodded and then bowed to Boris once more before turning around to head towards Rosen Empire.

Zhao Hai wanted to transfer some Rosen and Lyon Empire troops to the Buddha Empire. The Buddha Empire was known for their Iron Knights, the Rosen Empire for their Iron Infantry, while the Lyon Empire for their magic beast cavalry. The Rosen Empire troops are very skilled in defending cities, on the other hand, the Lyon Cavalry was quite skilled in the plains. These two qualities were very needed by the Buddha Empire right now.

Zhao Hai didn’t return to the Rosen Empire for quite some time. Although he was now the Emperor of the Lyon Empire, Zhao Hai didn’t really want to be one right now. So in seeing the Rosen Emperor, he still conducted himself as a son-in-law. This gave the Emperor a good impression of him.

When Zhao Hai arrive to the Imperial Palace, the Emperor was already holding a conference. Naturally, this was a discussion about the Demon Race.

While they discussed, a court eunuch suddenly arrived and reported Zhao Hai’s arrival. The Emperor and Randolph were startled, they were thinking that something must’ve happened in the front line. The Emperor immediately said, “Invite him in, quickly.”

After Zhao Hao entered the room, he immediately gave salute to the Emperor and Randolph. The Emperor looked at Zhao Hai and said, “What’s the matter Little Hai? Did an accident happen in Demon City? With your strength, it should be impossible for the Demons to break through this quickly. So what happened?”

Zhao Hai immediately replied, “Father-in-law, there aren’t any problems with the frontline. As long as we have hold over Accra Mountain, there won’t be any major problems in our defense. I have just visited the various powers, and even Boris to discuss something. This time, I came to see father-in-law to discuss the same thing. I’d like for the Rosen Empire to send troops over to the Buddha Empire in order to aid with the defense.”

The Emperor nodded and said, “This isn’t an issue. I’ve also thought about establishing an advance defensive line. We can’t just be overly passive. At the same time, the Buddha Empire is known for its Iron Knights, they can only express their full might in the plains. On the other hand the Rosen Empire troops are very skilled in siege warfare. We’re already prepared here, just tell us how much troops you need and we’ll provide it to you.” Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Alright, then I’ll make sure to send a number as soon as possible. I really can’t stay here for long, I still have a lot of matters to deal with.”

The Emperor nodded, “You are my son-in-law, so I will definitely support you. You go busy yourself now. There’s no need to worry about our side. Focus on teaching those bastard Demons a lesson they won’t ever forget.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Father-in-law can rest assured, we’ll be doing just that.”

The Emperor gave a satisfied nod and said, “Right how are Lizzy and Megan? You’ve been everywhere lately, how are they doing? Since they can’t provide help, then they might as well come home lest they provide you with unnecessary trouble.”

Zhao Hai forced a smile and said, “Father-in-law, that’s not a good idea. They really aren’t giving me any trouble, instead, they are actually very helpful. At this point, the formations for my undead have already been handed to the two of them. Their talent in commanding is very good.”

The Emperor and Randolph couldn’t help but stare, the Emperor looked puzzled at Zhao Hai as he said, “You have Megan and Lizzy take charge of your undead? Am I hearing it right?” Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I won’t dare to deceive you, I’m telling the truth. Megan and Lizzy have already been commanding my undead for quite some time. Especially back in the Fishman territory, they were a great help in defeating the Sea Dragons. In the war with the Demons, I’m also thinking of having the two of them command my undead. If they are to go home, then that would be a huge problem for me.”

The Emperor laughed and said, “Alright, that’s good. I didn’t think that those two girls had such a skill. Alright, then we’ll have them continue to accompany you. However, you must ensure that they are safe at all times.”

Zhao Hai quickly replied, “Father-in-law can feel relieved. I will certainly keep them safe.”

Chapter 698: Crucial Refining

Zhao Hai was currently looking at Bubble who was floating in front of him. Although Zhao Hai can’t see any expression on him, he was sure that Bubble was having a smug expression.

However, Zhao Hai was too glad to mess around with Bubble. This was because the little blob was now able to do refining. Moreover, the experiments done on the Space’s plants yielded great results. Bubble was now ready to refine the lotus. Zhao Hai was wondering what surprises the lotus would bring once it has been refined.

Zhao Hai looked at Bubble, then he snorted and said, “What are you being so smug about? Go and start working on the lotus. Refine everything in the pool as well. If anything goes wrong, then I will definitely clean you up.”

Bubble wasn’t very afraid of Zhao Hai, he was smart, he knew that although Zhao Hai was being hostile, Zhao Hai wouldn’t do anything to him. Zhao Hai just cared too much about the lotus, so if anything goes wrong, then Zhao Hai would be very disappointed.

Although Bubble was quite a headache, in fact, he had already considered Zhao Hai as his master. He knew when things were crucial and when he could mess around. So upon hearing Zhao Hai, Bubble immediately turned around and went to the pool where the lotus was placed. Then after a moment, the lotus pool suddenly disappeared. Zhao Hai wasn’t too surprised about it, he knew that Bubble had his own space inside his body where he can store things. Bubble just needed the lotus to be inside so that he can slowly refine it .

Zhao Hai made Bubble come closer, then he looked into Bubble’s transparent body and saw a small bubble where the lotus was located. Zhao Hai nodded and then looked at Bubble and said, “Bubble, remember to refine the lotus well. There should be no mistakes. Place every inch of your energy in refining, don’t get distracted. Understand?”

Bubble complied as he said, “Young Master, feel relieved, I shall complete it with no problems.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he turned around and proceeded to head towards the villa. He was receiving messages from the various powers in the alliance aside from the Lyon Empire since there was no need for it. Although Zhao Hai was just a temporary Emperor of the Lyon Empire, the Great Nobles of the Empire still wouldn’t dare to disobey him. Not only because of Zhao Hai’s strength, but also because of his status as the focal point of the alliance. If they dared to misbehave under Zhao Hai, then the days left for them to live wouldn’t be very long.

Zhao Hai also instructed them to prepare some troops. At the same time, he also released more magic beasts in order to reestablish the Empire’s elite cavalry unit, making it much stronger than before.

When Zhao Hai came back from the Lyon Empire, Bubble had approached him about his success in refining the plants in the Space. Therefore, Zhao Hai wasn’t able to enter the villa up until now.

When Zhao Hai entered the villa, he was immediately greeted by Ruyen’s smiling face while she was talking with Berry. Lizzy and Megan were at the side as well, looking at the monitor, probably discussing various battle formations and so on.

Upon hearing the sound of the door, the group immediately turned their heads and saw that Zhao Hai has come back. They quickly stood up and welcomed him in. Zhao Hai looked at the women and then smiled, he felt a warm feeling in his heart while looking at this scene. Then he smiled to the group and said, “What’s happening? Are there new formations?”

Lizzy smiled and replied, “How could it be as easy as that? We’re just introducing the Space to sister Ruyen and sister Berry. Big Brother Hai, you should give sister Ruyen some work inside the Space. With this, her body would be benefited as well. And also, we can approach her to discuss some matters later on. What do you think?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “You don’t need to ask me about these things, you can just do it yourself. Ruyen, you can help Laura in the future. Lizzy and Megan aren’t skilled in that area. The only one that can currently lend Laura a hand is you. Now that the continent is at war, material distribution, manpower problems, and the likes are needed to be sorted out properly. Laura has been busy doing these things alone, you should be able to at least ease her burden. LIzzy and Megan will have to command the army a few days from now, so you and Laura need to work hard.” Ruyen immediately replied, “Alright, Brother Hai, rest assured, I will help sister Laura with management.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he turned to Berry. He didn’t know much about the Succubus so he said, “Berry, do you want to stay inside the Space or do you want to go outside with me? If you stay in the Space, then you need to find something to do, otherwise you will get bored. If you go outside, then you can stay by my side.”

Berry quickly replied, “I’ll go and follow you out. The other sisters are very busy with their own affairs inside the Space while I have nothing else to do. I can take care of anything that you need when you’re outside. I have already discussed this matter with sister Lizzy and the others.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Alright, then do as you like. How is Demon City doing right now?”

Lizzy replied, “There aren’t any significant developments in Demon City. However, the Dwarves had already arranged their army. You should look and see if you can transfer them to Demon City right now.”

Zhao Hai thought for a moment and said, “Tell Patriarch Billy to wait . I’ll immediately go and tell General Besmir to prepare a place for the Dwarves to stay in. This is the first cooperation between Humans and Dwarves after a long time, it needs to be processed well.”

Lizzy nodded, then she said, “Alright, then I’ll go talk to Patriarch Billy. Sister Berry, we’ll be leaving Brother Hai’s care to you. As you can see, we have a lot of things to take care of at this time. Only you can take care of Brother Hai right now.”

Berry quickly replied, “Sister, rest assured, I will take good care of Brother Hai.”

Zhao Hai just smiled faintly and didn’t say anything. Actually, he’d much prefer having Meg take care of him. After all, Meg has been looking after him for a long time, so he was already familiar with her routine. However, Meg was also quite busy in helping Laura with her job. With her being heavily engaged, it would be impossible for her to take care of Zhao Hai.

On the other hand, it was quite obvious that Berry had zero interest in those matters. This made it possible for her to go outside of the Space with Zhao Hai.

At this time, Besmir was quite worried. The only thing he knew was that Zhao Hai had fought with the Demons and then went back to the city to take a rest. Besmir didn’t know whether Zhao Hai was doing well or maybe he has been injured. If Zhao Hai was wounded, then it would be a fatal blow to their morale. However, when Zhao Hai came in along with a beautiful woman, Besmir immediately calmed down. Then he went forward to greet Zhao Hai, “Mister came. Please come in. May I know the details regarding mister’s fight with the Demons?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and replied, “It went quite fairly. None of us has taken too much of an advantage over the other, it’s a tie. Right, I came here to talk about something.”

Besmir quickly said, “I ask Mister to tell me and I will do my best to comply.”

Zhao Hai said, “General is too polite, there’s no need to be so formal. I just want to ask you to prepare three camps in the next few days, the sooner they get finished, the better. Some Dwarves will be arriving later, they will help us with defending against the Demons. In a few days, Beastmen and Elven warriors will arrive as well. I want you to prepare three separate areas for each of them. Also, make sure to tell everyone to refrain from offending them. Our cooperation with the other races will be very crucial in the following days.”

Besmir couldn’t help but stare for a moment when he heard Zhao Hai. But it didn’t take too long before he became elated with the news. He was aware that although everyone was willing to resist the Demons, it wasn’t necessary for them to send troops over. At the same time the people of Demons City had already accepted this truth. The others can just be considered to be offering moral support. But now that the other powers are sending their troops, the morale of the defenders would surely surge up once more.

Although Zhao Hai didn’t say it, Besmir knew that these people were all invited by Zhao Hai. Besmir didn’t expect that Zhao Hai would have this much clout over the other races. This was very good for the alliance, so Besmir quickly agreed, “Mister, rest assured, I shall arrange for those areas immediately.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Also, the Elves only take fruits and green vegetables as food, they don’t eat meat. Pay attention to this when giving them rations. On the other hand, the Beastmen love meat. Both the Dwarves and the Beastmen also liked to drink liquor, prepare some for them. If you don’t have any of these in hand, then don’t hesitate to inform me.”

Besmir quickly replied, “Yes Mister. I’ve noted them all down. Don’t worry, I’ll make sure that nothing goes wrong.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he adds, “Remember to keep the area for the Elves very clean, they don’t like dirty places. Also, tell the soldiers to refrain from looking at the reinforcements as though they are monsters. The Dwarves and the Beastmen are quick to lose their temper, and the Elves get offended quite easily. Small problems like these wouldn’t be good when the actual fight comes.”

Besmir replied, “Alright, I’ll take care of it.” Zhao Hai nodded, then he looked outside and the sighed, “I already talked with His Majesty. While we delay the Demons here as much as possible, the Buddha Empire will mobilize its own army in order to provide defensive lines all over the empire. When all of the citizens have withdrawn, the entire Buddha Empire shall be converted into a huge fortress. We’ll make the Demons suffer when the set foot into its lands.”

Besmir’s eyes couldn’t help but fire up when he heard this, his hatred for the Demons couldn’t help but resurface as he replied, “Alright, Mister can rest assured, everything will go according to plan. But with this, it is inevitable that the Buddha Empire will be destroyed.”

Zhao Hai lightly sighed and said, “The Buddha Empire’s land will surely be destroyed. However, as long as its citizens survive, then sooner or later we can reclaim the land and revive the Empire. It’s useless to worry about the land. Don’t forget, the most important thing to the Empire is its people and its talents.”

Chapter 699: Dwarf Race

Citizens of Demon City have already withdrawn, so even if the army had moved in, there were still a lot of unoccupied space inside the City. Because of this, it didn’t take too long for Besmir to arrange three separate areas for the reinforcements to settle in.

Moreover, Besmir has sent word that the Dwarves will be coming soon. He told the people to not provoke the Dwarves since their temperaments aren’t very good.

When this information spread in the city, the people immediately expressed their reaction. All of them had the same idea as Besmir. Although it was said that there was an alliance between the Humans and the other races in order to resist the Demons, a long time has passed without any reinforcements coming. This made the defenders think that this was just a rumor that was disseminated by the major empires of the continent. And at the same time, Zhao Hai’s presence here was only to calm their worries. They didn’t think that the other races would actually send some troops to help defend the city.

Zhao Hai didn’t care about these reactions. After Besmir arranged the living areas, he immediately took Berry to inspect them. When there weren’t any problems, Zhao Hai led Berry outside the city as he opened a spatial rift allowing the Dwarf passage towards Demon City.

The one who led the Dwarven Army was an elder, Zhao Hai believes that the name of this elder should be Julian. He was quite a young elder and his relationship with Zhao Hai was quite good.

When Julian came out of the rift, he bowed to Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, we have fifty thousand soldiers here as well as ten thousand iron beasts.”

After Zhao Hai returned the courtesy, he smiled and said, “Alright. Follow me, I’ll be taking you to your area.”

Julian nodded, then he turned around to give orders to the army. These people were the most outstanding soldiers of the Dwarven Race. All of them had their war hammers, full iron armor, and iron shield. Besides these, they also had a set of small hatchets for long-distance attacks.

Before long, the fifty thousand troops and ten thousand iron beasts are ready to move. Zhao Hai looked at them and said, “Brothers, we’ll be heading to the battle quite soon. This will be the first time that we will have a cooperation with the Humans after a long time. Don’t be surprised of their gazes, they are just curious. We’ll just shock them when the battle comes. Still, if people dared to laugh at you, then don’t punch them immediately, report the matter to me first and I shall deal with it myself!”

This was how Zhao Hai always talked to the Dwarves, so they were already quite used to it. When Zhao Hai finished talking, all of them issued a shout. Then they followed Zhao Hai to Demon City. While heading there, all of them were curiously looking around. Nobody could blame them, after all, they had been inside Dwarf Mountain for a very long time. It wouldn’t be strange if they were to be interested in this new place.

Before long, the large unit approached Demon City. When the soldiers in the city spotted Zhao Hai’s group, they didn’t move and just stood there because of the instruction that they had just received. However, all of them couldn’t help but stretch their necks in curiosity. On the other hand, the adventurers weren’t very disciplined and just went towards the walls and looked at the Dwarves. But nobody dared to say a word, all of them knew about the temperament of the Dwarves as well as Zhao Hai’s orders. If they dared to say anything, then Zhao Hai definitely wouldn’t let them off.

In fact, these adventurers were extremely afraid of Zhao Hai. He was known to be very vicious and merciless, turning several hundred thousand Aksu Empire soldiers into undead in a single night. This was something that cannot be simply forgotten.

Therefore, these adventurers just looked at the Dwarves without making a single noise nor gesture. Zhao Hai was very satisfied with this result. He quickly brought the Dwarves to their area before taking Julian to see Besmir. After all, it was impossible for Zhao Hai to be here all the time, so Julian and Besmir needed to be acquainted to each other for future cooperation.

When Zhao Hai took Julian to the General’s residence, Besmir immediately gave them a cordial welcome. Besmir looked at Julian with curiosity while Zhao Hai gave Besmir a salute and said, “General, let me introduce you to the Dwarven Elder Julian. Julian, this is General Besmir, Buddha Empire’s general for Demon City’s defense army.”

Julian and Besmir gave each other a salute, then Zhao Hai said, “Alright, then let’s head in.” After that, the three of them went inside the General’s residence.

Inside the residence, there was a large topographic map of Demon City. Zhao Hai went towards the map and pointed at something and said, “We’re here in Demon City in order to defend against the Demon advance. At this time, the Demons are still busying themselves by building their city. However, I believe that they have their own mages, so it wouldn’t take too long before they finish. When the city gets built, I believe that God-ranked experts of the Demon Realm will start to make a move. Although they are suppressed by the Ark Continent and cannot stay here for too long, they can still pose a threat to our position. Now that the Dwarves have come, I have one request for you to do. We need tunnels going from the city towards an area outside of it, we need them as soon as possible. They should be deep and large enough for our purpose of using them as our escape passage. Julian, what do you think?” Julian nodded and said, “This is not a problem, leave it to us.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he turned to Besmir and said, “You coordinate with the Dwarves, this is something important for us. If a God-ranked expert comes, we can use that tunnel in order to escape.”

Besmir nodded, “Mister, you can feel relieved. I know what to do, there’s no need to worry about it.” Zhao Hai nodded, then he turned his head back to Julian and said, “Julian, you should restrain the tempers of the Dwarves as well. We need a harmonious environment in this alliance. If we have some fights, then it would be disadvantageous for us in the future.”

Julian nodded, “I understand. We came this time to wage war with the Demons, not with the Humans Race.” Zhao hai nodded, then he looked at Besmir and said, “General, restrain the mercenaries and adventurers as well. Don’t make them go too far. If they do, then there would be no need to wait for the Dwarves to retaliate, I will do the job for them.”

Besmir nodded, he knew the importance of the current matter. The entire continent needed to be unified right now. If these fellows were to go too far, then Zhao Hai certainly wouldn’t let them off.

Zhao Hai looked at the two and said, “The Dwarf tunnel must be made as secretly as possible. We want the entrance to be well hidden, even to our own people. With this, we can also use those tunnels in order to stage a counter-attack.”

Julian nodded, “I understand. Don’t worry, we know what to do.”

Zhao Hao nodded, “Then that’s good.  Julian, you go back and take a rest first. You can start working tomorrow. I still need to go out of the city to take a look at things. General, make the soldiers pay more attention. In the next few days, the Elves will be arriving, extreme discipline will be needed in order to peacefully cooperate with them.”

Besmir nodded and said, “Alright, mister doesn’t need to worry about it.”

Zhao Hai nods, then the looked at Julian and said, “Let’s go. After I take you back, I’ll be leaving some liquor for your men as well. Let them enjoy their stay here in the meantime.”

Julian laughed and replied, “That would be good. We didn’t bring any liquor this time, we’re expecting that you would provide for us.” Zhao Hai laughed as well as he led Julian out of the General’s residence.

While Besmir looked at Zhao Hai and Julian’s backs, he finally understood how Zhao Hai could have a good relationship with the other races. This was because Zhao Hai didn’t treat them as another race, his treatment of them wasn’t different from his treatment towards the Humans. It was this easy.

However, even if this was easy to do, only a few can manage to do it. The Humans of the continent were too used to feeling superior. They have always looked down at the other races. This made the other races dislike them in turn. In the end, nobody liked anybody, making it impossible for them to cooperate.

Besmir sighed, then he turned around and went back to his room. To be honest, he was also  looking down on the other races, but Zhao Hai woke him up. The situation was now very different, they couldn’t just look down on different races anymore.

When Zhao Hai escorted Julian to his camp, he also left behind a lot of liquor. As for the other necessities, there was no need to worry about them, Besmir already prepared it for the Dwarves. This made Zhao Hai commend Besmir deep inside.

Zhao Hai looked at the busy Demons in the distance and couldn’t help but sigh. He really wanted to call all of his undead and then kill them directly. However, Zhao Hai knew that this wasn’t going to work. It was for certain that experts were already stationed there. Although Zhao Hai can overwhelm them with his undead, he also knew that the Demons were surely prepared. If Zhao Hai attacked them, then he would certainly suffer huge losses in the long run.

Moreover, Zhao Hai had some suspicions that the God-ranked experts had already arrived. It was only because of the current construction that the God-ranked experts decided to stay put.

The reason why Zhao Hai had this idea was because of a certain person, and this was none other than the Demon Dragon King. The information that Cai’er was able to get about the Demon Dragon King was too small. In fact, there wasn’t much information that Cai’er can get regarding the God-ranked experts of the Demon Realm. These God-ranked experts were very well-hidden.

And this Demon Dragon King was quite a low-key expert as well. And since Cai’er was unable to find out what his strength was, Zhao Hai believed that the Demon Dragon King was a God-ranked expert himself!

Chapter 700: Consummate the Marriage

Although Zhao Hai hadn’t fought with the Demon Dragon king, he just had this feeling that the other party was a God-ranked expert. He can’t really describe this feeling, but it was there, this was also the reason why Zhao Hai didn’t act rashly.

On the other hand, Zhao Hai also believed that the Demon Dragon King had sensed his strength. Therefore, he wasn’t quick to advance and just stayed to construct their city. It seems like both sides are dreading the ability of the other.

If the other party just had the Demon Dragon King as the God-ranked expert, then Zhao Hai wouldn’t be polite and just attacked them. But now it seems like the enemy doesn’t have the Demon Dragon King as its only God-ranked expert. Zhao Hai has the feeling that there were at least five God-ranked experts in the enemy’s army. If he dared to attack, then he might be besieged by those God-ranked experts. However, even if Zhao Hai didn’t attack, those five God-ranked experts can just make a move on Demon City. If they did it this way, then Zhao Hai’s prior preparations might be placed in a precarious position.

As to why the other party didn’t attack, Zhao Hai was not sure. Maybe they still aren’t adapted to the Ark Continent? Who knows.

In fact, Zhao Hai was correct in his guess, these experts still needed to familiarize themselves with the Ark Continent, this was the reason why they decided to refrain from making any actions in the meantime.

The Ark Continent had its own laws, one of them forbade the long-term existence of God-ranked experts. The suppression of this law gets more powerful as the violating party gets stronger. Therefore, these God-ranked Demons needed to adapt their strength in order to perform at their full strength.

Because of this, in addition to Zhao Hai’s existence as well as his undead, the Demon Dragon King decided to stay back and refrain from attacking Demon City immediately.

Berry was currently right by Zhao Hai, at this moment, she turned to him and said, “Brother Hai, there’s no need to worry too much. Although there are a lot of Demons that would come to invade, it would still need some time before all of them manages to come out of the spatial rift. I’ve gotten a whiff of their plans before. They would have several God-ranked experts take command of the vanguard in order to construct their city, after that, they would proceed to attack the Ark Continent bit by bit.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I was thinking the same thing. But how many God-ranked experts do they have? And since they have God-ranked experts, why haven’t they made an attack yet?”

Berry smiled and said, “Things aren’t as easy as that. Although they are God-ranked experts, I heard that they would still need to adapt after arriving at the Ark Continent. Otherwise, they wouldn’t be able to show their full strength. And the time it takes for them to adapt isn’t short. Therefore, it would still take quite some time before they can express their full abilities. We can definitely resist them for a long time.”

Zhao Hai frowned and said, “I’m afraid that the Demon Realm would have a lot of God-ranked experts. If all of them were to arrive at the Ark Continent, then we would be in deep trouble.”

When Berry heard this, she couldn’t help but frown as well, “This is also an issue. I know that there are quite a number of God-ranked experts in the Demon Realm. If they attack, then it would indeed be very troublesome.”

Zhao Hai sighed, then he said, “It looks like we need to start our plan soon. There are a lot of herbs in the Space, but the herbs that we need to make a God-ranked potion is really a lot. At the same time, the growth time of those plants is too long. Our rate of making God-ranked potions is just too low.”

Zhao Hai was quick to discover that the Processing Machine was now able to make God-ranked potions. At that time, he also noted which herbs were needed and planted them. However, he didn’t think about how many were needed to make a single potion.

It was only afterwards that Zhao Hai discovered how much herbs he needed to promote a 9th rank to God-rank. Also, the herbs that were needed to make the potion were very demanding. Take a certain ginseng, for example. In the past, Zhao Hai was able to plant ginseng in a very simple manner, and he was also able to harvest them in large quantities. But now, the ginseng needed for the potion required a hundred mu of farming ground. And in this 100 mu, no other plant must be present in order for this special ginseng to grow. And after this ginseng gets planted, extreme attention needed to be made in order to nurture it. It needed to be watered in a specific time or else the land would get dry. Although the ginseng still wouldn’t die then, but it would lose its potency to be used for the God-ranked potion. This made it hard to cultivate this herb.

More importantly, the God-ranked potion didn’t need one or two of this ginseng, but instead it needed 81. And this was only the ginseng, the other herbs still weren’t calculated.

If one wanted to make the potion, then one would need to grow more than 100 herbs. Each of then unique and each of them needed special ways of growing. Some of these were present on Earth, while some have already been acquired by Zhao Hai, like the Goldmetal fruit. And the amount of Goldmetal Fruit needed was actually more than the ginseng.

Because of all these limitations, Zhao Hai was still unable to make Green and the others into God-ranked experts. With the materials he currently had, Zhao Hai only has enough to make a single God-ranked potion.

Therefore, for Zhao Hai, what he needed the most at this moment was time. As long as he has enough time, then he would be able to raise a lot of God-ranked experts. And when that time comes, whether they be Demons or the Divine Race, all of them weren’t going to be problems anymore.

Another reason why Zhao Hai was unwilling to fight the Demons was the existence of the Divine Race. The Radiant Empire has become more and more mysterious as the days passed. And since Zhao Hai couldn’t go there to scout, he was getting more and more anxious as time goes by.

When the Divine Race comes, Zhao Hai didn’t know what plans they would have. Therefore, Zhao Hai decided to refrain from going all out against the Demons. He was afraid that if he lost too much in fighting the Demons, then he wouldn’t have anything to resist the Divine Race with.

Although Zhao Hai hoped that the Divine Race would divert the Demons’ attention, it seems like there weren’t any movements coming from the Divine Race. This gave Zhao Hai a sense of dread. This was why Zhao Hai thought of making the Buddha Empire into a huge battlefield. Not only would it help in fighting the Demons, it would also prove useful when the Radiant Empire attacks.

When Berry heard Zhao Hai mention the promotion of 9th ranks into God-ranked experts, she was immediately startled, she seemed to have remembered something. Berry looked embarrassingly at Zhao Hai and said with a shy voice, “Brother Hai, I’m a 9th rank Succubus. When a Succubus consummates her marriage, she will gain a huge boost in her strength.”

Berry was blushing as she stared downward. Zhao Hai looked at Berry and immediately understood what she wanted to convey.

Berry was a 9th rank expert, if her marriage goes official, then her strength would gain a huge promotion, it might even be possible for her to advance to God-rank. When he thought of this Zhao Hai’s eyes couldn’t help but shine.

As for consummating the marriage, Zhao Hai was quick to understand what it was. Although Berry had become Zhao Hai’s wife and had people recognize her status, the two of them had yet to make the marriage ‘official’. In other words, they haven’t done what married people tended to do.[1]

Zhao Hai looked at Berry and said, “Are you sure?”

Berry gave a shy nod. This made Zhao Hai laugh and said, “Then what are we waiting for, let’s go.” Then he pulled Berry as they flashed to the Space. However, he didn’t go through the villa’s entrance but instead appeared directly inside his room.

Berry knew what would happen so she didn’t have any intentions to resist. She just lowered her head in embarrassment, making her much more charming for Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai held Berry’s hand as he said, “Berry, I apologize. The situation is quite hectic and I am not able to hold a wedding for you.”

Berry looked at Zhao Hai as she shook her head and said, “You didn’t do anything wrong, Brother Hai. I don’t really care about a ceremony. As long as you treat me as your wife, then that would already suffice.”

Zhao Hai patted Berry’s head and whispered, “Silly girl.” Zhao Hai pulled Berry into his bosom as he gently kissed her forehead. Berry gently closed her eyes as Zhao Hai went down to kiss her eyes, her nose, her cheek, her neck……”

When Berry felt Zhao Hai’s lips on her own, she couldn’t help but feel an electric current going through her whole body. Her body tingled with numbness, sapping all of her energy away.

Zhao Hai gently removed Berry’s clothes as he proceeded to kiss her whole body. In the end his mouth reached Berry’s sensitive breasts, he continue to tease it until Berry made a delighted moan.

Zhao Hai didn’t expect Berry to taste this good, he was unable to stop himself. He couldn’t help but nib lightly on the tip as Berry gave a tender sound, arousing Zhao Hai even more.

Zhao Hai’s tongue explored Berry’s peaks for a moment before he went and kissed Berry lips. Berry curled her tongue as she met Zhao Hai’s lips, the two of them played around before Zhao Hai removed all of his clothes and started to work on Berry’s figure.

* * *

( ͡° ͜ʖ ͡°)

Chapter 701: Who To Promote First?

While Zhao Hai and Berry united their marriage, Zhao Hai suddenly felt a huge suction force that was unexpectedly coming from Berry. Although Zhao Hai was not affected too much by it, he also discovered that it was already impossible for him to withdraw.

When he felt that his body’s energy was almost absorbed, a sudden force suddenly rushed into him. This force was very powerful, and it was quite warm as well. Once it entered Zhao Hai’s body, it slowly integrated into him. Zhao Hai discovered that this strength was even stronger than what was absorbed, and it seemed to be purer than before.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but make a surprised expression at Berry. Betry currently had her eyes closed while her hair was slowly waving around on its own. Then suddenly, Berry’s eyes emitted a strong glare, making Zhao Hai close his eyes immediately. When he opened his eyes, Zhao Hai was quick to notice crystal on Berry’s forehead. The crystal looks like a kind of diamond, it was radiating blue light, it was beautiful.

Without knowing, Zhao Hai suddenly kissed the crystal. This action made Berry’s body tremble lightly. When Berry’s eyes recovered, she looked at Zhao Hai in a much more charming gaze.

Zhao Hai kissed the crystal again, eliciting another reaction from Berry. Zhao Hai was elated to find this new toy to play around with. He teased the crystal constantly as Berry made moans again and again. It didn’t take too long for another round of ‘playtime’ began.

At this point, Zhao Hai was currently on the bed with Berry lying on his chest, breathing heavily. She looked up at Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, I’ve really became God-rank.”

Zhao Hai chuckled and said, “I know. I really didn’t think that your Succubus Race would have such an astonishing ability. It’s quite amazing.”

Berry made a charming pout as she said, “How could it be that easy? Although our race has a rule of marrying anyone who resisted our mental attack, complying with the rule and accepting it are two different matters. If we felt compelled to marry the other person because of the rule, even if we can still get stronger, the boost wouldn’t be that much. On the other hand, if we are really willing to marry the other party, then the improvement that we get would be extremely large.”

When he heard Berry, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile and said, “So you’re saying that you really are sincere in marrying me? Hahaha. It seems like I’m quite the attractive man.”

Berry couldn’t help but lightly hit Zhao Hai. At this point, Zhao Hai suddenly turned over and carried Berry’s body, much to the latter’s surprise. Then Zhao hai smiled faintly and said, “Let’s go take a bath.” Then he continued to carry Berry towards the bathroom.

Each room in the villa had its own bathroom, in addition to the communal one in the basement. Moreover, the individual bathrooms weren’t small. Inside them were huge bathtubs filled with water from the hot spring.

After the two had taken their bath, they returned to the bed and had a good rest. As soon as they woke up, Zhao Hai and Berry put their clothes on before going out into the living room. Upon arriving there, the two of them saw Lizzy and the others looking at Demon City’s situation in the monitor.

When the group saw Zhao Hai and Berry coming out of the room, they looked at each other with sly expressions. Megan even examined Berry’s skin as she said, “Congratulations, Sister Berry. It seems like you have been promoted to God-rank.”

Berry’s face went red as she faced Megan, she kept her head down and was too embarrassed to talk. Megan looked at Berry and couldn’t help but chuckle, “Sister Berry, there’s no need to be shy. After all, all of us are Brother Hai’s wives. It’s fine.”

Zhao Hai turned to the nearby dim-faced Ruyen, then he smiled faintly and said, “That’s good. Now, how is the outside situation been? Did something happen?” Then he proceeded to the center of the living room and sat beside Ruyen.

Ruyen couldn’t help but stare at Zhao Hai, then her complexion turned red as she lowered her head down. At this time, Lizzy turned to Zhao Hai and smiled, “There’s no significant development. The Demons are still building their city. On the other hand, the Dwarves are truly formidable. They had already made a tunnel and had concealed its entrance. One couldn’t just spot it without proper guidance.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and replied, “They had been doing this for many years, so its natural that they are very skilled in this aspect. The only thing that is left to do is to resist the Demons. Also, we need to take a look at how the Divine Race responds.”

Lizzy frowned as she said, “There aren’t any actions from the Divine Race’s side. Who knows what wicked plots they are currently making. Big Brother Hai, how much people do you think the Divine Race would send down?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “I can’t really say. However, I’m quite sure that they’ll be sending God-ranked experts. They already have experience in sending one to the Ark Continent, therefore, they should have already developed ways in order to make them stay for a longer period of time.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Lizzy’s expression turned worse, with a troubled voice she replied, “If that really happens, then we would be facing hard times ahead.”

Zhao Hai nodded, but he still smiled and said, “I don’t think our troubles would be that heavy. Don’t forget, the Demons had appeared too suddenly. Therefore, it shouldn’t be only us who were caught off-guard, the Divine Race should be in the same situation as well. They were only planning to deal with us, but now that the Demons have appeared, I’m quite sure that they just wouldn’t ignore it. After all, the combat prowess of the Demons isn’t something that can just be ignored. For us, the sooner the Divine Race appeared, the better.”

Lizzy sighed and said, “I sure hope so.”

At this time, footsteps can be heard before Laura, Meg, and Ni’er appeared. It was evident on their faces that they were tired and weary. Zhao Hai quickly stood up as he approached them and said, “How have you been doing? Are you tired? If so, then don’t hesitate to take a rest. You shouldn’t overexert yourselves.”

Laura smiled and said, “We’re fine. You don’t need to worry about us. Right, what were you talking about?”

After having the three sit down, Zhao Hai answered, “We were just talking about the Divine Race. There aren’t any movements that can be seen from their side. We suspect that they might be waiting for us and the Demons to give each other some mutual wounds. However, i reckon that if we manage to hold the Demons off long enough inside the Buddha Empire, then they might change their sights towards the Radiant Church. At that time, the Divine Race would be compelled to make a move.”

Laura nodded, then she said, “In fact, there’s another way. If the Demons really don’t intend to go to the Radiant Church, then we can just attack the Radiant Church ourselves. I think the Divine Race would similarly be pushed to take action.”

Zhao Hai stared, he had overlooked this point. His eyes couldn’t help but shine at Laura’s suggestion as he said, “Right, right, that’s a good idea. If the Divine Race really wants to wait, then we’ll take the fight to them.”

Then he looked at Laura and said, “Alright, you don’t need to worry about these matters anymore, you go take a nice bath and rest. Meg, Ni’er, you do the same as well. There wouldn’t be to much actions in the following days, so you can just relax yourselves.”

The three nodded with a smile, then they turned around to leave. After seeing them leave, Zhao Hai turned his gaze towards the monitor. There really weren’t any significant events happening right now, everybody was conserving their strengths, the undead were just like statues as they stood motionless on the field.

Zhao Hai sighed, then he turned his head to Lizzy and the others, “You take a rest as well. I’ll be heading back to Demon City to catch up on the Dwarves. Also, it seems like the Elves would be coming soon, I’ll be needed in greeting them into Demon City.”

Lizzy nodded, then she looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, you must be very careful. I’m afraid the experts of the Demon Race wouldn’t just let you off so easily. After being in contact with you for twice now, I reckon that they already have a vague idea of your abilities and methods. They will surely use that against you in the future.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Rest assured, there won’t be any problems. After all, Berry is with me, and she is a God-rank expert as well. With two God-ranked experts, I think there won’t be a lot of things that would place us in a dangerous position. Right, I have one last thing to discuss. At this moment, the plants in the Space can only promote a single person into God-rank. Who do you think we should promote first?”

Lizzy thought for a moment before she said, “Shue, Brother Hai, Shue should be the first one to be God-rank. Don’t forget, Shue is a Divergent Ability user. If his clones can have God-ranked strength, then it would be a huge benefit for our fights in the future.”

Zhao Hai stared, then he quickly remembered that Shue was indeed a divergent ability user. If he rose to God-rank, then wouldn’t his clones be God-ranked as well? If his clones do indeed become God-rank, then they wouldn’t need to fear anyone in the future. Also, if his clones can’t be promoted, then at the very least they would be the most outstanding 9th ranks in the field, they shouldn’t be vastly weaker than general God-ranked experts.”

After thinking about it, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but repeatedly nod as he said, “Right, Shue is indeed a good choice. That fellow has been very busy in the Black Wasteland, it seems like its time to bring him back to the Space.”

Lizzy smiled and said, “It’s true that the Black Wasteland was too busy before, but now, most things have already been taken care of. It should be fine to have him exit for a short while. I’ll have Cai’er inform him later and have his tasks handed over to someone else.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “The Black Wasteland has indeed been very busy. After all, settling massive amounts of people isn’t that easy. However, our people are already well coordinated. Moreover, the commodities have already been prepared, so settling people shouldn’t take too much time. Also, Blockhead and Rockhead are there as well as our first batch of slaves, they should be able to manage things properly. It shouldn’t be a huge issue if Shue were to leave. ”

Lizzy nodded, then she stood up and said, “Brother Hai, let’s first make that potion and then have Cai’er call Shue over. It would be good if we take care of this matter as soon as possible.”

Chapter 702: Elves in Flower City

When Zhao Hai and the others arrived at the Processing Machine, Cai’er was already waiting for them. Moreover, she already got the herbs and placed them on the side of the machine.

Zhao Hai looked at the pile of material’s on the ground, ginsengs, crow’s heart, snow lotus, goldmetal fruit, and a lot more were present. Moreover, one could clearly see how expensive the potion must be judging from how much precious things it needed. When he saw this, Zhao Hao couldn’t help but sigh. All of this just to make one potion, it really was a very hard to make product.

Although Zhao Hai lamented about this fact, he still turned to Cai’er and said, “Start it.” Cai’er nodded and then pressed the buttons on the Processing Machine. The Processing Machine suddenly flashed a bright light on the pile of herbs on the ground, absorbing them one by one.

When all of the herbs had vanished, the Space immediately issued a prompt, “Strengthening Potion being processed. Estimated time, 48 hours. 1 million gold has been deducted. Please wait patiently for the product to finish.”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but force a smile at this. The Space really was a drain of money. Even if it works for him, it still deducted 1 million coins to his inventory.

Cai’er looked at Zhao Hai and couldn’t help but chuckle, “Young Master, you don’t need to worry. When the Space gets upgraded to a certain level, the Processing Machine wouldn’t need gold to operate anymore.” Zhao Hai bitterly smiled and said, “Still, we need to wait for that day. Who knows, maybe I will go broke even before we reach that point.”

Lizzy and the others chuckled, all of them knew that Zhao Hai was just cracking a joke. Although the Processing Machine had indeed taken a lot of money, Lizzy and the others knew that Zhao Hai wouldn’t run out of money. With the produce that the Space provides everyday, money would certainly be the last of their problems. And even if they can’t sell it to the continent, Zhao Hai can still sell them off to the Space. Although the Space buys them at a lower price, it was still at an understandable rate. When Lizzy and the other first saw this happen, they were very startled. If Zhao Hai were to introduce these gold coins to the continent, then he would certainly give ruin to the running economy of the world. Fortunately, Zhao Hai wanted to be low-key, he didn’t like to go too far in acquiring and introducing gold to the continent.

Forty-eight hours, it would take two days before the potion gets made. Although Zhao Hai was somewhat disappointed that he couldn’t see the potion today, he didn’t say anything and just led the group back to the villa.

On the other hand, even though Shue got word from Zhao Hai, it was still impossible for him to hand over his work to someone else in such a short period of time. After all, there were too many people currently living in the Black Wasteland.

The Elves and the Dwarves have already reached the Buddha Family’s land. Zhao Hai had also given them a place to settle in. There was no need to mention the Dwarves, they were now temporarily living inside the camps. However, they have started to dig inside Iron Mountain to see if there were iron deposits still left. At the same time, they were also preparing the caverns inside the mountain since they were used to the living environment there.

On the other hand, the Elves were much more troublesome to settle in. They were too familiar to the life inside the Tree of Life, and it was impossible for the Black Wasteland to have a tree of that size. And compared to the temperate forest, the Black Wasteland would have freezing winters, at the same time, it was impossible for the Elves to live inside Iron Mountain.

Therefore, Zhao Hai made a special plan to give them a place to which they can plant trees in. This way, they would find their settlement more comfortable to live in.

Although the Black Wasteland is big, it was impossible for it to have places like the Dwarf Mountain and the Elven Forest. Because of this, Zhao Hai still had problems in finding places appropriate for the Elves to plant their trees.

In the end, the plan was stopped since way too many people had started to stream into the Black Wasteland. Since Zhao Hai didn’t have a means to arrange a proper place for the Elves, he decided to just place them in Flower City, making them live their isolated lives once more.

Flower City was quite big, and because it was in the Carrion Swamp it was very isolated from the others. This gave the Elves a feeling of security. However, it was still impossible for the city to accommodate all of the Elves. In the end, Zhao Hai had to ask Cai’er to expand the city so that the Elves can move in.

This was only a temporary arrangement, it was impossible for Zhao Hai to make them live for too long in this place. After all, Flower City was once interlinked with a spatial rift to the Demon Realm. Zhao Hai couldn’t have people living in this place.

However, the Elves loved Flower City. Although they had a change of environment, flowers and vines were present everywhere in the place. Moreover, they also didn’t need to worry about food because Zhao Hai would be bringing it to them. Because of this, it took a very short time for the Elves to get settled in.

But even so, the Elves were still quite restless. After having lived in Flower City, they discovered that they had nothing else to do. They cannot just eat and sleep everyday, that was something that pigs did. Therefore, they proposed an idea to Zhao Hai, they wanted to plant trees in the Carrion Swamp.

Zhao Hai didn’t have a choice but to comply. He went to the Elf Queen and told her about this matter. The Queen immediately agreed and had prepared some seedlings to be sent over. These seedlings were the ones most commonly used by the Elves.

Now that the Elves had started to plant trees near Flower City, Zhao Hai stopped thinking about them. He decided to let them be, this was also allow them to cultivate their strength.

Although the magic beasts of the carrion swamp didn’t disturb the Black Wasteland anymore, Zhao Hai has yet to subdue them. It wasn’t because he didn’t have the capability, but because he just didn’t want to, he wanted the beasts to live in the swamp quite freely. Now that the Elves have occupied Flower City, it was inevitable for them to get attacked. Whenever the Elves go out into the outskirts of their settlement, there was a high probability for them to meet these magic beasts. Although the magic beasts didn’t dare to enter the city, they were still able to roam around due to the absence of 9th ranks.

Zhao Hai already told the Elves about this matter when they decided to plant trees. However, the Elves didn’t care much about it. They were already used to being attacked by the magic beasts in the Elven Forest, being attacked by magic beasts now wouldn’t be much of an issue.

Because of this and many other matters, Shue needed to lend Green and the others a hand. Extracting himself from these tasks couldn’t be done in a short time.

Since the Processing Machine needed two days to make the potion, Zhao Hai decided to have Shue continue with what he was doing in this period of time. Also, it seems like the Demons would still need some time to prepare their attack. At this moment, Zhao Hai had nothing to do, he was totally free.

After taking care of the Processing Machine, Zhao Hai made Lizzy and the others rest. Then he led Berry out of the Space to visit the Dwarf camp.

Although the Dwarves were tasked to make tunnels, these tunnels don’t need too much manpower to make. At most, the operation would need a commanding Dwarf while most of the work was done by the iron beasts. Because of this, a lot of people were still present inside the camp.

Zhao Hai went to the camp and saw the Dwarves practicing their fighting techniques. Meanwhile, outside the camp were a lot of curious adventurers. They were looking at the camp in order to see the Dwarves. However, because of the order, they didn’t dare to go in. At the same time, the Dwarves were too preoccupied to care about them.

When Zhao Hai arrived at the camp, the Dwarves immediately took notice of him. Two Dwarves went forward to greet Zhao Hai as they bowed and said, “Elder, you came”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he looked at the two and said, “Where’s Elder Julian?”

One of the Dwarves answered, “Elder Julian is currently taking charge in making the tunnels. Do you want us to call him over?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I’ll have to trouble you then. Tell him I came with liquor to drink.” The Dwarves nodded as one of them turned around and ran.

Zhao Hai entered the Dwarf camp with a happy mood. Although the area of the Dwarf camp has been made private, it wasn’t fenced off or walled in. It was only the Humans who didn’t dare come here because of Besmir’s strict order.

The remaining Dwarf led Zhao Hai to the place where Julian lived before he retreated. Zhao Hao looked around the place and muttered, “This is quite a small courtyard.” It was relatively independent, but it wasn’t just Julian who was living here. There were a lot of Dwarves inside, all of them busy with what they were doing that none of them took the chance to approach and talk to Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai couldn’t blame them, he knew that this was just the Dwarves being Dwarves. It doesn’t matter who came, as long as the Dwarves were busy, they will not come and greet that person, even if it was the Patriarch.

Not long after Zhao Hai reached the courtyard, a laugh was suddenly heard, “Mister, how did you have the time to ask me for a drink?

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I had nothing to do, so I came to drink a cup. But also, I was waiting for the Elves to arrive. I think it wouldn’t be long before we can see them on the horizon.”

Julian smiled and said, “But still, they can’t be as fast as us. I must say, your Space Divergent ability is really something. For you to be able to take us from the Dwarf Mountain to Demon City in such a short time is extremely astonishing. It’s quite nice to be able to travel a thousand kilometers in just a single step.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “It’s quite good. In a few days, I’ll be taking the Beastmen from the Prairie to here. When that time comes, Demon City would become more lively.”

Julian smiled and said, “The Dwarves and the Beastmen had broken our relationship for a long time. It would be great to see our Beastman brothers once more.” The Beastmen and the Dwarves have quite similar temperaments. Because of this, their relationship in the past was quite good. However, when the Humans started to suppress the other races, the Dwarves drew back to their Mountain while the Beastmen returned to the Prairie. This broke contact between the two races. Being able to meet again in Demon City made Julian quite glad.

While Zhao Hai was preparing to drink with Julian, a Dwarf suddenly came knocking at the door, “Elder Julian, Elder Zhao Hai, there’s a Human outside. He said that a flying group can be seen outside the city. It’s possible that the Elves have arrived. They are asking Elder Zhao Hai to go and assist in meeting them.”

Chapter 703: Threat

Zhao Hai stood up and turned to Julian before saying, “It would be nice to have a drink with you. But it seems like I don’t have the opportunity to do it this time. Sigh. To be honest, I really don’t like to deal with the Elves. Although they are good fighters, they are a bit too proud. However, since they are also a member of the Ark Continent, we can’t just leave them behind.”

The reason why Zhao Hai dared to tell Julian about this was because he knew that after the previous debacle, the Elves weren’t exactly in good graces with the Dwarves.

Although Billy knew that the attitude that the Great Elder and the Prince showed him was due to them being people from the Radiant Church, Billy was also aware that the Elves were truly looking down on the Dwarves. This fact made Billy quite angry.

And after Billy returned to the Dwarf Mountain, he told everyone about this matter. With the Dwarf Race’s disposition, they just wouldn’t let this offense go lightly. Therefore, the Dwarves didn’t have a good impression with the Elves from then on. It was only because of the Demons that the Dwarves chose to refrain from acting on the Elves.

The Dwarves have the capital to do so. After all, they have a lot of opportunities to get in touch with the Humans. Their weapons were very popular for Human armies, this made it possible for them to acquire Human goods as trade. Among the other races, the Dwarves has been faring the best.

The Elves’ arrogance ran through their bones, and it was a completely incomprehensible attitude. One should know that before the Dwarves came, the Elves were living quite terrible lives. Only after they got in contact with the Dwarves and managed to sell some of their artworks off that they began to live comfortably. For the Elves to still look down on the Dwarves after all of this was something that Billy and the others were unable to bear. But since the Elves were quite important to the alliance, the Dwarves didn’t dare to make any moves. However, the gap was already there.

Because of this, Zhao Hai can feel relieved when expressing such bold words regarding the Elves in front of the Dwarves. Not only will it be fine, the statement might even make Zhao Hai look better in the eyes of the Dwarves.

When Julian heard Zhao Hai, he couldn’t help but laugh and said, “Alright, but you still need to see those guys. I just can’t understand why the Elves are arrogant towards the Dwarves. It’s very strange.”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but laugh as well, “It’s quite strange indeed. Alright, Julian, I’ll have a drink with you when I have some time.”

Julian nodded and said, “Alright, then I’ll wait for you.” Zhao Hai waved to Julian one last time before turning around to leave.

Outside the Dwarf camp was a Human soldier. When that soldier saw Zhao Hai come out, he immediately went forward and gave Zhao Hai a salute, “Mister, the guards on the western walls saw some flying beings in the distance. We hope that you can come and look at it.” Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright, let’s go and take a look.” Then he summoned the Bone Dragon and captured the soldier before shooting up into the sky.

The soldier became a little excited, he was shaking when he was standing on top of the Bone Dragon. After all, this was the first time that he flew into the sky. And for him to do it on the head of a Bone Dragon was a truly exhilarating experience.

Before long, Zhao Hai’s Bone Dragon arrived at the western walls of the city. The Bone Dragon descended slowly before Zhao Hai had the soldier go down. After that, Zhao Hai looked into the horizon to see what was going on.

The plain white sky was currently dotted by some black spots. And presently, Zhao Hai was getting information that those black spots were red lights on the monitor. This assured Zhao Hai that the people in the distance were the Elves.

Zhao Hai immediately stood on the back of the Bone Dragon as it flew towards the sky in order meet the approaching party. Before long, the the black spots got closer and closer. Then Zhao Hai can finally make out a silhouette of Elves on top of some flying beasts. Majority of the Elves were archers, only a few of them were Mages. And it seems like it was the Mages that were taking the lead.

Zhao Hai had also spotted an acquaintance among the group, it was Gellar, the Elven Race’s princess. Zhao Hai didn’t expect her to be the one leading this group. Zhao Hai turned his Bone Dragon around and went side to side with Gellar’s mount. Zhao Hai turned his head and said, “Captain Gellar, welcome. Please follow me.” Then Zhao Hai flew towards a part of the city where the Elves were supposed to live in. Besmir personally inspected the cleanliness of the place. It was even much cleaner than the residences for the Dwarves and the Beastmen.

Gellar hadn’t had a chance to say anything as she gave a command to her people to follow Zhao Hai towards Demon City. This time, most of the archers that came with Gellar were harp users, they numbered about 5 thousand. Zhao Hai and Besmir had arranged to have them stay in the richer parts of the city, where the environment was relatively better.

After Gellar and the others had disembarked, Zhao Hai led them to get familiar with their residences. Zhao Hai turned to Gellar and said, “Captain, this place shall be your area inside Demon City. Rest assured, I’ve already sent an order to have the Humans refrain from coming here. If one disobeyed the order and still came here, then your people would be fit to judge them. Everything that you will need has already been prepared. If there’s anything else that you require, then you can send someone to approach me or send it through the General. Speaking of which, Captain Gellar, come with me to meet the General of the Demon City’s army.”

Gellar nodded and said, “Alright, Elder, please lead the way.” Zhao Hai gave a nod before he led Gellar as well as two harp archers towards the center of Demon City. Zhao Hai didn’t mind the guards too much. After all, Gellar was the princess of the Elven race.

The arrival of the Elves elicited more of a response compared to the Dwarves’ arrival. This was the Elves, titled as the most beautiful race in the entire Ark Continent. The entire city caused a stir, mercenaries, adventurers, and soldiers alike were filling the roads.

When these people saw Gellar’s appearance, each of their eyes turned red. Two mercenaries even dared to whistle, which were promptly made stiff by Zhao Hai’s pressuring gaze.

Gellar and the others weren’t familiar with all these attention. The three of them glared at the two people when Zhao Hai took action. The two guards were completely ready to kill, afraid that people might rush towards Gellar.

Zhao Hai didn’t care much about it. These mercenaries and adventurers in Demon city weren’t generally good people anyway. Majority of them came to offer their lives in exchange for money. To make their own and their family’s lives better, they disregarded life and death. Therefore, it made an environment of lawlessness inside the city.

At the same time, Zhao Hai also wanted to give them a warning. Elves were truly very attractive. If these fellows were to have bad thoughts, then they might even charge towards the Elven encampment to cause trouble. At this time, Zhao Hai stopped, Gellar and the other two Elves looked at him in confusion. Zhao Hai swept his gaze towards the mercenaries and adventurers as said with a threatening tone, “I don’t care about any of your backgrounds, however, I must tell you that the Elves, Dwarves, and the Beastmen are our allies. Allies that this Zhao Hai had invited. If anyone dares to be impolite to them, then I would personally make them regret their decision. Don’t think that since the world is going into turmoil, you would be able to do whatever you want. If you do any crimes inside Demon City, then even if you go to the ends of the continent, I will come to you and eliminate you. This Zhao Hai has always lived by his words. You better reign in any improper thoughts. Otherwise, I won’t mind adding more people into my undead army.” Then after giving a cold look to those present, Zhao Hai moved forward.

What Zhao Hai said about these people were in fact true. Among these people, a lot of them held criminal records. They have done crimes on other places, so they cannot stay in the continent for too long, this made them decide to run towards Demon City.

These fellows just became so bold after seeing how beautiful the Elves were. With how weak their minds were, the only thing that was on their mind was how much they would get if they can capture on Elf. One should know that even one Elf can garner enough gold coins that can make someone live in luxury for the rest of their lives. They believed that with the chaos in the continent, they can just run to another place and nobody would take the effort to arrest them.

However, Zhao Hai’s threat was actually effective. One could say that the people’s worst nightmare would be Dark Mages. From what they heard, Dark Mages were people who were able to take your soul out of your body and imprison it. Dark Mages can then use methods interrogate that soul and ask for the whereabouts of one’s family, who will then die to the hands of the Dark Mage.

Moreover, when one’s soul is imprisoned, it doesn’t mean that one would have control of their own being. In essence, an imprisoned soul could just helplessly stare as the Dark Mage proceeds to kill all of their loved ones. This was a kind of torture that nobody would be able to withstand.

Because of this, no matter what kind of person one was, they would always be afraid of Dark Mages. This was because Dark Mages were the quintessential ‘bad guys’ of the continent.

And with Zhao Hai being the strongest Dark Mage, his threat was the most ominous one. Although these people were lawless, they were still intelligent enough to not ignore Zhao Hai’s words.

After Zhao Hai issued his threat, the onlookers immediately behaved themselves. They didn’t dare to act unreasonable anymore. In the current Demon City, Zhao Hai undoubtedly held the most power. If they disregard Zhao Hai, then they wouldn’t even be aware how they died. Therefore, they had no other choice but to stay honest.

Zhao Hai brought Gellar’s group to the General’s residence and introduced them to Besmir. This time, the Elves were just present because they needed to experience the battlefield. Then at appropriate times, Zhao Hai would have them fight with the Demons. Zhao Hai didn’t really expect the Elves to have a large impact against the battle, after all, the number of Elves were just too small.

Chapter 704: The Elephant Race Arrives

After Gellar was briefed on their tasks, Zhao Hai immediately lead them back to their camp. However, he didn’t have enough time to be idle since it was time for him to meet the Elephant Beastmen.

One must say, the Beast King’s working efficiency is very high. It wasn’t a long time before Zhao Hai approached him but everything has already been prepared. Upon asking the Beast King, Zhao Hai knew that the Beast King didn’t have the Elephant Race head to Beast God City. Instead, he just had them gather in their main camp and wait there for Zhao Hai to pick them up. This saved a lot of time since the only thing that needed waiting was the hawk that delivered the letter.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but sigh when he heard the Beast King’s method. Then his body flashed and appeared in a place not far away from the Elephant Race’s main camp.

The Elephants had a very good reputation in the Prairie. But although their temperament was quite mild, they were really good fighters. They didn’t fear any race in the Prairie and the other races didn’t want to offend them either.

Ordinary Elephant Beastmen were much bigger than Humans. They have average heights of five meters while some of them can even reach six or seven meters high. The weapons that they are using were special and were divided into two types. They had maces for both hands, but they were much bigger than the ones usually used by the other Beastmen .They were sturdy weapons that seems to be made out of beast bone.

Their other weapon was actually a scimitar. This weapon wasn’t wielded by their hands, but instead by their noses. It was quite known that the nose of an Elephant was much more dextrous compared to their hands.

Like majority of maces, the Elephant Race’s maces pack a lot of thunderous power in each strike. On the other hand, their scimitars were quick and light, due to the control provided by their long trunks. With how their scimitars gracefully swing on the battlefield, the Elephant Race’s blade arts became quite famous in the continent.

When Zhao Hai arrived at the main camp, he saw a gathering of about twenty thousand Elephant Beastman Warriors and twenty thousand war elephants. This army can be used both as an infantry and as a cavalry. However, the Elephants were less lethal when riding their mounts. Their mounts weren’t really suited for high speed movements, which weakens the Elephant Race’s ability to charge the enemy. In the end, the Elephant cavalry can only be played around by their much nimble enemies.

On the other hand, their prowess as an infantry was different. Every single step the Elephants make, even if quite slow, gave off an intimidating aura, pressuring the creatures  they were up against. There wasn’t a lot that an army could do to withstand an Elephant infantry advance.

The war elephants of the Elephant Race weren’t suitable for being mounts. They weren’t fast beasts, however, they are quite heavy, this made it possible for these beasts to be used in wars as well.

When Zhao Hai flew his Bone Dragon towards the main camp of the Elephants, the 20 thousand warriors were already prepared to be deployed. At the same time, the tribe’s Patriarch was already there waiting for Zhao Hai.

The Royal Clan of the Elephant race was quite a famous group in the Prairie, they were the Silver Elephant Clan. Their skins were silver-white, some might even claim to see them radiate silver shine. Their skins were extremely defensive, and in addition to their monstrous strengths, they were quite the force among the Beastman Race.

Zhao Hai had his Bone Dragon land outside the main camp. When the Elephant Patriarch saw Zhao hai, he immediately went forward and bowed, “Elephant Race’s Patriarch Baht meets His Highness, Prince Zhao Hai.” Zhao Hai returned the courtesy and said, “Patriarch Baht is too polite. To be honest, I didn’t expect your race to get prepared this quickly.”

Baht smiled and said, “When I received His Majesty’s letter, this Baht didn’t dare to neglect it. After all, we Beastman have been longing to fight with the Demons for quite some time. I didn’t even expect that we would be the first ones to be deployed. This is really the luck of the Elephant Race. I already made the men gather around so that the Prince can take them away at any time.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he glanced at the Elephant army and said, “I will have to trouble the Patriarch this time. Since Demon City has become quite hectic, I won’t be staying here for long. When I have time, I shall have a drink with the Patriarch later.”

Baht smiled and said, “The Prince is too polite. When you visit later, I shall personally arrive to entertain you.” Zhao Hai laughed and said, “Alright, then that’s settled.” Then he waved his hand as a spatial rift appeared. Zhao Hai turned to Baht and said, “Then I won’t be staying, Patriarch please command your men in.”

Baht nodded, then he beckoned his hand before a Silver Elephant came. Baht looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Prince, this is my son, Barres. He will be the commander for this troop. If the Prince has anything he needs, then you can freely approach him.”

Barres immediately bowed and said, “I have seen His Highness Prince Zhao Hai.” He had a very nasally voice. Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Alright, then we’re good to go.” Berres trumpeted his trunk before the army slowly entered the spatial rift.

When all of the Elephants had entered the rift, Zhao Hai then turned to Baht and said, “Patriarch Baht, I shall be leaving. I won’t be disturbing you anymore.” He bowed to Baht once more before entering the rift and vanishing.

When Zhao Hai came out of the rift, he saw Barres leading his men to make a formation outside Demon City. Seeing them prepared, Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Barres, follow me. I’ll lead you to the place where you will be staying at. Let’s have you rest in the city first.” Bares complied and commanded his army to walk towards the city along with Zhao Hai.

The people on the city had spotted the army as well. However, when they saw Zhao Hai’s Bone Dragon, they immediately knew that it was the reinforcements. This made their hearts warm up with excitement.

Although there weren’t a lot of reinforcements from the three other races, it was still a very huge morale boost to the defenders of Demon City. For the people inside the city, this meant that three powers were supporting them from behind.

Before long, Zhao Hai had taken the Elephant Beastmen to their residence. One must say that the Elephant Race’s camp needed special attention. They needed big houses otherwise they wouldn’t be able to fit.

The arrival of the Elephants didn’t make as large as a commotion compared to the Dwarves and Elves. After all, there were still ample contact between the Humans and Beastmen all these years. At the same time, Humans and Beastmen would constantly go into war with each other. This made the Beastmen look bad in the minds of the Humans.

Although the Buddha Empire didn’t border with the Beastman Prairie and big battles generally didn’t bother them, knowing that the Beastmen and Humans went to war with each other still had an effect in their mentality. However, the arrival of the three races were still able to calm the defenders’ hearts. Knowing that Demon City has been reinforced and strengthened was a very good thing for the people inside the city.

In fact, it wasn’t only Demon City which will have reinforcements. Later on, the three races will be sending more troops to aid the Buddha Empire. Together with the Humans, the entire Buddha Empire will be formed into a defensive fort.

At this time, all of the races in the continent needed to be united. The Divine Race even has yet to arrive, and this worried Zhao Hai.

After taking care of the Elephants, Zhao Hai lead Berry back to the Space. Laura and the others had now gotten up and were ready to eat their meal. Since Zhao Hai was quite hungry as well, he decided to eat along with them. At the same time, Zhao Hai also looked at the monitor and looked at the scenery outside Demon City. The Demons hasn’t made a single sound, this made Zhao Hai worry.

When the Demons came, would they just be building their city in peace? Why doesn’t this feel like standard Demon behaviour? Is there something wrong?

However, Zhao Hai was also wishing for this to happen. He was also waiting for the God-rank potion to be finished. When Shue gets promoted to God-rank, then Zhao Hai’s side would have four God-rank experts. With this number, Zhao Hai can now lead his undead to harass the Demons.

Time slowly passed as the skies turned dark. After this day passes, the Demons have already stepped foot on the continent for three days. There weren’t any fighting between both sides yet, there weren’t any significant losses. The present situation looked like a peaceful coexistence.

However, Zhao Hai knew that this wasn’t peace. This was merely the calm before the storm. The Demons were only waiting for their God-ranked experts to stabilize their strength. On the other hand, Zhao Hai was also waiting for his potion to be finished. As soon as the potion gets used up, then Zhao Hai would launch his own attack against the Demon Race.

Originally, Zhao Hai wanted to wait for the response coming from the Divine Race before taking any action. However, the Divine Race has been very slow in responding. Because of this, Zhao Hai decided to take a shot at the Demons and see if he can drive them back all on his own. Even if he cannot deal with the Demon Race, Zhao Hai would still cement his image as a formidable person inside the minds of the Demons.

After a peaceful night, Zhao Hai came out of the Space and went to see the people from the base of operations outside the City. Zhao Hai didn’t have the Gan family take charge for the whole night. Although Tywin and the others were 9th rank experts, they weren’t like Zhao Hai who didn’t need to use any spiritual force in order to control the undead. They were different, they needed to exert an effort so that they can give orders to their minions. The reason why Zhao Hai had them guard here in the daytime was so that they can train their spiritual force.

Zhao Hai knew that although the potion for 9th rank was very beneficial, those who drank it needed to be accustomed to 9th rank strength as well. Because of this Zhao Hai decided to position them outside the city, making them use their spiritual force in controlling the undead. This way, they would be able to use their 9th rank abilities much more comfortably.

Chapter 705: The Thing They Worried Most About

The Demons still didn’t attack in the next two days. However, Zhao Hai didn’t idle in this period of time. He called Barres, Julian, and Gellar over to go meet with Besmir. After all, everyone was together in defending Demon City.

After the group met, they immediately discussed about their arrangements in the future. In the end, the main task that was handed over to the Dwarves was the construction of the tunnels.

Naturally, since the Dwarves didn’t need too much people in digging, they were also tasked to deploy some of their members to help defend the city. Like the Humans, they would be acting as sentry as well as wall patrols. This wasn’t an embarrassment to them, after all, this would also help them in judging the status of the City in the future.

On the other hand, the task that was given to the Elves was quite simple. While Zhao Hai was fighting with the Demons outside the city, the Elves would be the outside aerial cavalry, taking shots at the Demons from time to time.

Although the Elves had brought a lot of dual cultivators of sword and harp, their melee capabilities were trained for ground combat. It would be impossible for them to learn aerial battles in a short time. Therefore, it would be detrimental for them to approach the Demons in melee combat.

However, the one with the biggest problems were the Elephant Beastmen.. Although they were quite slow, their defensive abilities were quite amazing. At the same time, some of them were able to use earth magic as well. They would be a huge help in the defense. The only problem was the fact that the walls were made for Humans, the Elephants would have a hard time while being stationed there.

The Elephants wouldn’t be able to scale the walls. Although their fighting strength is indeed significant, it wouldn’t have that much of an effect, after all they were on the defense. However, Zhao Hai was still quite reluctant about this. But since there was no other way, the temporary task handed over to the Elephants right now was to help transport weapons and commodities all throughout the city.

In order to prepare for the attack of the Demons, Zhao Hai had also made the Humans use the first excavated tunnels by the Dwarves to reinforce the walls of the city. He was afraid that the walls wouldn’t be able to withstand the charge of the Demons.

Those two days went past in a blink of an eye. At this time, Zhao Hai wasn’t inside Demon City but instead he was inside the Space along with Laura and the others. All of them stood in front of the processing machine. There were only two minutes left before the God-rank potion becomes available.

Shue was standing right by Zhao Hai’s side. When Shue heard that Zhao Hai wanted to promote him into a God-ranked expert, he was utterly stunned. He was aware of the God-ranked potion, however, he didn’t expect Zhao Hai to pick him to be the first one to consume it.

But when Zhao Hai explained the reason to him, Shue immediately understood. Shue didn’t say anything, and after handing his tasks over to someone else, he immediately went to the Space.

The ticking of the Processing Machine’s timer coincided with the heartbeat of those who were present. The atmosphere got more and more tense with each digit that the timer counted down.

This was the first time that Zhao Hai would use the God-rank potion in order to promote someone to God-rank, telling people that he was not anxious would be a lie. When Shue gets promoted, then their relative power would be very close to the power of the Demon Race. Also, as long as they are given time, the number of 9th ranks that they produce would get more and more. By then, forcing the Demons to return to the Demon Realm would be an easy matter.

Ten, nine, eight, seven, six, five, four, three, two, one. “Strengthening Potion has been completed. Please collect it as soon as possible.” Then a small bottle appeared right in front of Zhao Hai.

This bottle was about the size of one’s palm. It was an extremely ordinary bottle, there were no cosmetics on it. Filling half of the bottle was a dark blue liquid. The color was very beautiful, it was akin to the dark blue ocean. One could see how clean the potion was, there was no point of impurity that can be seen.

Zhao Hai took the bottle and inspected it properly, then he couldn’t help but say, “All of those precious materials, only to make this much. It’s really quite an expensive potion.” Then he gave the bottle to Shue and said, “Shue, go and prepare yourself before drinking this potion. Adjust your mental state accordingly before taking it all down.” Shue carefully received the bottle before bowing, “Yes, Young Master.”

Zhao Hai nodded, he looked at Shue and then added, “Shue, it would be great if this potion would be able to make your clones into 9th rank. However, if it doesn’t matter. After all, the Space can just plant more materials for the potion.”

Shue nodded then he said, “Young Master, let me excuse myself.”

Zhao Hai gave his approval, then Shue went towards his room as Zhao Hai and the others returned to the living room. At this time, Lizzy looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Big Brother Hai, do you think that Shue would succeed?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Success is for certain. The Space has not disappointed me before. However, I’m afraid that the potion won’t be enough to turn his clones into God-rank. If that happens, our strength would be lesser than what I wish it to be.”

Berry frowned as she said, “We also aren’t aware as to when Shue would be done. I feel that the God-ranked Demons are already done with restoring their strength.”

Zhao Hai sighed and said, “Maybe we’ll have to wait for a few more days. I don’t think it would be easy to deal with the Demons now that the Divine Race seem to be absent. Moreover, there is also the Demon Race’s self-exploding methods. They are quite powerful, Berry, you should already know about it.”

Berry nodded, “Demons regard being captured after defeat to be a shame. Therefore, when they are defeated, they would immediately initiate their self-destructing incantations. Moreover, 9th rank Demons have the capability to injure God-rank experts with their explosions.”

Zhao Hai inodded, this was what he dreaded the most about the Demons. They were simply unafraid to die. They regard war as their lifestyle, such a race would definitely be fearless warriors.

When Laura and the others heard Berry’s statement, their expressions couldn’t help but change. They didn’t think that the Demons would get that aggressive. If both sides fought and the Demons decided to blow themselves up, then the casualties would definitely be huge.

Laura couldn’t help but look at Berry and asked, “Do only 9th rank Demons explode themselves?”

Berry shook her head and said, “I’m afraid not, every Demon above 5th rank, no matter Demon or magic beast, can self-explode. This was because of the difference between the Humans and the Demons. Humans practice Battle Qi and Magic, and while the Demons train in these methods, upon reaching 5th rank all of them would develop a Demonic Core. As long as these Demons have their core, then they would be able to explode themselves. However, low level Demons wouldn’t have powerful explosions. 5th ranks can kill or wound 6ht ranks while 6th ranks can injure 7th ranks. When 7th ranks explode they would take an 8th rank’s life. And similarly, 8th ranks would become threats to 9th ranks.”

The worries on Laura and the others’ face became more evident. For 8th ranks to become threats to 9th ranks meant that 8th rank Demons would prove a threat to Zhao Hai’s undead. One must know that Zhao Hai’s undead were their main source of strength when going against the Demons and the Divine Race. Now it seems like Zhao Hai needed to be more careful with regards to future battles.

And although Zhao Hai can crystallize his body to the point of being unbreakable, Zhao Hai was still unaware of how strong the God-ranked Demons were. If those God-rank experts can break Zhao Hai’s crystallized body, then Zhao Hai would be placed in a perilous situation.

But even if they can’t break Zhao Hai’s crystallized body, they were still unsure whether they can beat the God-ranks of both the Demon and the Divine Race’s side. This was where the undead would prove useful.

Zhao Hai looked at those around him and smiled, “Alright, there’s no need to worry about these for now. Let’s wait before the Divine Race arrives and then we’ll make prior arrangements. At this point, I’m more worried about their absence than them being already here.”

Laura nodded and said ,”I don’t know what kind of plan is being made by the Divine Race. However, I’m quite sure that when they start, then their movement wouldn’t be small. Their actions should be as fast as lightning. We should be careful about this point.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he frowned and said, “Right, apart from sending in 9th ranks, what other methods can the Divine Race do? I remember from what Iron Hammer said that its harder to descend to the Ark Continent than to ascend to the Divine Realm. Is it possible for them to have found a much better way?”

Laura and the others frowned, “They were unable to guess what ideas the Divine Race might have. After all, they had Cai’er and Berry to get information about the Demon Realm. But when it came to the Divine Realm, they have virtually nothing. This point made them worry.”

The enemy you understand isn’t terrifying since you can make all sorts of plans against them. On the other hand, and enemy that you can’t understand is scary. No matter how many cards you have on your hand, you still couldn’t use them since you don’t know what move to make.

The preparation done by the Divine Race was certainly more than the Demon Race. But now that the Divine Race had done nothing, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but feel a headache.

Zhao Hao didn’t underestimate the Divine Race. When they sent their person down last time, they were able to turn heaven and earth upside down. Now that they had prepared for tens of thousands of years, who knows what methods they had already conjured.

However, there was one thing that Zhao Hai was sure about. No matter what methods the Divine Race does, he would make sure to give them the strongest counter-attack!

Chapter 706: Don’t Take It Too Seriously

Shue quietly sat inside his room. He didn’t drink the God-rank potion immediately. Instead, he decided to adjust his mind first, only consuming the potion at his peak state. He held the bottle in his hand and stared at it for quite some time,

Although he kept rotating the bottle in his hand, Shue’s mind was actually somewhere else. He was thinking about the first time he and Zhao Hai met. At that time, two of them were enemies, with Shue being hired as an assassin.

But now, he was a 9th rank expert and a steward of the Buda Clan. And at the same time, he had made a name for himself that even Great nobles would give him great face whenever they meet him. And soon, he was going to be a God-ranked expert, an existence placed at the utmost apex of the entire Continent, a position only his Young Master had acquired before.

All of these things were given to him by his Young Master. Shue knew the current situation of the continent. At this time, they were truly in a dangerous position. If the Demons decide to attack at this time, then his Young Master would surely be unable to stop them.

In the past, Shue had always lamented the fact that his strength was too low, and that he cannot offer any significant help to Zhao Hai. But now, as long as he becomes a God-ranked expert, then he would become an aid to Zhao Hai’s plans.

Shue never thought of going against Zhao Hai. And this was not because of the Blood Oath, in fact, the Blood Oath has already been deemed useless once he became 9th-rank. Shue didn’t dare think about betraying Zhao Hai because he wouldn’t have had all of these things without Zhao Hai.

Shue recovered from his thoughts, his eyes held a firm resolve. He decided deep in his heart that once he becomes a God-rank expert and had God-ranked clones, then he would still follow Zhao Hai’s side, he would always stand by and protect his Young Master.

After thinking up to here, Shue’s heart became free. This was a kind of feeling that made it seem like his heart was two taels(100g) lighter.

Shue looked at the bottle, then he smiled slightly before he turned the cork and drank it. The moment the potion hit his stomach, Shue immediately felt a rush of strength tyrannically going through his body. Shue felt his body going to shreds, however, he wasn’t afraid. He believed that Zhao Hai would never harm him. Because of this, he calmed his thoughts and just allowed the energy to go through his body. He understood that there was no point in controlling something that can’t be controlled, so he just decided to wait it out.

Shue was currently in a unique state of mind. He felt that he had been separated from his fleshly body. It seemed like he was standing in a far off place, observing as his soul separated from his body. It was a marvelous feeling, Shue felt that he had become omniscient in his own little world.

Not knowing how long, but Shue suddenly felt that the rush of energy had completely subsided. It was currently running in his meridians in a straight and orderly manner.

Shue knew that the process has succeeded. He currently had the feeling of invincibility that couldn’t compare to what he was feeling before. At the same time, Shue suddenly had a discovery, his clones hadn’t been promoted to God-rank.

Shue sighed, he stood up and felt the strength of his body. Then he summoned a clone, the clone was still 9th-rank and did not reach the next level. Shue frowned before he slowly walked out of his room.

At this time, Zhao Hai was sitting inside the Space looking at the situation outside the city. It hasn’t been too long before Shue entered his room, only about two hours had passed.

Hearing Shue’s door open, Zhao Hai immediately turned his head to look. Shue had arrived at the living room at this time, he bowed to Zhao Hai and said, “Young Master.”

When Zhao Hai looked at Shue’s gloomy expression, his face couldn’t help but turn heavy as he asked, “Shue what happened? Did you fail?”

Shue worriedly replied, “Young Master, I only half-succeeded. I am now a God-ranked expert, however, my clones are still 9th rank.” Zhao Hai didn’t become disappointed with this result as he laughed and said, “That doesn’t matter, you already did good. Hahaha, from the expression of your face, I really thought that you had failed.”

Shue looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Young Master, I have this very unusual feeling. I think that as long as I drink another potion, then my clones would reach God-rank.”

Zhao Hai stared, then his eyes shined as he said, “Really?”

Shue nodded and said, “Yes, Young Master. The feeling is quite strong. I can assure that you that it is not a desire, but it is a genuine feeling.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “That’s good enough, there’s no need for you to explain yourself further. Cai’er, how long will the next batch of ingredients be prepared?” Cai’er counted with her fingers and said, “Young Master, at minimum, five days.” Zhao Hai nodded, then he gave some instructions, “Look after those materials, after they get prepared, go and immediately make a potion, there would be no need to notify me.” Cai’er nodded.

Then Zhao Hai turned to Shue and said, “Shue, you don’t need to worry too much. When that other potion get finished, then you’ll get to drink it. When that time comes, we would have more than 1000 God-ranked experts. Those Demons and Divine Race fellows would surely get swept away.”

Shue’s looked at Zhao Hai with an elated expression, then he kneeled to the ground and said, “Shue is forever grateful to the Young Master.” Zhao Hai smiled faintly and held Shue up as he said, “Alright. Shue, there’s no need to be this formal. All of us here is family, you’re too modest. Right, follow me outside. It really makes me feel disgusted whenever I see the Demons continued to build while we couldn’t do anything. Let’s show the Demons that building their city in the Continent wouldn’t be that easy.”

Shue couldn’t help but laugh, “Alright, Young Master. I haven’t fought with a Demon before, I want to see how fierce they really are.” Zhao Hai smiled faintly and then turned his head to Berry, “Berry, let’s head out and see how the Demon Dragon King’s people plans deal with us.” Then the three people went out of the Space.

Outside, Zhao Hai summoned his Bone Dragon as the three of them stood on its head. Zhao Hai summoned 1000 undead, all of them in their humanoid form. Then Zhao Hai smiled as he relayed a message to Lizzy and Megan, “Lizzy, Megan, I’ll be handing the control of the undead army over to you while we block the God-ranked experts. Today, we must let the Demons understand that the Ark Continent isn’t just a place where they can casually come over and build cities in. They seem to be underestimating us too much”

Lizzy and Megan, who were both inside the Space, nodded. Then they commanded the undead army to slowly approach the Demons. The city that the Demons planned on building wasn’t small, therefore, the Demons were still in the process of laying in some foundations.

Upon seeing Zhao Hai’s huge army of undead, the Demon Dragon King’s expression couldn’t help but change. Just as what Berry thought, the Demon Camp had five God-ranked experts. However, the five of them were still yet to restore their strength. Currently, none of them were able to fight to their full potential.

Because of this, the Demon Dragon King sent their most elite troops to meet Zhao Hai in the past. He wanted to make Zhao Hai understand their strength, making him afraid of ever attacking them again.

Naturally, the Demon Dragon King also discovered that Zhao Hai was a God-rank expert. In order to prevent Zhao Hai from attacking, he deliberately had the God-ranked experts in his army to show a hint of their aura. This was to make it known to Zhao Hai that the Demon side had five god-ranked experts, making him hesitate to attack them.

His plan had become very successful, Zhao Hai didn’t make any other moves. He just stayed in Demon City all the time, looking at the city slowly being built. The Demon Dragon King wanted this state to continue up until the God-ranked experts were able to use their full strength. When that time comes, then they wouldn’t need to worry about any attacks that Zhao Hai might do in the future.

However, they had decided to launch an attack, not giving the Demons any chance to prepare. Moreover, the Demon Dragon King didn’t expect that along with Zhao Hai, there were also two other God-ranked experts.

The Demon Dragon King couldn’t help but smile bitterly, he used to think that Zhao Hai was a patient person. He didn’t expect Zhao Hai to make a move this abruptly.

Moreover, the Demon Dragon King felt worried about the two other God-ranked experts beside Zhao Hai. Where did these two people come from? Didn’t the Ark Continent forbid the existence of God-ranked experts? The Demon Dragon King had realized that their conquest wouldn’t be as easy as they thought.

Additionally, it seems like Zhao Hai’s side wasn’t struggling from the suppression brought by the Ark Continent. They were God-ranked experts yet they seem to be able to use all of their strength. Completely unlike the Demons who needed to stabilize their condition in order to reach their full performance.

However, there wasn’t enough time to think about these. The Demon Dragon King immediately issued a command, “Prepare to meet the enemy!!” At the same time, his Black Dragon carriage shot up into the sky, the other God-ranked experts going alongside him.

These God-ranked experts were also very special. One of them was a member of the Black Dragon race, he wore a black plate armor as his sat down on his horse. The hooves and tail of this horse was aflame. It had two eyes, a scaled body and a look of extreme savageness. The Knight had a lance on his hand while a two-handed sword hung on his waist. At the same time, he also had a knight’s shield mounted on his back.

Then next God-ranked expert had a Mage’s appearance, it was a Lich. Underneath this Demon Lich was a skeleton beast. From the looks of it, the beast seemed to be a huge blood sucking bat.

To the right of the Lich was a leather armor wearing archer. He had a jet black longbow on his hand and quivers on his waist. Each quiver holding 12 jet black arrows within it.

Second to the right was a person that looked like an Assassin. Cotton garments wrapped the whole person’s body except his eyes. One couldn’t spot a hint of skin on his body. Other than the rapier on his back, there weren’t any weapons that can be seen.

Chapter 707: Domain

Five people, five different appearances, but all had the same characteristics. They gave off the feeling of being dangerous. And behind them were flying Demons and magic beasts.

The undead army didn’t attack immediately. When they saw that the Demon Dragon King was coming to them, the army stopped. This gave hope to the Demon Dragon King, he was thinking that Zhao Hai really didn’t have any thoughts of attacking them today, otherwise, he wouldn’t have stopped.

Zhao Hai’s group of three went forward while on top of the Bone Dragon. The Demon Dragon King looked at Berry and saw that she already had a crystal on her head. This made the Demon Dragon King’s eyes shrink, then he shifted his gaze to Shue who was standing behind Zhao Hai.

Shue was also a God-ranked expert, but the Demon Dragon King felt a distinct aura of danger on Shue. In addition to being a God-ranked expert, the Demon Dragon King can also see a warrior, a warrior that wasn’t afraid of death.

Most importantly, the Demon Dragon King can see how Shue looks at Zhao Hai. It was a look of complete devotion, a look of worship.

Such a gaze wouldn’t have been strange on an ordinary person, however, it was truly bizarre if it appears on a God-ranked expert.

What were God-rank experts? It was a world’s peak existence. Even if one were a slave before, once he becomes God-rank, then he would achieve the treatment of a God-ranked expert as well as the respect that come along with it. One must know that these God-ranks consider themselves as the top of the food chain, there was nobody that they would lower their head to.

Taking the Demon Dragon King’s group for example, although the Demon Dragon King held a higher status, he was still unable to give commands to the other God-rank experts. The only reason why these experts listened to him was because it was an order from the Great Demon King.

In the Demon Realm, nobody can violate the order of His Majesty the Great Demon King, even if you are a God-rank expert. Therefore, these God-ranked experts chose to cooperate with the Demon Dragon King for now.

The Demon Dragon King turned his gaze to Zhao Hai, the dread on his eyes getting thicker. He didn’t think that a God-rank expert could actually make another God-rank expert worship him. Without even considering Zhao Hai’s strength, just this point alone made Zhao Hai the most dangerous person present here.

The Demon Dragon King slowly stopped in front of Zhao Hai, then his deep voice sounded out, “Is mister really unable to let us go? Do we really need to fight to the death?”

Zhao Hai looked at the Demon Dragon King and smiled faintly, “There’s no need for the Demon Dragon King to talk too much. I know the reason why you came to the Ark Continent, and you know the reason as well. Further talks are useless at this point. However, I still need to make a final question to the Demon Dragon King. Are the Demons really unwilling to go back to the Demon Realm?”

The Demon Dragon King looked straight to Zhao Hai’s eyes, and without blinking he said, “Never!”

Zhao Hai laughed, “Hahaha, then that’s the end. However, there is one thing I need to tell you. In fact, I am bringing my undead over today with the intention of having them eat a good proper meal.”

Then Zhao Hai waved his hand as the undead behind him disappeared. When they appeared once more, they were now behind the Demon Dragon King. These undead had already changed their shape into small groups of cone formations. All of them were rotating fast as they rushed towards the Demon army.

The Demon Dragon King’s expression changed, he waved his hand as well as he said, “Kill them!!” Then his black dragon carriage went charging towards Zhao Hai. The God-rank experts behind him heading forward as well.

Zhao Hai didn’t retreat, his figure moved as the Bone Dragon vanished. Then he, Berry, and Shue’s bodies disappeared in mid air. When they reappeared, they were already surrounding the Demon archer. Zhao Hai’s Blood Ghost Staff has been transformed into a glaive as it chopped towards the Archer.

Glaives weren’t present in the Ark Continent. However, because of the circumstances, Zhao Hai believed that the glaive would be the most suitable weapon for him to use at this time.

The reason why Zhao Hai chose to attack the archer was because among the other people, the Archer was the one who held the biggest threat. With his long-ranged attack, it wouldn’t be good if he was still present when Zhao Hai and the others were suppressing the Demon Dragon King.

The Archer wasn’t expecting Zhao Hai’s group to target him first. However, he wasn’t scared, instead, his face actually revealed a look of excitement. Then his figure moved as he disappeared into a region of dark cloud which also wrapped Zhao Hai’s group. At the same time, Zhao Hai and the others experienced their bodies’ weight increase by a few folds.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but mutter, “Is this the strength of a Domain?”

Zhao Hai was a God-rank expert, therefore, he knew how strong God-ranks can be. After achieving God-rank, an expert can then comprehend his own domain. This Domain would go alongside a person’s combat strength as it slowly forms. In this domain, a God-ranked expert would be able to display 120% of their strength while their enemies would be weakened to 80% of their abilities.

However, Domains are very hard to comprehend. One shouldn’t think that once you become God-ranked, then you would immediately comprehend a Domain. It takes a long time and enough experience in order to gain one.

A God-ranked expert who didn’t have a Domain could only exert about 80% of their true ability. It can be said that God-ranked experts who have a Domain and those who don’t were on two different stages.

Zhao Hai’s group hadn’t managed to comprehend their own Domain yet. Because of this, Zhao Hai used this moment to capitalize on the fact that the God-ranked Demons were yet to fully recover their strength. However, Zhao Hai could still feel the disadvantages of not having a Domain.

The God-ranked Demons seem to be aware of this point, therefore, the Demon Dragon King ominously sounded, “Domain Merge!”

Merging of Domains was a very peculiar technique. God-ranked experts were prominent people in their worlds, therefore, it was rare for them to cooperate with one another. However, once they manage to do so, they would still find it hard to fight without their Domains being a hindrance to the other. Because of this, God-ranked experts had finally thought of a method, and it was to merge the Domains together. When Domains merged, then the owners of those Domains would be able to fight together without causing trouble to their ally.

Naturally, this merging wasn’t something that can just be used casually. First, it needed two people who had fairly the same levels of strength. Then, the two people needed to have absolute trust of one another, otherwise, the process would fail.

When the Demon Dragon King saw that Zhao Hai’s group were stranded inside the Archer’s domain and still didn’t use their own, he immediately knew that Zhao Hai’s side were still yet to comprehend their domain. This made the Demon Dragon King happy. As long as Zhao Hai didn’t have a Domain, then they can just merge their Domains and lock Zhao Hai inside. Therefore, the Demon Dragon King immediately ordered for the merging of Domains.

The other God-ranked experts didn’t delay, they immediately merged one another’s Domain. Then slowly, each of their Domains fused and became a huge but unstable Domain.

However, when they used their Domain, Zhao Hai’s group had already disappeared from their original place. Zhao Hai knew about Domains before, this was because Bloody War spoke about it.

Since the Demon Realm had God-ranked experts, then they certainly knew how to use a Domain. Zhao Hai just baited them to use it in order to see what a Domain really is.

At this moment, Zhao Hai and the others were sitting inside the Space as they observed the Demon Dragon King’s group. Although their Domains looked the same, there were some differences in places. The Archer’s domain was a dark mist that seemed to affect gravity. However, this Domain excludes the Archer. This allowed the archer to not only slow the enemy but blind them as well while he has free movement inside it.

The Demon Dragon King’s Domain was quite interesting, it was a type of Domain that gives a mental attack. One would fall into an illusion where the Demon Dragon King was your ruler, your god, and that you must submit to him.

The Lich’s Domain was a sea of bones. Everything inside it was an endless facade of white skeletal parts. Inside of the Domain were several undead that gets stronger and stronger the more one fights. At the same time, the undead weren’t bland fighters, they were also able to learn your techniques and use it against you.

The Knight’s Domain was very simple. Inside his Domain one would feel weak, frightened, bloodthirsty, violent, and all other negative feelings. At the same time, the knight would feel empowered, strong, and invincible. This was a Domain that would reduce someone’s abilities to the minimum while the Knight improves to his peak.

The Assassin’s Domain was an unusual one. In the Domain was a shattered house that was covered with a black fog. The fog was very poisonous and can hide the Assassin. While inside the Domain, not only would you worry about the attacks from the Assassin, you would also worry about the poison that the fog would constantly give you.

Chapter 708 – Domain War

The reason why Zhao Hai knew all of these was because he had the Space’s help. Although his group had entered the Space, the Blood Ghost staff remained outside. This essentially made the Staff akin to a sensor for the Space to use in order to analyze the characteristics of a Domain.

The merging of the Domain caused a change to how they appeared. In that huge field, large houses appeared along with an imperial palace. The whole place seemed to become a city.

In addition to the structures, undead can also be seen walking through the streets of that city, looking like the citizens of the place.

At the same time, dark poisonous mists were billowing right outside the Domain City. This fog caused an increase of both gravity and negative emotions felt by those affected. On the other hand, the undead seem to benefit in all of these things. It was a very unusual sight.

After hearing the analysis of the Space regarding this merged Domain, Zhao Hai’s brows couldn’t help but wrinkle. He was now thinking of ways to break this huge Domain.

For Zhao Hai, leaving this Domain is very easy, he can just use the Space and teleport out. However, if he wanted to defeat the Demons, then he would need to destroy these Domains first. Otherwise, Zhao Hai’s attacks wouldn’t have an influence to the Demon Dragon King’s group.

What Zhao Hai didn’t know was that the Demon Dragon King was also frowning. One must know that merging Domains as well as maintaining it was a huge drain of energy. After the Demon Dragon King’s group merged their Domain, they immediately discovered that Zhao Hai had disappeared, this made them extremely confused.

The Domain that God-ranked experts comprehend was a magical field that was just like Zhao Hai’s Space. Zhao Hai can understand the changes in his Space, God-ranked experts can do the same on their Domain. The only difference was that Domains needed energy to be activated, while the Space did not. Domains can be used in battles while the Space cannot. And lastly, Domains are small while Zhao Hai’s Space was very large.

Because of this, when Demon Dragon King’s group attacked Zhao Hai, they were quick to notice Zhao Hai’s disappearance. It was clear that Zhao Hai didn’t use his own Domain. This made the five people very puzzled.

At this time, the Space suddenly issued a prompt, “Aggressive Spatial region detected. Extracting its properties and adding it into the Sace. The host can now use a Spatial region. The characteristics of the region would be the same as the Space.”

Zhao Hai gawked, but then a huge amount of information suddenly flooded into his head. He carefully analyzed them and discovered that it was a method to apply his Domain. The Domain was very similar to the Space. It had the Space’s environment and Zhao Hai was a god inside it, everything inside it was all up to his whims.

However, this Space wasn’t actually a real Domain. It was just a method for Zhao Hai to use the Space in a certain region outside. Zhao Hai can change the terrain outside as well as the environment, it was just like the Space.

This Domain was completely different that the one used by the Demon Dragon King’s group. Zhao Hai’s Domain doesn’t need energy to support it. This was because this Domain completely relied on the Space, it didn’t need any input from Zhao Hai. Essentially, rather than being called a Domain, it was more appropriate to call it a projection of the Space.

When he saw this Domain, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but laugh. In this Domain, Zhao Hai was invincible and would have his own laws, nothing from outside can influence it. As long as a God-ranked expert gets trapped inside this Domain, then they wouldn’t be able to get out.

Naturally, this Domain needed to surround the enemy first, just like the Space. If the Space wanted to attack a person, then that person needed to be inside the Space. Otherwise, the Space wouldn’t be able to attack that person directly.

Other God-ranked Domains might be able to do it since their had their own offensive abilities. However, Zhao Hai’s Space had no way to outwardly attack. But on the positive side, Zhao Hai’s Domain cannot be destroyed. One could see Zhao Hai’s Domain as a meat grinder. It had a layer of iron outside, so you cannot destroy the meat grinder while the meat grinder couldn’t hurt you. However, once you enter that meat grinder, then you would no doubt be turned into mincemeat.

Although his Domain had no way to attack outward, Zhao Hai was still quite happy about it. God-ranked experts always worried about their Domains since having one made you a true God-ranked expert. Otherwise, you could only be considered to have a false God-rank.

Since Zhao Hai had his own Domain, then naturally he could use it. Zhao Hai’s body came out of the Space as he immediately established his Domain.

A scaled-down version of the Space suddenly appeared around Zhao Hai. This miniature Space looked very much like the beginning stages of the real Space. There were a few fields, some grasslands, a wooden house and a small seedling on the field. However, even this smaller Space was just as big as the merged field of the Demon Dragon King’s group.

Zhao Hai immediately moved his Domain to repel the merged Domain of the Demons. In retaliation, a huge pressure went towards Zhao Hai’s Domain, wanting to crush it. However, was Zhao Hai’s Space that easy to deal with? At this moment, on the periphery of Zhao Hai’s Domain, a seven colored light suddenly flashed. The seven colored light then started to rotate around Zhao Hai’s Domain, making the pressure do nothing to Zhao Hai. When the God-ranked Demons saw this, they immediately exerted extra effort in order to squeeze Zhao Hai’s Domain out from their merged Domain.

When Zhao Hai’s Domain was pushed out of the merged Domain, the merged Domain suddenly formed into a giant skeletal archer. The arrow on the archer’s hand had a black mist surrounding it while its bow had a gloomy gas going in and out. The skeletal archer pulled the string on its bow as an arrow quickly flew towards Zhao Hai.

When the misty arrow hit Zhao Hai’s Domain, the Domain immediately turned into a whirlpool, absorbing the arrow in the process.  While inside his Domain, Zhao Hai’s eyes suddenly shone with a joyful expression. This was because when the Domain received the arrow, the Space had issued a prompt, “Attacking method from space type attack received. Host can now use external attacks for his spatial region. The attack method needs to be comprehended voluntarily by the Host.”

Although Zhao Hai had no idea what voluntarily comprehended means, he understood that his Domain had now gained an exterior offensive ability.[1]  And as for the method itself, Zhao Hai gained an inspiration from what the Demon Dragon King’s group just did.

Zhao Hai waved his hand as his Domain slowly changed its shape and became a gigantic Stone Golem. The Stone Golem seem to be made out of transparent rocks. Then the Golem suddenly picked a stone from its own body and threw it towards the opposite Domain.

When met with the attack, the merged Domain suddenly divided into five smaller Domains. These five Domains changed their form as well. The Archer’s Domain turned into an arrow. The Demon Dragon King’s Domain became a black dragon. The Lich’s Domain turned into a giant skeleton. The Knight’s Domain became a lance. And lastly, the Assassin’s Domain turned into a clump of dark gas.

Zhao Hai looked carefully at the five Domains. The inside of the Demons’ Domain cannot be seen, it was covered by their own forms. On the other hand, Zhao Hai’s Domain was transparent, people could clearly see what was happening inside. Even when his Domain had changed its form, it was still transparent. This difference was quite bizarre.

As for the other party, the Demon Dragon King and the Lich’s Domains looked very complicated. The Archer, Knight, and Assassin had simpler forms of their Domains. It seems like the Demon Dragon King and the Lich were the more powerful people in the group, making their Domain avatars more complicated. If this was the case, then it meant that a Domain can also develop over time. The stronger the Domain the more complicated its avatar would be. At this point, Zhao Hai was wondering about how these new forms would attack. Will it be just like normal attacks?

It seems like the Demons were keen to confirm Zhao Hai’s suspicion, the arrow of the Archer’s Domain suddenly attacked Zhao Hai by launching similar arrows towards him in a non-stop barrage.

On the other hand, the Demon Dragon King’s black dragon flew in a circle before charging towards Zhao Hai’s Domain. In the process of the attack, the black dragon actually spewed a black gas towards Zhao Hai.

The Lich’s Domain did quite the same, the skeleton rushed towards Zhao Hai’s stone golem. The skeletons arms aiming to puncture through the stone golem’s body. The Knight’s lance thrusted itself while the Assassin’s mist disappeared and appeared right beside Zhao Hai’s stone golem, intent on weakening it. Just as the mist got in contact with the stone golem, white smoke suddenly came out, it seems like the gas intends to corrode the stone golem down!

* * *

It can now make yo’ momma jokes

Chapter 709: Myriad Transformation Domain

Before, Zhao Hai thought that his Domain’s avatar would only get stuck with his first choice, the Rock Golem. But now, he knew that a Domain can still change. Then Zhao Hai tried to transform his Domain into an archer, which it did. It seems like he can make many transformations to his Domain.

This discovery made Zhao Hai’s heart light up. He can now understand what ‘voluntarily comprehend’ meant. Due to the forms of his Domain being numerous, the Space didn’t bother to tell him what they were.

When Zhao Hai saw the attack of the God-ranked Demons, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but recognize how strong they were. Their attacks were on a whole different level. Although the Archer, Knight, and Assassin’s Domains were weaker than the Demon Dragon King and the Lich, they still couldn’t be underestimated. Each one of these Domains were inseparable from the properties of their owners.

Zhao Hai gave a nod before changing his Domain into a revolving sphere, making the Assassin’s dark fog unable to melt it. However, the other attacks had already arrived. The first to appear was the Archer’s arrows. Although the Arrows looked weak, they were actually extremely fast, aking to a machine gun from Earth. If an average person were to meet this Domain, then there was no doubt that they would be thrown into confusion. However, Zhao Hai didn’t care about it too much, he rotated his Domain much faster, throwing the Archer’s arrows off to the side, not a single one managed to penetrate the spherical Domain.

On the other hand, the Demon Dragon King’s black dragon already spat out its ball of black gas. When this ball hit Zhao Hai’s spinning Domain, it actually managed to burn it. It seems like the rotation alone wasn’t enough to repel this burning attack.

At this moment, the Lich’s skeleton Domain also arrived with the Knight’s lance. Zhao Hai quickly transformed his Domain as it flashed with blue light before becoming a rotating ball of water. The Demon Dragon King’s black fireball slowly got extinguished by the water ball. After that, Zhao Hai changed the form of his Domain yet again into a huge fly-swatter, swatting the Lich’s skeleton Domain away. Then Zhao Hai’s Domain became a hand as it caught the Knight’s lance Domain intending to flick it towards the direction of the Demon Dragon King’s black dragon. However, the lance had already transformed into a clump of gas, getting away from the grip of Zhao Hai’s Domain.

At this time, the Demon Dragon King’s black dragon Domain arrived by Zhao Hai’s Domain, biting it in the fingers.

It was at this attack that Zhao Hai had truly felt pain for the first time, his chest suddenly experienced a severe sting.

Zhao Hai immediately understood that an attack on the Domain can injure the main body. Although his Domain was a tool to help him out, the one commanding it was still him. Therefore, if the Domain gets attacked, then he would still feel it.

This discovery didn’t make Zhao Hai flinch, instead, his hand quickly moved as the big hand transformed into an iron shovel. Then the iron shovel whacked the black dragons’ head. This made the black dragon retreat while shaking its head. Even the Demon Dragon King looked like he was made dizzy by the attack.

At this moment, the Lich’s Domain was already back as it charged over. This time, it has a huge bone sword in its hand which stabbed towards Zhao Hai’s iron shovel.

Zhao Hai just ate an attack from the black dragon, so how could he let himself suffer a second time? The iron shovel immediately turned into a spinning sphere. The Demon Dragon King was shocked by the transformations of Zhao Hai’s Domain. In the beginning, he thought that Zhao Hai didn’t have a Domain. Therefore, he decided to use this opportunity to bully him, even kill him if the chance allowed it.

But who knew that Zhao Hai actually had his own Domain. Moreover, this Domain was very formidable, it can actually push five Domains back on its own.

Most importantly, the forms of Zhao Hai’s Domain were numerous. Just like Zhao Hai guessed, Domains couldn’t be easily transformed. Take the Archer’s Domain for example, the Archer’s strength can only turn his Domain into the form of an arrow. If he got stronger later on, then the Domain might transform into something that went along with the Archer’s experiences. However, it was still impossible for their Domains to have many transformations like Zhao Hai’s. This was completely impossible to do, one should know that a Domain can only have two forms, the field form and the avatar form. Zhao Hai’s Domain actually had alot of transformations. Looking at Zhao Hai’s Domain, it wasn’t strange for the Demon Dragon King to be extremely shaken.

Zhao Hai didn’t have the mood to think about these, although he looked very relaxed while dealing with these people, he was actually quite stressed. The Archer’s arrows came too quick, although they had been deflected, they were still able to deal some damage. At the same time, the Assassin’s attack was also starting to take its toll. The Knight and the Lich’s attacks were strong as well. Zhao Hai’s chest felt quite stuffed right now, and it was obvious that he had been slightly injured.

But at the same time, the Demon Dragon King’s group weren’t having it better. Although Zhao Hai’s attack wasn’t that strong, they still managed to suffer minor wounds, especially the Lich. He flew quite far due to Zhao Hai’s fly-swatter. His injury was on the heavier side.

While Zhao Hai’s battle had gone very lively, the undead and the Demons weren’t idling, with the Demons the ones being pushed back. Although the Demons were quite strong, they weren’t all 9th ranks. Additionally, under Lizzy and Megan’s command, the undead formation constantly changed from a concrete solid block into smaller flexible formations, the damage that they had done was quite significant.

The Demons were currently confused regarding these undead. Zhao Hai was currently fighting with the Demon Dragon King’s group, so he should be preoccupied with fighting with them and should be unable to take command of the undead. However, why were the undead still able to move like this? It was too strange.

Casualties slowly came from the side of the Demons. However, Lizzy and Megan were still dissatisfied. Although these Demons were being suppressed right now, the number of Demon deaths were still lower than what they expected. And once these Demons knew that they were going to die, they would immediately self-explode, taking a clump of undead along with them.

However, the undead couldn’t be disregarded as well. Some low-level Demons didn’t even have the chance to self destruct before they were killed immediately. After these Demons were killed, they were quickly absorbed into the Space, transforming them into a member of the undead army.

The explosions that destroyed the undead were generally those from 8th ranks. Low-ranking explosions had zero effect on the undead.

However, even if the undead casualties weren’t big, Lizzy and Megan were still dissatisfied. It was because this was their first fight where they managed to lose some of their troops.

Women were usually mean-spirited, once they get angry, then the consequences would be critical. The attacks of the undead suddenly turned more violent. All of them started to suppress the Demons even more.

When the Demon Dragon King saw this situation, he immediately turned to the Lich and said, “White Ghost, go deal with the undead. Leave this place to us.”

The Lich’s skeleton Domain immediately moved away from the group and headed towards the undead army. When the skeleton turned around, a bone lance appeared in its hand. Then the bone lance was thrown straight towards a undead formation. When the lance clashed with the undead, they didn’t even have the chance to react as all of the undead immediately shattered into pieces.

Although Zhao Hai and the Demons seemed to be playing around in the clashes, but one must know that attacks of a God-ranked expert’s Domain were very strong. And judging by the size of the giant skeleton, one could imagine how large its bone lance was. The lance being able to puncture a dozen undead wouldn’t be an overstatement. At the same time, although the lance looked like it was made out of bone, it was actually made out of pure energy, its offensive ability was very formidable.

When Zhao Hai saw the Lich’s attack, he immediately had Berry and Shue appear right beside the Domain. Although they had yet to comprehend a Domain, they were still God-ranked, they can certainly suppress the Lich.

When Berry appeared, she immediately shouted as the hair on her head wrapped around the arm of the skeleton Domain. At the same time, Shue took out a big axe. One shouldn’t underestimate this axe. Zhao Hai had this axe made from the Processing Machine. Although it cannot be a Divine Artifact, the axe was still quite a formidable weapon.

With his axe pulled out, Shue shouted as he swung his axe even while being ten meters away from the Domain. However, distance didn’t matter because as Shue swung his axe, a projection suddenly appeared that cut down towards the skeleton Domain. The Lich issued a scream, it seemed to have been hurt. Then the Lich’s skeleton Domain stretched its other arm out as a lance appeared once more, aiming to stab towards Shue.

Chapter 710: Captured

Although Shue’s movement was simple, his actions were very quick. In a flash, another Shue appeared right by his side as their figure moved and went towards different directions to flee.

The Lich didn’t expect Shue to have this move. While he was stunned, one Shue disappeared as another one appeared bearing an axe as it chopped once more towards the Lich’s Domain.

Although Shue’s two attacks weren’t able to break the Lich’s Domain, it still managed to damage the Lich. At the same time, Berry’s hair attack wasn’t that simple. Her soul attacks used her hair as a conduit, her attacks had already made a name for itself in the Demon Realm. Although Berry was yet to comprehend a Domain, her soul attacks couldn’t be underestimated, it was God-ranked after all.

A God-rank that had comprehended a Domain was much stronger than one who hadn’t, however, this statement had its limits. As for the Lich, he could easily deal with Berry and Shue if he was in his peak form. But now, in addition to him not being in his peak, he was also injured by Zhao Hai. At this point, it would be impossible for him to easily deal with Berry and Shue.

Moreover, Shue and Berry were different from Zhao Hai. In the past, Zhao Hai exclusively fought using his own undead, making his close combat abilities quite poor. On the other hand, before becoming a God-rank expert, Shue was a mercenary assassin. Nobody knew how much fighting Shue had in his life but one could be assured that his fighting experience was rich. While being a mercenary, he was even known to kill people who were a rank higher than him. Now, although he hasn’t comprehended a Domain yet, him and the Lich were of the same level. With his experience, Shue should be able to clash with the Lich quite comfortably.

There was nothing else to say about Berry, she was born in the Demon Realm. No matter which race, all of the Demons in the Demon realm grew up fighting. This made Berry’s fighting experiences quite ample. Her only downside was her lack of a Domain since she just managed to become God-ranked.

From the very beginning, the Lich had truly underestimated the attack from Berry and Shue. In his opinion, these two who didn’t have a Domain wouldn’t be able to launch strong attacks. However, the Lich managed to make a mistake. He forgot that they had also underestimated Zhao Hai, assuming that he wasn’t able to establish his Domain, injuring the Lich in the process.

Berry’s hair continued to entangle the Lich’s skeleton Domain, attacking him with a constant barrage of soul attacks. Although these attacks weren’t able to injure the Lich, it was still enough to cause a headache.

The Lich were generally immune to physical attacks, especially after they reach God-rank. However, the Lich’s most feared attack were the ones who target their soul. These kinds of attacks do heavy damage to the Lich Race. Although the Lich had his Domain to protect him, the other party’s attacks still managed to influence his mind. The skeleton Domain was now more unstable compared to when it battled with Zhao Hai.

When the Demon Dragon King saw this situation, he immediately gave a command, “Shiying, go help White Ghost. Deal with those two as soon as possible.” The Assassin gave a nod before he threw himself towards the Lich.

Zhao Hai looked at the departing Shiying as his complexion turned ugly. He looked towards the Demon Dragon King as he muttered, “You had truly forced me.” Then he waved his hand as a spatial rift appeared in front of the Assassin. A vine suddenly came out of that rift and entangled the Assassin’s Domain. Then the vine retreated, pulling the Assassin’s Domain towards the Space.

The Assassin became surprised. It was impossible for him to know about the Space, so naturally he wouldn’t dare to go in. He tried to break free from the vine but found out that he couldn’t. This made him even more surprised, his Domain couldn’t actually free itself from this vine. The Assassin gnashed his teeth as he forcefully retrieved his Domain. When he saw that the vines didn’t do anything, he quickly drew back

However, just as the Assassin was retreating, a enormous whale suddenly appeared in front of him, swallowing him up. The Assassin noticed that the whale was actually transparent, and its interior had grasses, flowers, plants, and even a hut. More importantly, Zhao Hai was present as well!

The Assassin was startled, then he discovered that he had been absorbed into Zhao Hai’s Domain. The Assassin immediately established his Domain, but discovered that he couldn’t. He couldn’t even command his body properly. It seems like he had become helpless inside this Space.

While Zhao Hai captured the Assassin, he was also enduring full-on attacks from the Demon Dragon King, the Knight, and the Archer. Zhao Hai coughed up some blood, this time he was truly injured.

Zhao Hai became anxious when he saw the Demon Dragon King command the Assassin to help the Lich. He knew that Berry and Shue already had their hands full in suppressing the Lich, the addition of the Assassin wouldn’t be great for their situation. Because of this, Zhao Hai didn’t have any other choice but to have Cai’er make a move.

Cai’er was a card that Zhao Hai kept in secret, he didn’t want to use her quite easily. Cai’er’s strength surpassed ordinary God-ranks. This was the reason why the Assassin wasn’t able to move when being entangled by her vine.

Zhao Hai had also thought that the Assassin would let go of his Domain and escape. Therefore, he waited for the Assassin to do so. As soon as the Assassin managed to escape, Zhao Hai didn’t pay any attention to the oncoming attacks and just took the Assassin into his Domain.

Outward attacks of Zhao Hai’s Domain weren’t very formidable, however, its internal attacks were incomparably strong. As long as a God-ranked enters his Domain, then Zhao Hai can do whatever he wants to him. There were different laws inside Zhao Hai’s Domain, and the strength of these laws were very strong, God-ranked experts are simply helpless against it.

The reason Zhao Hai deemed it necessary to capture the Assassin was because he wanted to hide Cai’er’s strength. Since he wanted to keep her as a secret, then it was natural that he wouldn’t have to Assassin escape and tell the Demon Dragon King about how strong Cai’er was.

Fortunately, when Cai’er took action, she didn’t show her characteristics of being a Seven colored flower. The vine that came out looked just like any ordinary vine. It would be troublesome if the Demon Dragon King were to recognize her.

Since Zhao Hai neglected the attacks, then it was no wonder that he was injured. After all, his Domain wasn’t the true Space where even if he can’t control it, Cai’er was still there to take charge. Zhao Hai didn’t dare to drag things further as him and his Domain suddenly vanished. Berry and Shue, who were suppressing the Lich, disappeared as well. The undead who were fighting the Demons were also withdrawn.

Besides the Demon Dragon King’s group and the Demons, there weren’t anybody else in the battlefield. The magic that the Demon Dragon King was currently preparing was left with no target to cast on.

The Demon Dragon King’s heart immediately constricted as he gave a shout, “Be careful!”. Then he turned his head towards the direction of Demon City. He knew that Zhao Hai was injured, and if Zhao Hai were to return to the city, then a commotion would surely rise up.

When he turned his head, he saw Zhao Hai appearing in a place about a kilometer away from them. He currently stood on top of his Bone Dragon with his undead army behind him. Berry and Shue were also with him on the Bone Dragon.

Zhao Hai’s complexion was calm, one wouldn’t be able to find out that he was injured. The Demon Dragon King became even more alert. He withdrew his Domain as his stared at Zhao Hai. The Lich and the others have also arrived by the Demon Dragon King’s side.

Zhao Hai looked at the four God-ranked Demons and smiled faintly. Then he gave a small bow to the Demon Dragon King and said, “I managed to get good lessons from the Demon Dragon King. To be honest, I’ve lost quite a bit this time. If there’s an opportunity, then I will definitely ask for more advice from the Demon Dragon King’s group. However, today, I must say my farewells.” Then Zhao Hai made his Bone Dragon turn and head towards Demon City. The undead army following behind him.

The nearby Archer looked at the Demon Dragon King and said, “Why haven’t we made pursuit? Are you afraid?”

The Demon Dragon King turned to look at the Archer and said, “Herd, do you have the confidence to stop him? Do you think our group of four is enough to hold him down? Don’t forget, although those two people on his side weren’t able to establish a Domain, their fighting strengths were still very good, even enough to tie one of us down. And did you see those vines that managed to capture Shiying? If those vines weren’t anything special, then Shiying wouldn’t have given up on his own Domain. That thing can hold another one of us back. Do you think that two people is enough to suppress Zhao Hai?”

Herd didn’t speak, he knew that the Demon Dragon King was telling the truth. Zhao Hai had already shown his exceptional strength. He managed to block four people and suppress three, it was almost impossible for their side to kill Zhao Hai. And Zhao Hai just captured Shiying, the Demon side had truly suffered a blow. Although Zhao Hai has been injured, do they still have the confidence to tie him down? It was completely impossible to do so.

At this moment, the Knight’s voice was heard, “What do we do now?” The Demon Dragon King replied, “Iron Claw, you go return to the Demon Realm and report all that happened to the Great Demon King. Ask for a few more people to be sent here. Shiying’s strength isn’t that much different from all of us, yet he was still captured. Things just became dangerous for our side. We need more people to keep the security of the city so that we can establish a foothold on the Ark Continent.”

Chapter 711: Strengthened

Iron Claw gave a nod before he went towards the spatial rift. The Lich and the Archer didn’t speak, they were aware that the Demon Dragon King was telling the truth. Even if Zhao Hai was injured, he still had a lot of cards in hand. They weren’t even sure if Zhao Hai had a method to recover quickly. If Zhao Hai did, then with his strength as well as his strange helper, the Demons’ troubles would surely be big.

Also, for them and the Demon Dragon King, protecting the the city was a much more important task. Therefore, before their city gets finished, they still wouldn’t go and attack Zhao Hai.

In fact, the Demon Realm intended to attack Zhao Hai in turns. God-ranks were unable to stay in the Ark Continent for too long. And since the Demon Realm’s experts were numerous, they were planning to have them go to the Ark Continent in turns. They believed that with such a plan, the Ark Continent wouldn’t be able to hold on.

The Demon Dragon King’s group were one of the most famed experts in the Demon Realm, thus the reason why they were the ones to who were sent to the Demonic Abyss first. The Demons believed that with them in the vanguard, then there wouldn’t be any problems that would derail their plan.

However, they had underestimated Zhao Hai as well as his Space. They didn’t think that the Ark Continent would produce three God-ranked experts in such a short time. Most importantly, they didn’t expect that Zhao Hai was able to comprehend a Domain, and a formidable Domain at that.

And because they underestimated Zhao Hai, they lost big. It was then that the Demon Dragon King discovered that their current group weren’t enough to keep the city safe. Therefore, he decided to ask for reinforcements from the Demon Realm. For the Demon Race, asking for reinforcements was something that was extremely rare. However, the Demon Dragon King still did it, this city was just too important for the Demons.

Zhao Hai was healing himself up inside the Space. This was the first time that Zhao Hai had been injured after all his fights. He couldn’t help but recognize how strong those Demon God-ranks were.

Although Zhao Hai has his crystal body, he was using his Domain in this fight. Because of this, the damage to Zhao Hai was more spiritual than physical. This was the reason why the crystal body was unable to block the Demon attack.

To be honest, this was also due to the fact that Zhao Hai was still unskilled in using his Domain. He can actually use his divergent abilities with his Domain. However, he has not done it yet because it wasn’t an easy task to use divergent abilities with a Domain. However, as long as he succeeds in doing so, he would definitely be more powerful.

Among the many fights that Zhao Hai did, this was the first time that he had suffered such a heavy wound. However, Zhao Hai was not too worried about it. The Space had a lot of methods to cure wounds, among them were the Spatial Water and the God’s Blood.

However, Zhao Hai also managed to discover that another place actually had a good healing effect, it was the Hot Spring. It could actually make him recover, and the effect was no weaker than the Spatial Water and God’s Blood.

Although Zhao Hai’s wound was quite heavy, it was actually just a damage on his soul. Such wound might be troublesome to others, but to Zhao Hai, he really doesn’t need to worry too much about it.

Even if the Space didn’t have the experience of curing damage to the soul, one shouldn’t forget that Zhao Hai’s side had an expert on spiritual force, Berry.

The Succubus race relied purely on spiritual attacks in order to confront the enemy. Their mental attacks were the most powerful among the Demons. Therefore, Berry was quite experienced when it came to treating these kinds of damages. Moreover, Berry had a method of curing such wounds. So when Berry discovered that Zhao Hai suffered an attack on his soul, she immediately imparted the method over to Zhao Hai.

But who would’ve thought that when Berry passed the method over, the Space suddenly issued a prompt, “Host obtained soul cultivation manual, Advanced level. Host’s spiritual force has been strengthened. Resistance to spiritual attacks increased.”

Zhao Hai blankly stared while listening to the prompt. He didn’t think that he would be gaining a soul cultivation method. Moreover, the Space had actually strengthened his spiritual force as well as his resistance to attacks on the soul. This was too astonishing.

All of these happened after Zhao Hai returned to Demon City. Before this, Zhao Hai appeared in front of the people of Demon City. He rode on top of his Bone Dragon as his undead were right behind him.

Zhao Hai did this in order to give confidence to the people of Demon City. He cannot have them think that he was injured since morale was too important to Demon City.

It was great that Zhao Hai’s wound cannot be seen by the naked eye. Because of this, the people of Demon City were completely unaware. The only thing they witnessed was Zhao Hai’s battle with the other God-ranked Demons.

After all, the Domains were very large and they were fighting mid-air. Even if they were far away, the people in Demon City can still see them. They saw Zhao Hai manage to fend off five attackers. And although they didn’t see Shiying being captured, they were still able to witness Zhao Hai retreating safely. Now that he had appeared in the city, it was no wonder that he was greeted with huge cheers.

After appearing in the city, Zhao Hai told the guards to stay put once more before entering his Bone Dragon to recover. He wasn’t even expecting that because of his relationship with Berry, he was able to acquire a soul cultivation method.

Zhao Hai had now recovered to his normal state, which made Laura and the others relaxed. When then they saw Zhao Hai spurt out blood, all of them had been worried to death.

After seeing that Zhao Hai was doing well, Laura then pointed towards the corner of the room, where the entangled Shiying was placed. Shiying was already sober from his bewilderment, he really didn’t expect that a God-ranked expert such as him would actually be captured.

When he was pulled into the Space, he intended to go all out fighting. However, he discovered that he was just a small insect in this terrifying place. The other party can just do whatever they want without him being able to resist.

He had witnessed Zhao Hai being healed, as well as the Space issuing a prompt. However, he was still completely clueless about what just happened. However, he knew one thing, the reason why Zhao Hai was able to fight them was due to this Space.

Zhao Hai stood up and walked towards Shiying, he smiled faintly to the Assassin and said, “I must congratulate you. You will be the first God-ranked undead to join my army. How does it feel? Do you feel honored?” Then Zhao Hai waved his hand, allowing Shiying to speak. The Assassin looked coldly at Zhao Hai and said, “The Great Demon King is all-powerful! All of those who offend him will suffer.”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile towards Shiying and said, “Not necessarily. I know that the Great Demon King is formidable. Although the Demons have been silent for tens of thousands of years, he still managed to make a plan that shocked not just me, but I believe the Divine Race as well. However, do you really think that he could do anything to me? The Demons have completely underestimated the Ark Continent. I’m afraid that the one who wouldn’t get a good ending would be the Demons.”

Shiying looked at Zhao Hai, he didn’t know what to say. Zhao Hai smiled at him as he made a signal to Cai’er. Without any hesitation, Cai’er twisted Shiying’s neck, breaking his spine in the process. Shiying’s vitality might be formidable, but it was completely useless in the Space. If Zhao Hai wanted to kill him here, then there was no doubt that he would certainly die.

Shiying quickly died from Cai’er’s move. Zhao Hai wasn’t polite as he immediately turned the Assassin into an undead.

But Zhao Hai didn’t expect that as he turned Shiying into an undead, a prompt was suddenly heard, “Mutant Robot Assassin detected. Copying his abilities and integrating it to all Assassin-class robots in the Space. Space’s Assassin robots now has God-rank strength.”

Zhao Hai stared, then a huge sense of happiness washed over his entire being. He never expected this outcome. Although he only had a small number of assassin undead, there were still more than 500. For Zhao Hai’s side, this development was too significant.

Most importantly, this discovery informed Zhao Hai about the method to turn his undead into God-ranked. When Zhao Hai became God-ranked before, he didn’t manage to hear anything about the undead. Zhao Hai even thought that the undead had already reached their peak, unable to advance any further. But there was actually a method to strengthen them. This was a very crucial discovery.

Laura and the others heard about the Space’s prompt as well. They weren’t expecting this to happen. Zhao Hai laughed in happiness as he turned to Laura and said, “Today is a very good day. We should celebrate. I think it would be great if we do it in Demon City.” Naturally, the others didn’t oppose to this idea. Zhao Hai smiled faintly as he brought Berry and Shue to appear in Demon City. At this moment, the people inside the city were talking about the recent fight that just happened. When they saw Zhao Hai come out, all of them cheered in one voice.

Zhao Hai looked at all of them and smiled. Then he stood on his Bone Dragon as he made the undead Shiying appear and told everyone, “I have good news! During the fight with the Demons, we managed to kill a crucial character to the Demon Realm. This is a God-ranked Demon, and now he is a member of my undead army!!”

Chapter 712: Unexpected Development, The Divine Race Has Arrived

The people in Demon City couldn’t help but stare at Zhao Hai. This was a God-ranked expert, a thing that only existed in legend. But now, it actually appeared in front of them, moreover, it has been killed and turned into undead!

But even with how unfathomable this was, all of them still believed in Zhao Hai. In their minds, Zhao Hai’s exploits have always been out of the ordinary. Therefore, upon hearing Zhao Hai’s announcement, a short dullness was experienced before the entire city blew up in cheers. The celebration was too loud that even the Demon Dragon King was able to hear it.

Upon hearing the cheers, the Demon Dragon King’s complexion couldn’t help but turn cloudier. He had a faint understanding about what this cheer represented. It seems like Shiying had suffered an unfortunate end.

The Demon Dragon King couldn’t help but sigh, he was truly speechless now. Their attack on the Ark Continent didn’t turn out as simple as they had thought, in fact, it was actually very difficult.

At this time, the sky in the distance suddenly had a huge change. Blood red radiance was seen coming from the Radiant Empire’s direction. Along with this red light, an incomparably huge blood red formation suddenly appeared. The formation seemed to cover the entire Radiant Empire, it slowly rose up as it clashed with the sky.

Zhao Hai’s complexion changed as his figure flashed, bringing Berry and Shue back into the Space. Then without saying any words to Laura and the others, he disappeared once more and reappeared in the border between the Buddha Empire and the Radiant Empire. He looked at the misty Radiant Empire in the distance, his expression difficult to describe.

The blood red formation slowly rose as the white mist covering the Radiant Empire slowly vanished. When the mist vanished, Zhao Hai immediately used his Divine Sense to scour the Empire, what he found out made his expression turn extremely sour.

He hasn’t visited the Ocean Waves Dynasty before, therefore he wasn’t aware of the situation inside. Then afterwards, while the Radiant Church usurped the Empire, he was in another place, unable to divert his attention to there. When he managed to make time, the mist had already covered the entire Empire, even his God-rank Divine Sense was unable to find anything out. In the end, Zhao Hai can only wait and see what would eventually happen.

The Ocean Waves Dynasty was one of the five powerful nations in the Continent. Although their strength wasn’t very good, their navies were still invincible. And in fact, the Dynasty was even the richest nation in the entire continent, this was because of their great marine trade.

As a country gets richer, their citizen’s moral requirements also increase. This made it rare for men in this country to have several wives. Because of this, the Dynasty population couldn’t be compared to the other great nations.

The reason as to why the Dynasty was  placed on the same level as the other Empires was because they took their navy very seriously, pumping huge amounts of money in order to gain naval superiority. This allowed them to hold their heads up in front of the other nations, even if their army wasn’t that great. It was their naval strength, not their population, that made them great.

When Zhao Hai’s Divine Sense swept through the first city of the Empire, he immediately found what was wrong. The whole city was extremely empty. Aside from the people of the Church, the entire city’s population have all died.

Everyone, it didn’t matter if they were women, children, elderly, or able bodied men. All of them seemed to be trapped in the city, like magic beasts ripe for slaughter. No living witnesses managed to survive.

The cause of death was also very unusual, all of them turned into a shriveled corpse. Their blood and flesh seemed to have been sucked out, only their skin and bones were left behind.

Under the bodies of these people were traces of a magic formation. It was quite obvious that the Radiant Church had grouped these people up in this place and then killed them, carrying a ceremony similar to sacrificial offering. However, this formation was actually used to make a connection towards the Divine Realm.

Zhao Hai’s face turned pale, his eyes spewing out flames of hatred. He didn’t expect the Divine Race to be as crazy as the Demons. The Demons used magic beasts in order to activate their Blood Void, however, the Radiant Church actually used living people, the entire population of the Ocean Waves Dynasty as the conduit for their formation!

Shue and the others had also seen this situation, they didn’t think that the Radiant Church and the Divine Race would be this merciless. Zhao Hai’s expression turned uglier and uglier as time passed by. His chest constantly heaving up and down, and when he couldn’t bear it anymore, he suddenly coughed up blood.

Shue looked with great surprise as he supported Zhao Hai, “Young Master, what happened? Young Master, what’s wrong?!”

Zhao Hai looked forward as he loudly shouted, “Divine Race! I, Zhao Hai, will surely slaughter all of you!!” Then he flashed into the Space. When he arrived inside, Laura and the others immediately rushed over. At this time the Space suddenly issued a prompt, “Host is undergoing major mental destabilization. Adjusting Host’s mental state. The potential of the Host’s body has been stimulated. Host’s strength has been improved, soul has been improved.”

However, nobody had the time to care about this. Laura and the others surrounded Zhao Hai, not knowing about what just happened to him.

Zhao Hai looked at the others and then smiled bitterly as he said, “Tell the Patriarchs and Emperors about what just happened. Make the people in Demon City retreat, we’ll proceed to the second step of the plan. Make the eastern and southern parts of the Buddha Empire enter in first level alert. Shue, take me to the Blood Point. Bubble, absorb me and the Blood Pond into your body.”

After Zhao Hai’s command, the people in the Space immediately made their move. Shue quickly took Zhao Hai to the side of the Blood Pond. Then Bubble changed his shape as he absorbed Zhao Hai and the Blood Pond. At this moment, Shiying appeared, carrying a black bead in his hand. He gave the bead to Shue as he said, “These will be useful to the Young Master.” Shue stared, he didn’t think that Shiying would speak at a time like this, he didn’t know what to say.

But Zhao Hai actually gave a nod to Shue, so he didn’t hesitate and threw the beads towards Bubble’s body. Then when the bead hit Bubble, he immediately rotated at fast speeds. Laura and the others can almost feel that the energy of the entire Space has been concentrated towards the Bubble’s body.

After watching Zhao Hai, Laura immediately said, “What are we doing here, we need to act on Brother Hai’s orders. Let the Patriarchs and the Emperors know about the current development, have all of them prepare their strengths since the Divine Race had come.” Although they were still worried about Zhao Hai, they needed to clench their teeth as they turned and went inside the villa. Only Shue and Berry were left to oversee Bubble. Bubble was still spinning, and he was getting faster and faster.

Just as Zhao Hai entered the Space, the huge formation in the Radiant Empire suddenly rotated. And at the same time, another formation descended from the sky. This formation seemed to have been prepared for a long time. However, it was not blood red, instead, it gave off a white light, giving people a very sacred feeling.

It wasn’t only Zhao Hai who managed to notice this formation. The Beastmen could even see faint traces of these two massive formations. They were just too high up and enormous that they seem to rival even the moon in the sky. It was actually difficult to miss it.

The Demon Dragon King stared blankly at the two formations. He didn’t know why, but he seemed to dislike these formations, their aura elicited disgust deep inside him.

Then without much thinking, the Demon Dragon King turned to the Archer and said, “Herd, you go and return to the Demon Realm, report this to the Great Demon King. It’s possible that the Divine Race had already made their move. Moreover, it seems like it wouldn’t bade well for us. Make them prepare for the future. We’ll continue to monitor the developments here. If there are instructions, then return here immediately.”

Herd didn’t dare to neglect this order, he gave a nod as he quickly dashed towards the rift. At this time, the Lich arrived by the Demon Dragon King and said, “Demon Dragon, do you really think that the Divine Race is behind this?”

Demon Dragon nodded, “Correct, you might not know, but His Highness has been sending out many scouts towards the Ark Continent. These scouts were able to discover the Radiant Church as well as their connection to the Divine Race. The reason why the Great Demon King decided to move this time is because he knew that the Divine Race wouldn’t be able to arrive soon. He wanted to take control of the continent before the Divine Race even arrives. This is why he sent the five of us here, he knew that we would be fighting with the Divine Race in the future, so it would be useless to rely on 9th ranks. The Divine Race is very strong. We never expected them to come this soon.”

The Lich looked at the two magic formations and said, “These two formations, have you seen them before?”

The Demon Dragon King shook his head and replied, “I haven’t but it looks like it has the same function as the Blood Void. It seems to have unusual origins as well.”

The Lich nodded, unlike the Humans, who weren’t aware of the Divine Race for a long time, the Demons already knew that the Divine Race existed. Moreover, they were also aware about their methods, this was the reason why the Demon Dragon King was quite worried.

The two formations in the sky slowly approached each other, their rotations going faster and faster. Both of them looked like two enormous stone mills, intent on grinding the skies, moving in opposite directions to each other.

As the two formations got closer, their rotations got faster and faster. Then when they met, a huge explosion was suddenly heard, Heaven and Earth seemed to be have all of its colors removed.

Chapter 713: Change of Laws, Beginning of Chaos

Along with this deafening sound, the entire Ark Continent was also covered with a white radiance. This light was as bright as the noon sun. Everyone in the continent felt their eyes sting, all of them called out in alarm as they quickly closed their eyes.

The Demon Dragon King’s group were shocked at this white light. They were God-ranked experts, therefore, this light had no effect on them. What shocked them was what came along with the white light. A spatial crack appeared in the sky and was getting bigger and bigger. Then suddenly, land can be seen going through the rift. It seems like the land was causing the crack to expand. The tearing continued as the rift became as large as half of the entire Radiant Empire. Then the land slowly descended before it fell and caused a huge bang. This cause the entire Ark Continent to tremble.

At this moment, the Demon Dragon King’s expression changed, he turned his head to the Lich and said, “White Ghost, try to feel it. The continent’s suppression has vanished.”

White Ghost stared, then his expression changed as well, he confirmed, “The suppression had indeed vanished. What is this all about?”

The Demon Dragon King was now quite pale as he replied, “The Divine Race, them and the Radiant Church had worked together to produce these two large magic formations, changing the Ark Continent’s Law of Heaven and Earth. Later on, God-ranked experts entering the continent wouldn’t be met with suppression anymore. White Ghost, you go back and report this to His Majesty. Ask him to organize all of our God-ranked experts and have them enter the continent. Otherwise, our plans would be placed into danger.”

After hearing the Demon Dragon King, the Lich’s expression changed, he immediately nodded and then turned around as he flew towards the spatial rift. The Demon Dragon King had a cold look on his face as he muttered, “Good, Divine Race, good job. But the ownership of this land has yet to be decided!’

Then the Demon Dragon King flew over his camp as he looked down at all Demons and said, “Fortify the camp. All 9th ranks for a group of ten each. If a God-rank comes attacking, then don’t hesitate to link your souls and self-destruct. There should be no hesitation! Defend the camp to your full capability!”

This was basically a suicide order. However, there wasn’t any changes to the expressions of these Demons. All of them nodded and without any pauses, all 9th ranks grouped themselves up into tens. Each group composed on combat squad. All of them were waiting outside the camp, in full anticipation for a fight.

The Demon Dragon King clearly knew that although God-ranked experts can be wounded by exploding 9th ranks, this only applied to those who had yet to comprehend a Domain. As for those God-ranks who had a Domain, 9th rank explosions were completely useless.

However, the strength of linked souls were different. The explosion of ten linked 9th ranks was almost equivalent to a God-ranked expert. The damage should be quite ample. Even if the other party had comprehended a level 2 Domain, he would still be unable to stop this kind of attack.

Zhao Hai’s prior guess was correct, Domains were truly divided into levels. As for the levels, there were False Gods, people who just became God-rank and haven’t managed to comprehend a Domain yet. Berry and Shue were among these people.

Then there were people like the Archer, Knight, and Assassin. Although they had comprehended a Domain, they weren’t very flexible in using them, their Domains were limited when it came to form. They belong to 1st Level Gods, this was where God-ranks officially reach Godhood.

After that was the level of the Demon Dragon King and the Lich. Their Domains were flexible, and they had many forms to transform into. Their Domains also had an avatar form that can fight by itself. They were called 2nd level Gods, or Highgods.

On the top of all God-ranked experts were Saint Gods. Only a few people can reach this rank. Their strengths were extremely powerful. With one raise of the hand, they can turn Heaven and Earth upside down. When they stamp their feet, mountains move. They were the strongest God-ranks. Even in the Demon Realm, these people were extremely rare. It was said that everyone who managed to reach this level had gone to a mysterious place. Nobody knew where it was, only those who managed to become Saint Gods were able to know.

It was precisely because of the absence of Saint Gods that the top existences in the Demon Realm had become people like the Demon Dragon King, the Highgods. Even the Great Demon King would need to discuss with them whenever he needed something to be done, he simply cannot force them.

But the reason why these people listened to the Great Demon King was due to three things. First, it was because the Great Demon King was a good leader. Second, because the Great Demon King was also a Highgod. Third, and most importantly, only the Great Demon King had the means to contact the Saint Gods. Because of this, nobody dared to challenge the rule of the Great Demon King.

However, even if one was God-ranked in the Demon Realm, he couldn’t just easily wage war against any Demon Army. Although God-ranks were indeed powerful, they were still completely susceptible to the soul-linked attacks by the Demons. Once Demons concentrated their strengths, the result was very astonishing.

Moreover, majority of Demons in the Demon realm grew up fighting. This made all of them fearless towards death. Once they were pushed too far back, then they wouldn’t hesitate to blow themselves up. Because of this, in addition to strength, God-ranks also need influence in order to get respect. This was the reason why the Demon Dragon King was also the northwest king of the Demon Realm.

The Demon Realm had a certain understanding with regards to the Divine Race. Because of this, after the Demon Dragon King discovered the changes in the laws, he immediately issued a command of self-sacrifice to his men. There were plenty of God-ranked experts in the Divine Realm. The only way to push them back was through the threat of Demonic core explosions.

While he issued his commands, the Demon Dragon King was completely unaware that he was heard by Cai’er. Although Zhao Hai was currently healing inside Bubble while Laura and the others were busying themselves by relaying information to the various Patriarchs and Emperors of the Ark Continent, Cai’er was also listening to the developments in the Continent. Moreover, she had become stricter in her gathering of information.

When the Demon Dragon King said that the laws had changed, Cai’er’s expression changed. She knew what this meant for the Ark Continent.

The reason why Zhao Hai was confident in going against the Divine Race and the Demons was because he was relying on the Ark Continent’s law. The law that forbade the existence of God-ranked experts. Because of this law, Zhao Hai and the others would be able to become equals with the God-ranked experts. But now that the laws have changed, both Demons and Divines would be able to send out swathes of God-ranks to the Ark Continent without any repercussions. This would diminish the Ark Continent’s means to defend itself.

Cai’er immediately relayed this information over to Laura and the others. When they heard this, all of them couldn’t help but stop what they were doing. They weren’t expecting the Divine Race to play this big move. Their hand was too great, it was akin to removing a huge advantage of the Ark Continent. At this point, what could the Ark Continent do in order to win?

While they were in  shock, Laura being competent woman,  managed to calm herself quickly as she said, “Don’t be upset. Let’s relay this news to the powers of the continent as well. Cai’er, immediately gather all assassin-class undead and see whether some of them are able to use a Domain. Then have them on standby, closely monitoring the movements of both the Demons and the Divine Race. Also, immediately tell the Buddha Emperor to hasten the evacuation, use the Space if possible but make sure that it doesn’t get discovered, stick to using the spatial rights and have them sent to the Lyon Empire. Have the Dwarves, Elves, and Beastmen prepare their 9th rank experts as well as their Divine Artifacts, then move them to the Buddha Empire. Inform the Lyon Empire and the Rosen Empire to prepare their experts as well and have them sent to the Buddha Empire. These were the emergency orders that Brother Hai prepared ahead of time.”

Among Zhao Hai’s wives, one must say that the earliest one was Meg. However, with Meg’s disposition, she wasn’t fit to become a leader. On the other hand, Laura was Zhao Hai’s second and also had the talent to be a leader. This gave her a high status compared to the other wives. Even Lizzy and Megan chose to listen to her. When Zhao Hai healed himself, Laura immediately became the default leader. Her orders were akin to Zhao Hai’s own.

The women immediately nodded and started to do their jobs. While telling the powers of the continent, they deliberately hid the fact that Zhao Hai was injured. Instead, they told them that Zhao Hai was currently focused on finding ways to suppress the Demons and the Divines. All of these actions were done in order to keep the morale stable.

At this point, everyone in the continent were aware as to how strong Zhao Hai was. Moreover, the fact that Zhao Hai was God-rank was also relayed to the other powers. The fact that he had killed another God-rank was also relayed. This was to increase morale. But now that the Divine Race had descended, another wave of anxiety had appeared on the continent. If the fact that Zhao Hai being injured was revealed, then the continent would surely fall into chaos.

Laura knew that Zhao Hai was the Ark Continent’s sole pillar of hope. Once Zhao Hai falls, the continent would surely fall alongside him. At that time, there would be no army that would have the strength to resist. Nobody would be able to stop the advance of both the Demons and the Divine Race.

Chapter 714: Dao Lotus

Zhao Hai was lying down on the Blood Pond. To be honest, ever since he came to the Ark Continent, this was the first breakthrough that he had experienced by himself, all other breakthroughs were brought to him by the Space. This time’s breakthrough made Zhao Hai sense a qualitative increase to his own strength. However, he didn’t feel like he had reached his peak, his strength can still be promoted.

This was the reason why in addition to lying down on the Blood Pond, Zhao Hai decided to be placed inside Bubble’s body. The Blood Pond was made out of the blood of a Divine, the energy within it was tyrannical. However, Bubble was a master of water, this allowed him to control how strong the blood’s actions was, nourishing Zhao Hai properly in the process.

Zhao Hai wasn’t afraid of exhausting the energy in the Blood Pond. The Space had already recorded its energy patterns and could just recreate an endless supply of it in the future.

On the other hand, Zhao Hai wasn’t aware that when he turned Shiying into an undead, his wisdom and intelligence was still kept intact. Shiying was a God-ranked assassin, he had a devious wisdom and formidable intellect, but he was now under Zhao Hai’s side, because of this, Shiying gave Shue his Demonic Core. He wanted Shue to hand the core over to Zhao Hai to absorb.

Zhao Hdi didn’t expect Shiying to do this. He still couldn’t understand why Shiying, who had kept his wisdom, would do this. However, he wasn’t afraid of of any harm. After all, Shiying was unable to have evil intentions towards Zhao Hai since the Space already suppressed him. Because of this, Zhao Hai agreed to absorb the Demonic Core.

What Zhao Hai thought was correct. Shiying was now an undead, and like what the Space said, he was like robot. A robot programmed to have perfect loyalty towards Zhao Hai. It was impossible for the undead to betray the Space’s host.

Since Zhao Hai wanted to increase his strength, then Shying would naturally be willing to help, making him offer his own Demonic Core.

Now that Shiying had been turned into an undead, his energy source has now been shifted to the Space. Because of this, the Demonic Core had become useless.

The energy in the Blood Pond, although formidable, wasn’t that abundant in energy. A Demonic Core was different, it was the source of a Demon’s entire strength, the reason why they were so strong. Because of this, once the Demonic Core’s energy entered Zhao Hai’s body, Zhao Hai immediately felt immeasurable pain in his meridians.

Compared to Shue’s pain, Zhao Hai’s suffering was much more. However, Zhao Hai didn’t move, he endured it as he kept lying down inside the Blood Pond, maintaining a peaceful state of mind.

This was the most painful time during Zhao Hai’s promotion. However, this was something that he needed to experience. His previous promotions were too smooth, this made his soul unable to catch up. This was the reason why he had been injured during his fight with the Demon Dragon King.

The pain that he was experiencing actually helped in increasing his spiritual force. Now that his body and soul has been upgraded, Zhao Hai was now a more well-rounded powerhouse.

Zhao Hai continued lying down in the Blood Pond, not even aware that he has been wrapped up by a lotus flower that has entered the Blood Pond. This was something that Bubble decided to do. Naturally, this wasn’t done in order to harm Zhao Hai. This was because Bubble felt that the lotus flower would have big use to Zhao Hai’s current state. Now that Zhao Hai was focused on maintaining his peace of mind, he simply didn’t have the capacity to talk to Bubble. At the same time, Bubble didn’t dare to disturb Zhao Hai. Because of this, he made his own decision to absorb the lotus flower into the Blood Pond. Then, with his own strength, refine Zhao Hai along with the lotus flower and the Blood Pond.

Zhao Hai didn’t know for how long, but he had started to feel that the energy that was rampaging through his body had become calm. And strangely, it seems like the energy was now following a strange and long journey. This route included all of his meridians, even the one in his forehead.

Zhao Hai gawked, he couldn’t help but take a look at what was happening to his body. At his lower navel, a colorful mass has been absorbing energy from the outside. On his chest was a strange lotus pattern with the petals wide open. And on his head was a small projection of Zhao Hai, meditating. This projection had a silver hair that extended into the void, seemingly to no end.

This scene made Zhao Hai blankly stare. Zhao Hai was a fan of novels, and he was clear about what these things were. In China, these spots were called dantian. There was the Lower Dantian(Xià Dāntián), placed below the navel. The Middle Dantian(Zhōng Dāntián), placed at the heart. And lastly the Upper Dantian(Shàng Dāntián), at the forehead between one’s two eyes.

Although Zhao Hai knew about these three points from the start, he didn’t mind them too much since he was practicing Battle Qi and Magic. He also thought that these three points were just something that was made up by the ancient Chinese. But now, it seems like these weren’t useless  at all.

Zhao Hai’s strength was centered on his Lower Dantian. Moreover, he had discovered that this was where his body’s physical strength came from.

Zhao Hai then used his Divine Sense towards his Middle Dantian, where the lotus flower was currently attached. Zhao Hai immediately investigated the lotus flower, this lotus was a treasure of the Heavens, it wasn’t even from the Ark Continent. A lotus seed had fallen down from an unknown space and arrived in the continent. Then the seed was buried deep down as it was nourished by the Continent’s energy.

Then after numerous years passed by, in the deep dark sea, the lotus seed suddenly turned into something like a small lake. Then that small lake slowly grew up and after many years, it managed to change its surroundings. The lotus roots continued to extend as it rooted itself on the surrounding rocks. Then when the lotus bloomed, Zhao Hai saw something that was very familiar to him. It was actually the same lotus that he saw from the Soul Sucking Reef!

The roots of this lotus had a ying-yang cross section. It’s roots along the rocks and soil formed an eight trigrams pattern, a pattern that was very much in line with the Heavenly Dao. This lotus, in turn, had become the world’s most important treasure, the Dao Lotus.

Bubble felt that this lotus would be useful for Zhao Hai, this made him decide to absorb it into his body, accidentally refining it and making it Zhao Hai’s Life Treasure. This lotus flower seemed to agree to this arrangement as it didn’t make any resistance to the refinement. One could say that the capabilities of this lotus was endless. It’s benefit to Zhao Hai couldn’t be easily described. Compared to the Divine Artifacts of the Beastmen, Dwarves, and Elves, this Dao Lotus was completely on another level.

Zhao Hai slowly drew his Divine Sense back. When he connected his Divine Sense with the Dao Lotus, he seemed to feel changes to himself, he had felt how mysterious the Heaven and Earth was. It seemed like he was in a state of understanding but also unknowing. But one thing that Zhao Hai knew was the fact that this Dao Lotus had a lot of functions. It can attack the enemy, it can defend, it can trap them, and it can even heal wounds. It was a treasure with tons of other uses.

The reason why this Dao Lotus was this strong was because of its growth. During its germination period up until it was absorbed into the Space, the lotus didn’t experience any stresses in its entire life. This caused its roots to go in line with the Heavenly Dao, forming an eight trigrams pattern as well as developing the yin-yang symbol. This made it possible for the lotus to make use of all the five elements.

Having this magical treasure made Zhao Hai extremely happy. But he still continued to use his Divine Sense to scan his Upper Dantian. However, Zhao Hai didn’t think that when his Divine Sense entered his upper dantian and scanned the little man, it was immediately sucked into nothingness. Because of this shock, Zhao Hai woke up. At the same time he also understood that this little man was the source of his Divine Sense. However, it seems like the little man’s hair had no traces of spiritual force.

When Zhao Hai opened his eye, he discovered that he was still inside Bubble’s body, lying down inside the Blood Pond. Therefore, Zhao Hai immediately said, “Bubble, take me out” Bubble’s body shook as Zhao Hai exited, the Blood Pool has been restored to its original position as well. Zhao Hai looked at Bubble and said, “Bubble, who told you to place the lotus flower into the Blood Pond?”

Bubble quickly replied, “It was in my own discretion, Young Master. Did Bubble make a mistake? I really don’t have an excuse to tell you, I just felt that the lotus would be fruitful in your current state, so I decided to absorb it and place it into the Blood Pond. Did I harm the Young Master?”

Zhao Hai laughed and then hugged Bubble, “No, no, what you did was right. Hahaha. Well done, Bubble, well done. You just made your Young Master very happy!”

At this time, Berry responded, she arrived hastily right beside Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, how are you? Are you doing fine?” Shue also came over, looking eagerly at Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “I’m alright, not only alright, my strength has been improved as well. Hahahaha. I’ve made you all worried. Right, Berry, how long was I out?”

Berry quickly replied, “Not that long, only more than a day. But Brother Hai, while you were gone, something happened. The Divine Race had managed to establish two large formations. When they arrived at the Ark Continent, they also changed the laws of the Ark Continent. In the future, God-ranks would no longer be suppressed in the continent.”

Zhao Hai stared for a moment, then he smiled and said, “These Divines are really good. This was surely not planned for a day or two. It seems like they had been on to this plan for a long time. It seems like they are the reason why the Ark Continent hasn’t produced a God-ranked expert in such a long time.”

Chapter 715: Universe Grand Dao

Zhao Hai already had a faint idea about this aspect. But when he connected with the Dao Lotus and had a feel of the Heavens and the Earth, he was even more convinced about it. And with the report that he had received, he was now quite assured that the reason why there were no God-ranks that had ascended from the continent after all this time was because of an interference done by the Divine Race.

Zhao Hai knew that changing the Laws was very difficult. What is a law? Actually, it was a type of projection of the Dao. And this Dao was separated into Yin and Yang. If the things that are normal to the Ark Continent were Yang, then those suppressed by it were the Yin.

A combination of Yin and Yang becomes a plane. And the reason why this plane existed was because of the Dao. Now that the Divine Race had broken the Laws of the Continent, the entire plane where the continent resides has become unstable. This time, not only did the Divine Race break the laws of the Ark Continent, it also broke the laws of many other planes.

The universe is comprised of multiple planes. And the reason that these planes exist and was able to act independently was also because of the universe. Now that the balance of the Ark Continent has been broken, then it was akin to breaking a part of the universe. As for what influence this action did, Zhao Hai had no way to know. However, he can be assured that the effects wouldn’t be small.

If the universe is composed of countless planes, then each plane would be like a domino that made up the universe. As long as it stood there and wasn’t moved, then there wouldn’t be any influence towards the other pieces. But once one domino fell, then all others next to it would definitely be affected as well. No matter how long or what effects it had, there will be events that would happen as a reaction.

However, Zhao Hai believed that the Universal Grand Dao has a way to repair itself. Just like how the Ark Continent had been punctured by the Demons and the Divine Race, in the end, it still managed to keep the continent’s space intact.

Zhao Hai also believed that there was an avenue for the Universe to adjust. The Universe is all about balance, yin and yang. If the Ark Continent were to be destroyed, then another place somewhere would be affected in order to balance everything out.

However, Zhao Hai had no idea how long this adjustment would occur. And as to the changes that would happen in the Ark Continent, it was difficult to say.

Because of this Grand Dao, it was very difficult to change the laws of a plane. The Divine Race needed to prepare for tens of thousands of years. And if nobody from the Ark Continent were to ascend during that time, then their job would be much easier.

After all, compared to the Ark Continent, the Divine Realm’s strength is leagues higher. They can definitely make a seal to inhibit the ascent of God-ranks from the Ark Continent. Setting wide-scale formations was easier done in the Ark Continent compared to the Divine Realm.

At this moment, Zhao Hai had an idea. He immediately convened all the 9th ranks in the Space. The majority of these 9th ranks were from the Carrion Swamp, there was also Origin Sword Saint who was invited by Zhao Hai. These people were among the oldest 9th ranks in existence. Zhao Hai had seen how strong they were. However, after all these years, they were still unable to reach the next step, this made Zhao Hai quite confused.

But now, he knew that this was a plot done by the Divine Realm. If this was really it, then it may be possible for these people to break into God-rank after going back to the continent.

These 9th ranks have trained inside Zhao Hai’s Space for a long time. Although their strengths were increased, they were still yet to upgrade into God-rank. Zhao Hai wanted to try having them go back to the Continent and see whether they can be promoted to God-rank.

When these 9th ranks heard Zhao Hai’s idea, all of them immediately agreed since. After all, aside from the Origin Sword Saint, all of these people were Zhao Hai’s subordinate. At the same time, the Origin Sword Saint had been training for a long time, he knew that he wouldn’t live for long if he wasn’t able to break through to God-rank, therefore, he also agreed to the idea.

To these 9th ranks, their biggest wish was to reach God-rank. Only then can they have greater strength as well as longer lifespans.

Zhao Hai didn’t have them exit directly to the battlefield. Instead, he had them go to the Black Wasteland first. In any case, the laws present there was the same as anywhere else in the continent.

After sending these people off, Zhao Hai immediately returned to the living room. He was inside Bubble’s body for more than a day, so he was clueless about what was currently happening outside. The only thing he knew about was the change in the Ark Continent’s laws. The reason why Zhao Hai was anxious to let the 9th ranks out was because he was eager to have them break through, only then would their strengths be improved.

When Zhao Hai entered the room, he saw Laura and the others being busy. Everyone looked thin and pale. When they saw Zhao Hai come, they immediately stopped what they were doing and came over. Zhao Hai looked at their faces and said, “Why do all of you look fatigued? Why are you still busy? What is going on outside?”

Laura, with dark circles under her eyes, forced a smile and said, “We’re fine. But Brother Hai, how about you? Are you doing well?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Rest assured, I’m already fine. If the outside situation isn’t that bad, then you should go and take a rest. You’ve been going at it for two days.”

Laura nodded and said, “Everything is almost done, large thanks to Cai’er. Brother Hai, the defenders in Demon City have already retreated. At this moment, the Demons have gone into full defense. So we decided to move the army, there was no longer any significance in having them defend Demon City anymore. Also, we’ve already had the various armies enter the Buddha Empire. All of the refugees in the Buddha Empire are gone as well, we used spatial rifts to have them moved quickly. Now, the Buddha Empire is already going according to your plan. It has been turned into huge battlefield.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “That’s good. At this moment, we have more than 500 God-ranked experts. And I already had Little Wen and Origin Sword Saint’s group exit the Space. Now that the laws of the Ark Continent has been changed, I want to see if there are some of them that are able to break through to God-rank. All of them are locals of the Ark Continent and still haven’t broken through even while inside the Space. I think that their cultivation is still not compatible with the Space. So I might as well have them break through their cultivation outside.”

Laura nodded, then she quickly replied, “Although they had their strengths improved inside the Space, they were still yet to break through. It’s a good idea to have them go out and try breaking through. At this moment, there aren’t any further movements coming from the Divine Race. I don’t know what they are planning to do.” Zhao Hai nodded, “Tell me everything that happened.”

Laura replied, “Brother Hai, take a look.” Then Laura turned her head to Cai’er and said, “Cai’er, let Brother Hai see the recording.”

Cai’er nodded, then she played the scene of the two huge magic formation as well as the spatial rift caused by the descending piece of land. After that, a video of the conversation between the Demon Dragon King and the Lich was shown.

Zhao Hai calmly looked at the monitor until everything was finished. Then he had Cai’er show the map of the continent. At this time, there were a dense group of red dots on the Buddha Empire. Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I didn’t think that there would be this much diversity in the continent’s army.”

Lizzy nodded as she said, “The current army of Demon City has fallen back to Rising Sun City. Rising Sun City, Lower Bank City, South Plain City, Water Wheel City, Broad Flat City have coordinated with themselves and had become one defensive line. Aside from the army in Demon City, there were also 200 thousand soldiers from the Buddha Empire, 50 thousand Beast Knights and 100 thousand infantry from the Lyon Empire, 50 thousand heavy infantry and 150 thousand normal infantry from the Rosen Empire, 200 Mages and 5000 archers from the Elves, and 50 thousand soldiers from the Dwarves. Altogether, there are more than 1 million troops separated amongst those five cities.”

Zhao Hai nodded, Rising Sun City was yet another fortress not far from Demon City. The walls of this city were quite thick. Moreover, its infrastructure was very well developed. Establishing a defense in this City would be a very good idea. It had good strategic placement. Just like in Demon City, Rising Sun City would be a good place to besiege.

Then Lizzy added, “Then Ashi river’s east bank has become another line of defense. There are two hundred channels connected to this river. Another 1.5 million troops are present here. Their main purpose is to either reinforce Rising Sun City and the other cities or aid them in their retreat.”

Zhao Hai nodded, Ashi river is the Buddha Empire’s second major river. It’s main and side branches stretched through almost the entire Buddha Empire. With the help of Zhao Hai’s Space, the river had now been turned into a defensive line.

Lizzy continued, “Then there’s Hard Fang City, White City, Upper Bank City, White Oyster City, Golden Crown City, Ox City, and other cities close to them who made up the bulk of the Buddha Empire’s defense. A total of 3 million troops are present on these places, 1 million Beastmen, 1 million Humans, 500 thousand Dwarves, 100 thousand Elves, and 400 thousand Fishmen who are in the surrounding rivers. Moreover, there are also troops present in the Imperial Capital.”

Chapter 716: Rising Sun City

When he heard Lizzy’s answer, Zhao Hai gave a satisfied nod and said, “Good, good. These defensive lines wouldn’t only help in dealing with the Demons, it will also help with resisting the Divine Race as well. Also, we should consider a path of retreat. If we turtle up in the Buddha Empire for too long, the Demons and Divine Race might join up to deal with us. On the other hand, if we are able to give up some areas of the Empire, then it might become a battlefield between the Demons and the Divine Race. Make sure that there aren’t too much supplies on those defensive lines. It wouldn’t be easy to get those excess materials during a mass retreat.”

Lizzy and the others nodded, then Zhao Hai looked at their faces and said, “Now that everything has been arranged, you should go and rest. I’ll use this time to show my face to the masses, otherwise, my absence might cause some panic.”

Lizzy and the others nodded, then Laura looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, you should be careful. You’re very crucial to the survival of the continent. We’ll definitely lose this war if you fall.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Rest assured, I won’t die that easily. In fact, my disappearance has nothing to do with me being injured, I broke through. Since I needed a lot of energy, I decided to go inside Bubble and absorb the energy inside the Blood Pool. Moreover, Shiying gave me his Demonic Core, supplementing my energy. At the same time, the lotus has been placed in the Blood Pond as well. Now, the lotus has become my Life Treasure. At this point, even if the Demon Dragon King’s group gangs up on me, I still wouldn’t be in any danger. So you don’t need to worry.” When Laura and the others heard this, they let out a sigh of relief. They were afraid that Zhao Hai had encountered a heavy injury. If that were to happen, then the impact on the continent would be great.

Laura and the others’ worries about Zhao Hai were without no reason. If Zhao Hai was really hurt, then his Space wouldn’t he used. And if there was no Space, then the transfer of both troops and supplies would be very difficult. Most importantly, without the Space, the powerful undead wouldn’t be used. This will leave the defense of the Ark Continent to the various native powers. For these people to go against the Demons and the Divine Race would be a disaster for the entire continent. Zhao Hai looked at their expression and said, “It’s fine, there’s no need to worry about me. Just go and take a rest. I’ll go have a look outside, I’ll take care of the unfinished work. Cai’er is still here as well. Cai’er, I’ll have to trouble you.”

Cai’er smiled and said, “Young Master is too polite. I also have some control over the Space. Moreover, I really don’t need to take a rest. Young Master can rest assured that I shall arrange everything.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he turned to look at Laura and the others and said, “Well, you heard it. Go and take a good rest. Shue, Berry, you two go take a rest as well. The recent days have been too hard on you.”

Berry smiled and said, “I’m fine, Brother Hai. I’ll be coming along with you. I’m a God-rank expert as well, I don’t need to rest.”

Zhao Hai looked at Berry and then nodded, “Alright, then you and Shue go with me. You also need to undergo some fights before comprehending your own Domains.” Then Zhao Hai’s body disappeared along with Berry and Shue. Zhao Hai appeared in Demon City first, he wanted to see the situation there before heading towards Rising Sun city.

At this time, there weren’t any people in Demon City, everyone has retreated, leaving an empty city behind. Zhao Hai looked at the state of the city and couldn’t help but sigh. The present Demon City looked like a ghost town, not a single sound can be heard inside it. The ground was also filled with junk, making it look bleak. But on the bright side, there weren’t any deaths here because of a fight.

Shue also looked at Demon City and felt quite awkward. Just yesterday, this place was filled with people. Now, there wasn’t anyone in this place. The mercenaries and adventurers here had no choice but to give up their homes, it was a bit sad to think about.

Zhao Hai flew above Demon City and looked at the Demon camp in the distance. The Demons were still busy right now. It seems like they weren’t planning to stop building their city. Zhao Hai can even feel ten God-ranked aura emanating from their camp.

Zhao Hai sighed and said, “It looks like the Demons are catching up. But this is also good. The stronger they look, the more attention they would attract from the Divine Race. Let’s go and take a look at Rising Sun City. I’ll leave some God-ranked undead there before heading towards the Radiant Empire to take a look why the Divine Race are still yet to take action . After all, they just made a huge move.”

After saying that, Zhao Hai used the Space to immediately teleport to Rising Sun City. Rising Sun City was the closest place to Demon City. The distance between Rising Sun City and Demon City was only five small towns. Because of this, Rising Sun City was considered to be the second stronghold after Demon City.

Rising Sun City was quite a big place. It’s original population was about 1 million. At this time, it has become part of the defensive line. On the five towns between Demon City and Rising Sun City, other than mounted scouts, not a single person can be seen.

Besmir and the others had already used the spatial rift in order to fall back to Rising Sun City. When they obtained Zhao Hai’s order to retreat but didn’t see him, they became immediately worried.

It wasn’t only Besmir’s group who was worried. The people in Rising Sun City shared the same sentiment as well. Although Zhao Hai provided a spatial rift for transport, his absence made a lot of people very bothered.

Zhao Hai might have given the order for retreat, but the one who delivered it was actually an undead that was under his command. This wasn’t Zhao Hai’s usual actions, so it was not strange that people were quite anxious about the situation.

Everyone who retreated from Demon City were very worried. But fortunately, their hearts were still stable. In any case, Zhao Hai’s spatial rift have proven that he was still around. Maybe the reason for his absence was him being tied up someplace else.

Zhao Hai didn’t ride his Bone Dragon this time, instead, he just straight up appeared inside the city. When Zhao Hai came out, he was immediately spotted by some Elven Archers, who couldn’t help but cheer out loud.

Although these Elves were arrogant, they weren’t fools. When they saw Zhao Hai’s fight with the Demons, they immediately became aware of how strong he was. They also understood that without Zhao Hai, defending against the Demons would be impossible. Zhao Hai glanced at the people inside Rising Sun City. There were nearly 500 thousand people in the city, most of them were from Demon City. This made Zhao Hai feel relief. Then he turned his gaze towards the defenders on the walls and nodded as he waved his hand and summoned his undead outside the city.

This produced another round of cheers. These people couldn’t help but feel at ease upon seeing Zhao Hai. Normally, seeing undead would make them feel disgusted, but now, it seems like these undead had become much more lovable.

Zhao Hai flew down towards a nearby Dwarf and then smiled, “Brother, can you take me to the General’s residence? I have some matters to discuss.”

The Dwarf immediately replied, “Of course, Elder, come with me.” Then the Dwarf’s two small feet quickly led Zhao Hai towards the residence. Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile at this scene as he led Shue and Berry forward.

It didn’t take too long before they arrived in Rising Sun City’s City Lord Mansion. The City Lord’s Mansion has now become the General’s residence, Besmir and the others were here. The one with the highest authority in the City was now Besmir along with the Captains of the reinforcing armies.  But since their numbers weren’t much, Besmir still held a higher command.

When Zhao Hai arrived at the General’s residence, the guards at the gates immediately gave him a salute. Then one of them ran into the mansion without even saying anything, telling the people inside that “Mister Zhao Hai has come”. Zhao Hai was amused at the man, then he turned to the Dwarf that led him and then said, “Thank you brother. Here’s take this as gratitude.” Then he gave the Dwarf a bottle of his distilled milk wine.

The Dwarf was ecstatic at the gift, he immediately bowed to Zhao Hai and said, “Thank you very much, Elder Zhao Hai.” Then he turned around and ran. From his expression, it seems like he was eager to show off to his companions. Zhao Hai didn’t care much about it as he turned and walked into the General’s residence.

Just as he entered the mansion’s gate, he immediately saw Besmir, Julian, Gellar, and Barres along with several Human soldiers. The soldiers were all looking at Zhao Hai with curiosity.

Besmir led the others forward to greet Zhao Hai before giving a salute and said, “Mister, welcome back. Please follow us inside.’

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Alright, then I’ll be impolite. By the way, how are things going on here?”

Besmir quickly replied, “Mister, everything has been completely prepared. Not only here, the others cities have settled down as well.” Zhao Hai nodded. Then he followed the group into the mansion. The battle room was much larger than the one back in Demon City. Not only were there more maps present here, there were even some soldiers doing logistics as well as a sand table in the middle of the room.

Zhao Hai inspected the room and gave a satisfied nod and said, “This is a great room. This looks more like a battle room compared to the one in Demon City. Right, tell me the arrangements.” Then he went towards the sand table.

Besmir and the others arrived by the table as well. Besmir beckoned to the sand table and said, “Because of the short time, I can only make this simple sand table. Along with Rising Sun City, the other cities already has troops stationed inside as well as some mobile cavalry and scouts. In order to make the battle and retreat more convenient, we asked our Dwarf brothers to dig tunnels between the cities. However, since the workload is too much, there aren’t much results yet. I believe that after Rising Sun City gets connected to the other cities, then we can act more united compared to now. Retreat and reinforcements would be carried out through those tunnels, making transport a lot less troublesome.”

Chapter 717: Divine Artifact

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “That’s a good method. But it’s extremely time consuming. How about this, I’ll try to discuss with the Emperors of the continent and see if they can lend some Earth Mages to help with the operation. However, since the Dwarves are still the experts in digging, Earth Mages would be placed under their command. Julian, you must link the cities as soon as possible. After that, start to link them to the other small towns as well. This will make our battles more diverse. Remember to make as much interconnected tunnels as possible. The Demons have their methods, they may cause some collapse on the tunnels.”

Julian nodded and said, “Rest assured, I’ve already made plans about that. I had the tunnels dug very deep so that general spells wouldn’t be able to destroy it. Tunnels are our expertise, so you don’t need to worry about this matter.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Alright, then I’ll place my trust on the ability of the Dwarves. I’ll be heading towards the Radiant Empire later to see the situation there. I’ll leave some undead here in the meantime. Don’t worry, even if they send God-ranks, they won’t be able to deal with me. Moreover, I’ve also taken a look at the Demon camp. They have focused on building their city, so they won’t be attacking anytime soon. I’m just worried about what plans the Divine Race are having, so I decided to take a look.”

Julian nodded, “Would you like to have the Patriarch bring the Divine Artifact here, increasing the security?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “There’s no need for that right now. We need to have Patriarch Billy and the others to keep the defense in Accra Mountain. If things go bad, then we can just give up on the Buddha Empire, handing it over to the Divine Race and the Demons. That way, those two can just contend for the land, fighting with each other in the process.”

The people in the room froze when they heard Zhao Hai, their complexions weren’t exactly beautiful. Most of the people here are from the Buddha Empire, this was where they grew up, where their family thrived. Hearing that they must give up their hometown was something very unpleasant to hear. Zhao Hai looked at them and said, “Don’t think about it too much. You’re just giving up your homes, your land. In the end, your families are still there. Wherever your family is, then that place is your home. You don’t need to worry too much here, the Demon’s wouldn’t be coming for quite some time. They have a certain understanding about the Divine Race, so they should be conserving their strength ,not leaving their camp.”

The people relaxed, then Zhao Hai looked at them one by one before waving his hand, making Shiying appear. Then Zhao Hai looked at the people inside the room and said, “This is Shiying, the Demon God-rank expert. He is now my undead, he will be my representative here. Even if the Demons or the Divine Race attacks, you don’t have anything to worry about since I shall be returning at the quickest time. Well, then I’ll be leaving. Besmir, I’ll leave everything here to you.” Besmir nodded, then Zhao Hai vanished from the room along with Berry and Shue.

Everyone present were already aware of Zhao Hai’s space divergent ability. Because of this, they weren’t very surprised with Zhao Hai’s performance.

Zhao Hai’s group of three appeared on the Radiant Empire’s border. There weren’t any changes compared to their past visit. The dead people and beasts at that time were still present. However, Zhao Hai didn’t feel extreme anger this time. He needed to wait in order to take revenge so he decided to bury that feeling deep inside.

Zhao Hai came this time in order to see the new land that had descended. He wanted to see what’s currently happening there and know why the Divine Race had yet to make an action.

He moved and flew towards the new land. Zhao Hai was a God-rank expert so he naturally wasn’t slow. When he arrived at the place, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare. It was because he saw a group of people. All of them were wearing the standard gown of the Radiant Church, it seems like they were people from the church.

When he saw these people, Zhao Hai’s killing intent couldn’t help but flare up. At this time, the people from the Radiant Church had also discovered Zhao Hai. Currently, the Church didn’t have a lot of members remaining, only the core people were left. Altogether, these people number around a thousand. The worst of them were 8th rank Warrior or Mage. Unexpectedly, their 9th ranks had actually reached a hundred people, this number wasn’t small.

When the people from the Church discovered Zhao Hai’s group, their 9th ranks immediately flew over, headed by three people. The forefront of the three was an old person, he seemed to look over a hundred years old. His beard was snowy white as he wore a golden Radiant Church robe. In his hand was a sparkling golden book. This book made him appear like deity.

There were two red-robed people on each of the old person’s side. Zhao Hai didn’t recognize these two people, but their strengths were 9th rank. One of them held a while staff, while the other held a sword.

Zhao Hai didn’t care about who these people were. From his deduction, the old man should be the church’s Pope while the other two should be red-robed archbishops. Zhao Hai didn’t pay attention on these three. However, what took his attention were the items on their hands.

These three items looked very uncommon. Most importantly, Zhao Hai can feel that these three items emanated an aura similar to Iron Hammer and Bloody War. It seems like these three items were Divine Artifacts.

When the Pope saw Zhao Hai staring at the book on his hand, he couldn’t help but stare as well. Then when Zhao Hai paid attention to it, the Pope immediately knew that Zhao Hai had discovered what his book was. This book wasn’t a normal one, it was actually sacred scripture that was given to him by the Divine Race, a Divine Artifact. The same was true for the items held by the two red-robed Archbishops, the Radiant Staff and the Sword of Judgement.

For Zhao Hai to notice these items in such a short time explains that Zhao Hai was a really powerful man.

The Pope looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Zhao Hai, I didn’t think that you would arrive today. Submit to me right now, and when the Gods descend, I shall put a good word out for you. You have created huge troubles for the Church, and since we cannot change our plans, we had no choice but to do a Blood Sacrifice. This action made the Gods very angry, the people in the Radiant Empire were their most pious servants, and all of them died because of you.”

Zhao Hai coldly looked at the Pope and then laughed, “What a joke, they died because of me? Who killed them? Weren’t they killed by you hypocrites? And now you have the guts to pin the deed to me? You’re truly shameless.”

The Pope calmly stared at Zhao Hai, “They are the Church’s most faithful servants, naturally they are prepared to be sacrifices for our God. If not for your disturbance, we wouldn’t have used them. Instead, we would have used heathens for the sacrifice. Because of you, all of them died, so isn’t that your mistake?” Zhao Hai sneered at the Pope’s statement, “Heathens? And what qualifies being a heathen? Is it just because they don’t believe in your Radiant God? In this world, there isn’t only one God, so why would they need to believe in yours? Hahaha, now that I’m thinking about it, all of them were killed because of their belief in the Radiant God, isn’t that quite ironic?”

The Pope coldly replied, “Everyone who believes in the Radiant God aren’t heathens. The Radiant God is omnipotent, the Radiant God is indescribably formidable. For them to be sacrificed to his cause is their fortune. Their souls would be purified.”

Zhao Hai sneered and said, “Purification, the soul just flows out of the body and perishers, nothing else. Sigh. Its useless to keep talking to brainwashed people. Shue, Berry, kill them all. But be careful, these people are carrying Divine Artifacts. Their capabilities aren’t small.”

The two nodded, then Shue wielded his big axe and rushed straight into the enemies. Berry, on the other hand, slowly vanished into thin air. Zhao Hai just stood there without moving, observing the actions of the two. He wanted to give them more chances to fight. As soon as they comprehend a Domain, then they would become full-fledged Gods. In this chaotic situation, only then would they be free from constant peril.

When the Pope saw Shue rushing over, he immediately retreated while having the other 9th ranks go forward. They spread out as they attacked Shue.

Shue didn’t have time to waste with them. His figure suddenly shook as large quantities of Doppelgangers appeared by his side, proceeding to kill these 9th ranks.

These 9th ranks didn’t expect Shue to have this ability, causing them to be caught off-guard. In an instant, their numbers immediately fell by a large margin.

Shue didn’t care about the remaining 9th ranks as he continued to charge towards the Pope. The Pope wasn’t expecting Shue to be this formidable as well. However, when he saw that the enemy was still approaching, he lifted his sacred scripture up and said, “God decrees that all enemies shall be punished!”

Then as he said that, a bunch of white light went out of the sacred scripture. This white light quickly coalesced to become a light sword as it went towards Shue’s direction.

Shue made a low grunt as he lifted his axe and greeted the light with the axe’s projection. When the axe hit the sword, it didn’t manage to block it. The axe projection was destroyed while the light sword continued on towards Shue.

Shue’s eyes twinkled brightly, then his figure moved as he dodged the attack while charging towards the Pope. But then, the sword of light actually went around and attacked Shue’s back.

When Zhao Hai saw the sword of light’s movements, he couldn’t help but raise an eyebrow. He didn’t think the techniques of the Radiant Church would actually be this formidable. Not only did it break Shue’s attack, it could even trace its enemy’s position. This Divine Artifact surely was quite unique.

Chapter 718: Comprehending A Domain

At this time, the red-robed Archbishop bearing the radiant staff began to move. He held his staff up high and muttered an incantation. A ray of light started to cover the Pope, protecting him. Then as the Archbishop bearing the sword of judgement started to attack, he suddenly felt something beside him, this made him immediately dodge to the side.

However, he wasn’t able to completely dodge the attack. On his left arm were four claw marks. The wound was quite deep, the flesh was gouged out as blood continued to flow.

At this time, Berry’s form appeared ten meters away from the injured Archbishop. Berry was no longer the gentle woman who was right beside Zhao Hai. Both of her hands were now equipped with foot long nails, sharp to the point of showing cold light. Four of her nails, besides the thumb, in her right hand was now dripping with blood.

Berry chuckled tenderly, sounding out as a delightful laughter. However, those who heard it felt their will collapse a little. Then Berry smiled as she held her bloodied hand out and licked it with her long tongue. Her movements completely enticing while at the same time quite dangerous.

Zhao Hai discovered that Berry’s attack didn’t only involve his nails. Her laughter and her movements were actually a type of mental attack. Since mental attacks of the Succubi were formidable, and their control fantastic, this made it hard for their moves to be discovered. If Zhao Hai didn’t have stronger spiritual force, then it might be impossible for him to notice it.

Zhao Hai was surprised at Berry. He didn’t expect her to have this wild side, this astonished him very much.

On the other hand, the people from the Radiant Church were very startled. They hadn’t felt Berry approach at all. In their opinion, this feat was completely impossible.

These people were the strongest experts of the Radiant Church. Otherwise, they wouldn’t have been bestowed Divine Artifacts. Because of this, they were very confident in their own strength. They simply couldn’t believe that someone was able to bypass their detection and arrive by their side.

But how could they know about the powers of the Succubus race, or the fact that Zhao Hai had reached God-rank. After all, they were just 9th rank experts.

The little lady Succubus continued to chuckle, then her figure disappeared once more. This made the people from the Radiant Church unconsciously take a step back. The Archbishop with the radiant staff couldn’t help but increase his protection. At the same time, the Pope also opened his sacred scripture.

When Berry attacked the red-robed Archbishop, Shue’s clones had already eliminated the other 9th ranks of the Radiant Church. Shue’s clones held absolute superiority when it came to strength and numbers. The 9th ranks had no chance to retaliate at all.

Zhao Hai waved his hand, wrapping the dead 9th ranks and made them into undead. Then Zhao Hai pointed his fingers towards the 8th rank experts before the new undead proceeded to slaughter them.

Zhao Hai didn’t change the appearances of these undead into skeletons. Instead, he made them into zombies, in other words, he maintained their original faces. This was to make the Radiant Church witness helplessly as their own allies were killing them. This would be a huge impact for these people. These were their allies, friends, and superiors. Having them turn around and kill them caused panic and fear to the victims.

In this situation, how could it be possible for the people from the Radiant Church to keep their morale. Additionally, Zhao Hai’s 9th rank undead were very strong, it didn’t take long before flesh and blood began to splatter around the place.

However, Shue had actually met with some trouble. He was now faced against the sword of light. The sword was very strong, able to defeat a thousand axe projections from Shue’s clones.

After the Pope released another the sword of light, he didn’t close his sacred scripture. Instead, he closed muttered an incantation once more, “God decrees that everything is just an illusion. One needs to open his eyes to see the truth!”

Just after he muttered those words, a white light appeared on his side, then it slowly transformed into a huge white eye. The eye turned and projected a beam towards the area right behind the Archbishop with the staff.

A grunt came as Berry’s hand clashed with the light, shattering it. However, this also revealed Berry’s form.

Then the Archbishop with the sword of judgement immediately moved and swung his sword towards Berry’s direction. Berry wanted to turn invisible once more, however, the white eye ejected a beam once more, forcing her to reveal her form.

Zhao Hai saw all of these happen but still didn’t go forward to help. He knew that he had underestimated these Divine Artifacts. Its possible that these artifacts were no worse than God-rank experts, they might even be stronger than average God-ranks. No wonder the Dwarves and the other races were able to defeat a God-ranked expert using only their three artifacts, these items were truly strong.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t regret sending Shue and Berry to this fight. Only through battles would these two grow, and will soon develop their own Domain.

Shue was now being assaulted by two swords of light. This made him very angry, he didn’t think that he would have problems in dealing with some 9th ranks with divine artifacts. This was too shameful, he was losing face for his Young Master.

Shue couldn’t help but be enraged at this point. He roared and this time, he didn’t use a projection of the axe for attack. Instead, he injected his energy into the axe in order to attack. The whole axe turned blood red, shoots of light continued to dance wildly around the axe. With Shue in the center, red light was whistling about in a ten meter surrounding. These weren’t projections, all of these was just the aura that was given off by the axe.

The two swords of light stabbed into Shue’s axe aura. Then an intense clash sounded out. After some time, Shue’s figure backed up, his clothes were ripped into two, his skin was wounded in some areas. At the same time, the axe on his hand now had two grain sized holes. But fortunately, the overall damage to the axe was not too serious.

However, Zhao Hai noticed the damage. He knew that Shue’s axe was built with quality. It shouldn’t be too far from a Divine Artifact. It seems like Shue needed a better weapon than this one.

When Shue finally disperse the two swords of light, he made a furious roar as he went towards the Pope. The Pope flipped the page on his sacred scripture and said, “God decrees that all enemies shall fall into Hell. Unable to be reincarnated!!” Just as his words fell, two big white hands suddenly appeared in the sky, one above Shue and one below. Then the two hands went closer to each other, intending to flatten Shue in between.

Shue wanted to move to the side, but discovered that it was impossible for him to move, he seemed to be imprisoned. Shue panicked, he couldn’t help but turn his head to Zhao Hai. He hoped to obtain help from his Young Master. However, Zhao Hai stayed put, showing Shue a face full of hope.

When Shue saw Zhao Hai’s expression, he knew that Zhao Hai didn’t want to help him right now. He was hoping that Shue would break through.

When he understood Zhao Hai’s purpose, Shue’s heart couldn’t help but shake. Then he screamed violently as the axe in his hand swung around wildly. However, the two big hands seem to be unaffected. More pressure came as Shue’s space inside became smaller and smaller.

Zhao Hai was now starting to worriedly look at Shue. Although he hoped that Shue would break through, he was still afraid that Shue would get heavily injured. Zhao Hai was thinking that he may have been too impatient. Berry and Shue just became Demigods, so it may be impossible for them to become a God in such a short time. It seems like he had gone too far.

After thinking up to this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but sigh and prepared to make his move. However, Shue’s axe aura suddenly vanished. Shue was just stood there, calmly holding his axe. This made Zhao Hai stare, confused. And at this time, Shue started to swing.

The speed of this attack wasn’t’ fast, it can even be described as relatively slow. Every single movement can be seen by the naked eye. However, such a move actually manage to crack the enclosure made by those two big white hands.

As the axe chopped, a blood red gas started to wrap Shue’s body. Then this gas expanded, getting bigger and bigger, and even bigger as it stopped when it became as large as the Demon Herd’s Domain. Then the gas formed into a red sphere, surrounding Shue who was in the center.

But this wasn’t’ the end, the red sphere slowly started to take shape. In the end, it turned into the shape of an axe. This was a greataxe, a two bladed axe. Its body was completely blood red, but the edge of the axe was actually golden. This made the greataxe appear even more sharp.

When Zhao Hai saw this axe, he couldn’t help but laugh. He knew that Shue had finally succeeded, he had finally comprehended his own Domain. Although it was still in its first stage, it was still a very great achievement.

At the same time, seeing Shue’s process of comprehending a Domain also gave benefits to Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai’s Domain was directly made by the Space, there were some parts of it that he was still yet to understand. However, Shue’s Domain was self-made. In fact, the only difference between a God and a Demigod was their understanding of a Domain. But this understanding was more difficult than once can imagine.

Demigods and gods, if purely based on strength, then they were similar. Their only difference was that one had a formidable Domain while the other didn’t.

Chapter 719: Hook!

A Domain is basically a technique in utilizing one’s own ability. At the same time, a God-rank who had a Domain would be able to absorb energy much more efficiently.

This was something that Zhao Hai had found out when he used his Domain. However, he still wasn’t able to convey this information over to Shue and Berry. This was because Zhao Hai didn’t comprehend his own Domain. Shue and Berry can only rely on themselves for this matter.

Every God-rank that comprehended their Domain would be able to more skillfully exercise their strength. An action that made them use all of their strength from before would only take half after getting a Domain. At the same time, their execution time would also be 40 percent quicker compared to before.

The Pope and the others couldn’t help but stare blankly at Shue. They didn’t know what just happened, and why such a thing occurred.

The Pope and the others weren’t God-ranked experts, so their understanding about God-rank wasn’t that much. Since the Divine Race controlled the Radiant Church, then it was naturally for them to restrict crucial information regarding these things. Moreover, the Radiant Church didn’t expect that God-ranks would emerge from the Ark Continent. The situation was just like what Zhao Hai thought. The reason why the Ark Continent wasn’t able to produce God-ranks was due to the machinations done by the Divine Race.

In order to achieve their goal of conquering the Ark Continent, the people from the Divine Realm began to make their preparations after their first failure. They first sealed the passage from the Ark Continent to the Divine Realm. This passage was as old as the laws of the Ark Continent. If one were to look at it, the Ark Continent was a plane that was much lower than the Divine Realm. The strongest people in the Ark Continent were nobodies once placed on the Divine Realm. It was for this exact reason that the Divine Race deemed it proper for them to enslave the people in the Continent. In their view, the higher planes should rule the beings from the lower planes. After all, their strengths and abilities were much stronger in comparison.

However, the people in the Ark Continent didn’t want to be slaves to the Divine Race. Because of this, the natives of the continent decided to band together and resist, making the Divine Race suffer a loss. Being unable to conquer a lower plane was a huge embarrassment to the Divine Race. To make sure that the blunder wouldn’t happen again, the Divine Race started to prepare for their next move in the past tens of thousands of years.

The Divine Race first gathered a lot of strong people in the Divine Realm in order to forcible seal the passage between the two planes. Although it seems like it was just like blocking a road, it still made an impact to the Ark Continent. After the passage was blocked, God-ranked experts can no longer emerge from the Continent.

And to maintain the position of being superior, the Divine Race refrained from telling too much information, even to those faithful to them like the Radiant Church. Because of this, the Pope and the others were ill informed of the rank a step above from them.

Now when they saw Shue’s Domain, even if they couldn’t understand what it was, they could still feel the immense pressure coming from it. This made the three of them more careful.

Compared to the three, Shue was much more relaxed. He felt that his energy absorption has gotten quicker. Moreover, his control over his strength has become more streamlined. At the same time, he was also made aware about how to use his Domain.

Shue felt that his Domain was like a Space of his own. In this space, he can control everything. All attacks coming from outside would be much weaker and all attacks that he made seemed to double in power once used within the Domain.

Shue slightly closed his eyes, understanding his own Domain. This was the Domain that he comprehended himself, so it didn’t take long before Shue understood it completely.

Shue opened his eyes and looked at the Pope’s group. He coldly snorted as his hand moved, pointing the blood red greataxe towards them.

The Pope stared for a moment, then he felt that he had been placed in a dangerous situation, he immediately opened his sacred scripture and then chanted, “God decrees that all your attacks shall be withstood by me. All suffering shall be bent by faith!” Then a huge angelic figure appeared in front of the Pope. There was a beastskin belt around its waist and it was completely covered in wounds. At the same time, there was also bloodstains on its clothes, it looked very fierce.

This angelic figure was actually a legend in the Radiant Church. It’s called ‘guardian angel’, it was said that this angel would bear the sufferings of a thousand believers. But in truth, this legend was just an advanced level light magic.

Then the Divine Race established the Radiant Church, they had also taught the light mages modified light magics. These light element spells were mystical, they felt very sacred when used. The sacred feeling was felt whether these spells were made to attack or defend.

This trick has been useful in the past as well as in the present. In the past, people thought of these spells as miracles. Now that the Church had a lot of followers, these magics were always thought to be actions made by the angels, they were made with divine power.

Shue’s axe continued to chop towards that angelic figure. Then the angel went alive, it issued a pained moan as its head split into two. However, that was it, Shue’s axe was stopped, it couldn’t continue on after splitting the angel’s head into two.

Shue stared, then immediately made another attack towards the Pope. At this time, the sword bearing Archbishop rushed over, swinging his sword towards Shue. When Shue’s axe projection hit the sword, both attacks nullified one each other.

Then the Pope opened his mouth and chanted, “God decrees the annihilation of the enemy. All enemies shall be punished. All enemies shall be suppressed. All enemies shall be subjected to the punishment of light!” Then when his voice fell, a blinding light suddenly came from the sacred scripture. This light was brighter than the sun, one couldn’t help but close their eyes upon being subjected to the glare.

Shue couldn’t help but block his eyes as well. On the other hand, Berry called out in alarm. Then after judging the situation, the Pope immediately said, “Deal with the Succubus first. Then we’ll deal with the axe wielding man.”

The two Archbishops immediately made their moves. Their bodies almost flashing towards Berry. Zhao Hai couldn’t help but change his expression upon seeing this. He knew that Berry had suffered some wounds. This was because light magic had an innate strength against Demonic beings. And the recent attack was the sacred scriptures light magic.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t make his move. He knew that if he helped Berry right now, then she would forever be unable to comprehend a Domain. Because of this, Zhao Hai continued to stand there.

Berry saw the two Archbishops coming over and couldn’t help but stare for a moment. Then she quickly moved and clashed towards a red robed Archbishop. At the same time, Shue also sent an attack towards the Pope, intending to lessen the burden placed on Berry.

However, it seems like the three people of the Radiant Church had their tunnel vision towards Berry. Even though Shue had made an attack, they still went straight towards Berry, making her fall into an unprecedented crisis.

Zhao Hai prepared himself to move at any time, but still decided to stay his hand. This was Berry’s most critical time. People can break through at a moment of life and death. If she misses this opportunity, then Berry might find it difficult to develop her own Domain.

Berry’s body had already reached the state of being able to comprehend a Domain. The only thing that she lacks was the opportunity to do so. Therefore, Zhao Hai decided to give Berry this opportunity to face life and death.

Actually, before this moment, Berry knew that nothing would happen to her. She believed that Zhao Hai wouldn’t allow to have her be injured. This kind of thinking became a barrier to her breakthrough. Only when she comprehends a Domain would she get away from being a Demigod and become a Full God.

When the three people from the Radiant Church started to aggressively attack, Berry suddenly forgot Zhao Hai, she forgot about everything. The only thing in her mind right now was how to evade the Pope and the other two’s attacks as well as how to counter. At this moment, Berry’s Demonic blood finally activated, restoring her true Demon nature.

Under everyone’s gazes, Berry’s appearance suddenly turned pale before she vanished from sight. The Pope and the two Archbishops couldn’t help but stare upon seeing this happening. Then the furiously roared and attacked Berry’s original position. However, the only thing that they hit was thin air, nothing else.

The moment Berry vanished, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but faintly smile. Then he closed his eyes and sank his divine sense towards the small figure on his upper dantian. Then the eyes of the small Zhao Hai opened, his hair waved calmly as he released a formidable spiritual fluctuation all around Zhao Hai’s body. Then everything was made clear, when those fluctuations returned. Zhao Hai couldn’t help but gawk at what he saw, it was actually a siege hook!

Right, a siege hook, one that was used to climb walls. This fly hook was looked more formidable than the ordinary fly hooks that Zhao Hai saw back in ancient times. There were five fingers on this hook, they were no bigger than a person’s finger. From what Zhao Hai can see, it seems like this hook was modeled after Berry’s hand.

Chapter 720 – Divine Race Arrives

The giant hook had a rope with it. This rope was made out of innumerable filaments that looked like hair, they looked terrifying.

Zhao Hai slowly withdrew his divine sense. He understood that this hook was just like Shue’s greataxe, it was Berry’s Domain.

Berry’s Domain looks like it had three functions. First  was providing her with stealth. Moreover, compared to general stealth ability, her Domain seemed to provide a higher level stealth. Even light magic wasn’t able to break this Domain.

The second function was possibly to pull the enemies over. Otherwise, the hook wouldn’t have this form. However, Zhao Hai was also sure that there were more to it than pulling enemies over.

The third function seemed to be a mental attack. The rope on the hook looks like Berry’s hair, making Zhao Hai think that it would make mental attacks.

And just as Zhao Hai thought about it, the giant hook went flying and grabbed onto the shields of the Pope and the other two. When the hook reached two shields, the shields immediately shattered. However, when it came to the third layer, the hook got deflected. This was largely due to the staff bearing Archbishop to being very careful. Without the extra shields, the Pope’s group would’ve already been killed.

The Pope’s group couldn’t help but cry out in alarm. They didn’t know what happened, but they saw that two of their shields had just shattered. But then, they immediately thought of Berry’s abilities. They knew that Berry was capable of stealth, so this hidden attack should have come from her.

However, they were still yet to find even Berry’s shadow. The Archbishop with the radiant staff just made a few more protections around them, providing them with additional support. At this time, Shue moved.

Shue has been paying attention to the Pope and the others’ movements. When he saw Berry vanish, he couldn’t help but stare for a moment. Then he immediately smashed their layers of protection. Right now, there was only a single layer of protection left for the Pope and the others.

Berry didn’t let this opportunity go. She grasped the rope and threw it towards the Pope and the others, entangling them in the process.

At this time, Zhao Hai discovered that the three people from the Radiant Church were staying still, just looking blankly in the distance. They weren’t any different from clay or wooden statues.

Zhao Hai understood that these three people had been enthralled inside Berry’s mental attack. They weren’t even thinking about their battle with Shue and Berry, they didn’t move a step.

Zhao Hai was already aware that Berry and Shue had won. Although their three enemies had three divine artifacts, the artifacts were already deemed useless. After all, they were only artifacts, they weren’t real and independent God-rank experts. Because of this, even them were unable to leave Berry’s mental attack.

Under Zhao Hai’s sight, Berry held her hook and gently attached on the last layer of the Pope’s shield. Then she gripped her hook tightly as she made a final pull to break the Pope’s last shield.

The just as Berry was about to grasp the Pope’s head, proceeding to kill him, a while light suddenly appeared from the sacred scripture. This stopped the attack while at the same time, awakening the Pope and the two Archbishops.

At the same time, Shue sent several axe projections towards the Pope. And even if the Pope’s group didn’t respond, the sword of judgement suddenly separated itself from the red robed Archbishop and proceeded to block all of Shue’s attack.

After blocking the attacks, the radiant staff also flew up and released a lot of defensive shields all around the Pope’s group. This made the Pope’s group stare at the sudden change. However, they immediately turned ecstatic. As they opened their hands to receive the divine artifact, an archaic voice suddenly came, “Those who attack the servants of the Divine Race shall receive punishment!”

Berry and the others turned towards the direction where the voice came from. Then from the newly descended land, an old person with white robes suddenly appeared. Both the beard and hair of this person was all white. This made him look like a wise old sage.

Berry and Shue became startled, they knew that this was certainly a person from the Divine Realm. This person appearing wasn’t good for them. Their plan to eliminate the Radiant Church has just been placed into disarray.

The Pope’s group were overjoyed, they immediately knelt down and said, “We’ve seen the sacred master. Your loyal servants give their best regards.”

The Divine Race person seemed to ignore the greeting of the Pope’s group, he just nodded and said, “Get up, useless things. You really can’t do things well, but since we can’t do it without your effort, then I shall save your lives today.”

As soon as the old man finished speaking, he suddenly heard a sneer, “Still daring to recklessly boast. They are already monkeys in the cage, and you still dare to guarantee their safety. I want to kill them today, let’s see if you have the ability to stop that.”

This made the people stare, then they turned to Zhao Hai. Shue and Berry’s figures moved and returned to Zhao Hai’s side. On the other hand, the old man actually gawked, he looked startled towards Zhao Hai’s direction.

Zhao Hai looked at the Divine Race person and then coldly snorted, “I completely hate you Divine Race people. You still had the gall to be proud even if you haven’t stepped a foot on the Ark Continent. I am going to kill these three today, you want to stop me? Then try it!”

The old Divine Race person’s eyes flashed a cold light. He returned with a cold snort and said, “Good, good. I didn’t think that the Ark Continent would actually have God-rank experts. Also, even if we haven’t reached the Ark Continent, then how does that matter? I can still command the divine scripture, radiant staff, and sword of justice to attack you. Just by your own strength, it would be impossible for you to block out attack. Do you dare to meet my attack?”

Zhao Hai replied, “Then try it. I will certainly kill those three today, turning them into my own undead. At the same time, i shall also snatch your divine artifacts away.”

The old man got angry, he said, “Arrogant! Ignorant and arrogant! You actually dared to disrespect this God. Suffer death!” Then he waved his hand as the sacred scripture opened up and released a sword of light towards Zhao Hai. At the same time, the radiant staff also gave of a dazzling white light, beaming an offensive light spell towards Zhao Hai. Then the sword moved forward to attack. The path of the sword of judgement was quite peculiar. It actually made a huge arc, intending to attack Zhao Hai’s back.

These three attacks weren’t simple. The sword of light that came out of the sacred scripture was an overbearing attack. Moreover, in addition to being overbearing, it also exerted pressure. The pressure was akin to an attack by a God-rank expert.

The offensive light magic was a soul attack, it was very formidable. And finally, the sword of judgement was quite peculiar. Even if one can see it, it was extremely silent. Other than sight, no other sense was able to feel it.

If an average person were to meet this attack, then they would definitely be caught off guard. However, Zhao Hai wasn’t a simple person. He didn’t take these attacks seriously, then he suddenly said, “Thunder!”

Then nine beams of lightning came out, clashing with the attack made by the radiant staff, eradicating it in the process. Then Zhao Hai continued, “Mountain!”

A huge mountain suddenly appeared in front of Zhao Hai, blocking the sword of light. Although the sword of light managed to make a huge hole in the mountain, it was still stopped.

Then Zhao Hai said, “Swamp!”

The word caused a huge swamp to appear behind him. This swamp didn’t look anything special, but when the sword of judgement collided with it, it seemed to be mired in a sticky web. Its speed got slower and slower before finally stopping in place.

Zhao Hai waved his hand as the three artifacts was pulled over to his body. The three artifacts didn’t have enough time to run as they were immediately grasped by Zhao Hai. Just as they struggled, Zhao Hai immediately threw the three artifacts towards the Space. Upon absorbing the three artifacts, the Space quickly issued a prompt. “Items with light energy detected. First item is an evil extinguishing book. The second item is a sacred staff. The third item is evil executing sword. Virus program detected in each of these items, negatively affecting their performance. Removing the virus, virus removed successfully. Extracting light energy from the three items. All light element robots in the Space have now been upgraded to God-rank. The three artifacts has been integrated to the Blood Ghost Staff. Host can now judge a person, allowing the host’s marked target to receive 50% more damage. Host’s light magic has been increased by 50%!”

Zhao Hai listened to this prompt with a blank expression. He couldn’t respond to the influx of information. He didn’t expect this result, it was completely out of his expectations. The light-element undead had actually become God-rank. This was extremely good, this was because he had a lot of light-element undead!

Chapter 721: Using the Trigram

Zhao Hai had clashed with the Radiant Church in many instances. Although not everyone in the church were light mages, they still held the majority of light mages and light attributed warriors. Additionally, Zhao Hai also killed a lot of magic beasts who had an innate talent in the element of light.

From the moment they were born, the bodies of the residents in the Ark Continent had their own attribute. Let’s take Meg, for example, she had the water attribute, so she was well suited to studying water magic. Therefore, there were quite a few people and beasts who had the light attribute. And some of them weren’t under the Radiant Church.

If Zhao Hai’s calculations were correct, then all of the light element undead that the Space had numbered almost 10 thousand. In other words, he now had the same number of God-rank undead.

However, after asking Cai’er, he knew that these God-rank experts were only Demigods. This was because they had no Domain. Unlike the 500 God-rank Assassins who was actually found out to have their own Domain.

Zhao Hai was confused about this in the beginning. However, he changed his mind when he began to understand. These God-ranked Assassins were brought up because of Shiying. Shiying himself had his own Domain, so this achievement had also manifested on the 500 undead Assassins. On the other hand, although the three artifacts were formidable, they were still artifacts in the end, unable to manifest a Domain. Because of this, the light element undead weren’t able to have a Domain.

After thinking up to this point, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but sigh. The Space was indeed quite rigid. When talking about fighting strength, three 9th ranks with divine artifacts weren’t any worse than Shiying, they might even be stronger. However, since they were artifacts and not people, the artifacts themselves were unable to establish a Domain. Because of this, the Space only extracted their strength and upgraded the undead, it didn’t bother itself with giving the undead a Domain.

However, Zhao Hai was still quite satisfied. No matter what, the Space now had 10 thousand God-ranked undead, about 1 out of a thousand undead were now God-rank. This made Zhao Hai smile. One must know that people with light element attributes were quite rare in the continent. If he hadn’t exterminated the Radiant Church, then he wouldn’t have this many God-rank undead.

But to be honest, Zhao Hai’s true happiness wasn’t because of this matter, it was actually about the usage of the Dao Lotus. The Dao Lotus was extremely wonderful, it can attack, defend, help in absorbing energy, and even help in comprehending the Heavens. This was truly a top class treasure. However, Zhao Hai’s understanding of the Dao Lotus was just limited, he hadn’t even understood half of it.

The three characters that he had shouted before were actually about the eight trigrams: thunder, mountain, and water! The eight trigrams is separated into eight sections, Heaven(Tiān), Swamp(De), Fire(Huǒ), Thunder(Léi), Wind(Fēng), Water(Shuǐ), Mountain(Shān), Earth(Dì).

When Zhao Hai acquired the power of the Dao Lotus, he also acquired the method of using the trigram. Using the trigram was quite convenient, as long as Zhao Hai says the character, then he would immediately get the corresponding knowledge in order to execute it. Moreover, each character’s might was very formidable. Zhao Hai only used three characters in order to block the attacks of three Divine Artifacts, this was hard evidence towards the formidability of the trigram.

After experiencing how strong the trigram was, Zhao Hai was now more confident regarding his own capabilities. With the help of the trigram, Zhao Hai was assured that he wouldn’t be any worse than any expert from the Divine Race.

Zhao Hai was now very clear about how fierce the trigram was. If hadn’t used the trigram and only depended on his strength, the most he could do was to block the three divine artifacts, nothing else. Now that he had used the trigram, not only was he able to block the attacks, he was even able to capture the artifacts. For Zhao Hai, this was definitely a good result.

Contrasting Zhao Hai’s happy harvest, the old Divine Race man didn’t know how to react. He didn’t expect that their side would actually lose three divine artifacts!

One must know that even in the Divine Realm, divine artifacts were still quite rare! In fact, what Iron Hammer told Zhao Hai before had some mistakes. Iron Hammer said that the Divine Race was strong, this was true, however, Iron Hammer didn’t elaborate the fact that divine artifacts with their own spirits were also very rare. Artifacts with artifact spirits were also deemed to be on the top of the item echelon in the Divine Realm. Otherwise, the ancestors of the three major races wouldn’t have entrusted their race’s fate to Iron Hammer and the others. And if those kinds of Divine Artifacts were quite common, then the Divine Realm wouldn’t have been ruled by the Divine Race, but instead, by the Divine Artifacts!

The three artifacts that the Divine Race had sent to the Radiant Church was meant to resist Iron Hammer and the others. However, since Iron Hammer and the others were injured, the Radiant Church managed to suppress their races quite easily without any intervention from the races’ divine protectors. Because of this, an issue appeared on the Radiant Church, the succeeding generations actually forgot the initial purpose of the three artifacts. This caused them to worship these artifacts, using them as little as possible. The Radiant Church had become unskilled in using the artifacts. In the end, the Radiant Church wasn’t able to eliminate the other races and just continued to suppress them.

The Divine Race’s appearance in the rift as well as their modification of the laws didn’t come without a price. The land that descended actually had a protective shield. This shield wasn’t used to guard against the people from the Ark Continent, instead, this shield was used in order to prevent any damages to the land as it fell down towards the Ark Continent. The shield was too formidable that it actually saved the falling land from being destroyed.

However, because this shield was too formidable, the Divine Race couldn’t just forcibly remove it, making it impossible for them to invade the Ark Continent immediately. Only after seven days, when the new land gets stable would they be able to proceed with their invasion. Aside from their Divine Sense, the Divine Race were unable to enter the Ark Continent.

This flaw gave Zhao Hai a huge advantage. The Divine Race person had underestimated Zhao Hai, he expected that he could just command the divine artifacts with his Divine Sense in order to kill Zhao Hai. He didn’t anticipate that the other party would actually take the divine artifacts for himself.

When he felt that his connection to the divine artifacts were severed, the Divine Race person couldn’t help but be angry as he loudly shouted, “Brat, you dare! Return those artifacts immediately, or else, I shall shred you to bits!”

ZHao Hai gave a cold smile and said, “If you have the ability, then come. In the meantime, I shall be dealing with your dogs.” Then Zhao Hai waved his hand as a giant palm appeared and grabbed towards the Pope.

The Pope was surprised, he sidestepped the attack as he muttered an incantation, giving himself a protective light element shield.

However, even if he was fast, Zhao Hai’s giant palm was faster. Just as the Pope made his move, Zhao Hai’s hand already captured him. And with zero delay, the hand clenched itself, completely crushing the Pope’s whole body. After a short and pitiful squeak, the Pope had turned into a pile of mush.

After that, Zhao Hai threw the Pope’s body towards the Space. He wanted to see whether the Pope can still be turned into undead or not.

He can! Although the bones had been crushed, the Pope was still turned into an undead This was due to the two requirements of making an undead, one was the flesh and blood, and the other was the soul. The soul, flesh, and bones were just materials in making undead. One could compare it to making a sword where you need to use iron, fire, and hammer. The bone was like iron, the flesh and blood was fire, and the hammering was like the magic spell. Even if the iron was broken, it can still be merged together, and as long as there was fire and a hammer, then the sword can still be made.

Upon seeing this, Zhao Hai didn’t become polite, he immediately did the same to the two red-robed Archbishops, then turning them into undead creatures.

The person from the Divine Realm had a pale complexion as he looked at Zhao Hai’s actions. He didn’t expect Zhao Hai to have this much courage. He actually dared to kill he people of the Radiant Church in front of the Divine Race’s eyes.

One shouldn’t just look at how the Divine Race treats the Radiant Church. Although they were seen as dogs, the Divine Race was still very satisfied with the church’s work. After all, the Divine Race wouldn’t be able to break through the space and change the continent’s laws without the help of the Radiant Church. He just promised the Pope’s group that he would save their lives. However, Zhao Hai was still able to kill them, for the Divine Race, this was an absolute shame.

After looking at the Divine Race person’s complexion, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile faintly, “Divine Realm friend, I had always been waiting for your arrival in the Ark Continent. In fact, I already prepared a lot for this to happen. However, the Demons suddenly appeared, this derailed my plan. This should have derailed your plan as well. At this point, we are in the same starting line. As long as your people arrive in the Continent, then I will immediately have you pay for the lives of the people in the Ocean Waves Dynasty. I’m very hoping for your quick arrival, I can’t wait to kill several people from the Divine Race.”

The Divine Race old man looked at Zhao Hai, and with clenched teeth he retorted, “Just you wait. When we arrive in the continent, I shall personally remove your bones one by one. I shall then go to your family and then feed them to the dogs!”

Zhao Hai looked at the old man and then coldly smiled, “I’ll be waiting for you. Don’t disappoint me.” Then he brought Shue and Berry along with him as they turned around and leisurely walked back to the continent, purposefully making the old man’s eyes turn red.

But what this Divine Race person didn’t see was Zhao Hai’s pale face just as he turned around. This didn’t signify that he was afraid of the Divine Race, nor was it because he had a hard fight with them. On the contrary, he was very satisfied with today’s result. Berry and Shue were able to comprehend a Domain, and he even managed to acquire ten thousand God-ranked undead as well as three divine artifacts. Today truly brought him a great harvest.

The reason for Zhao Hai’s ugly expression was because of anger, he was raging at the Divine Race. These people simply didn’t see the residents of the Ark Continent as people. Their arrival in the continent showed how they regarded the people of the continent. Compared to the Demons, it seemed like they were much worse.

Zhao Hai had an understanding regarding the Demon Race. He knew that the Demons lived with the rule of the jungle. The weak could only be either food or slaves, nothing else. But this characteristic made it sure that they wouldn’t just wantonly kill people. After all, an alive slave was much better than a dead one.

Although the Demon Race’s final goal was acquiring the Ark Continent and killing every single resident inside it, Zhao Hai discovered from their actions tens of thousands of years ago that this was might not be the case.

From the nature of the Demon Race, they would surely change their mind. It was possible that they didn’t want to eliminate everyone inside the Ark Continent, they also want to rule the place.

On the other hand, with how the Divine Race sees the people of the Continent, they would absolutely not be lenient. This can be seen in their previous action. In order to make their target, the Divine Race actually made the Radiant Church sacrifice an entire country’s worth of people. If the Divine Race were to use this mentality in dealing with the Ark Continent, then the residents surely wouldn’t be able to live proper lives.

When Berry and Shue saw Zhao Hai’s expression, they didn’t say anything. Although they weren’t aware of Zhao Hai’s thoughts, they still saw what happened to the Radiant Empire. They too were seething with rage.

The number of people in that country wasn’t small, and the Radiant Church actually killed them off. In the end, only 1 thousand people, all of whom were the core of the Radiant Church, were left. All others weren’t spared, this was too ruthless, it wasn’t strange for people to be angry at this.

After some time, Zhao Hai let out along breath, calming his emotions. Then he lead his group back to the Space as they entered the villa. Upon entering, Zhao Hai immediately said to Laura, “Laura, inform all the armies in the Buddha Empire to rotate the defense and focus on the Radiant Empire. The attack of the Divine Race would truly be fierce. Focus all future defense strategies towards them. As for everything else, leave them to me!”

Laura nodded, then went along to follow Zhao Hai’s directions.

Chapter 722: An Enemy of an Enemy

Lizzy turned to Zhao Hai and said, “The Divine Race truly are formidable. They changed the laws of the heavens and the earth, they even managed to block the progression to God-rank. And now, they managed to bring an entire army in order to deal with us. It seems like they were truly annoyed by their past failure. Their plan of attack would surely be as fast as lightning. Fortunately, we had managed to get good fortunes to resist them. But Brother Hai, would the ordinary armies really be of use? They will surely die in the battlefield!”

Zhao Hai sighed, “We still need to have them. After all, they are also residents of the Ark Continent. If we don’t make them help, then they might feel dread when everything is over. They might fear that we would coerce them in the future. Also, did you forget about the other races in the Divine Realm? One must know that the Divine Race still had their own enemies in the Divine Realm, and those were the Gods of the three races. If those three races were to enter the war, then it would be a huge advantage to us. These people would definitely be great allies.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Lizzy gave out a small sigh, “I understand. But Brother Hai, do you believe that those Gods are still alive? It’s been countless years, I’m afraid that they had been eliminated a long time ago. Even Gods wouldn’t be alive after tens of thousands of years.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “I’m also aware of that. However, them being of help is still a huge thing for us, so we might as well try. If those Gods can help, then establishing a good relationship with them would be very good. Even if they can’t, then we can just rely on our own strength, showing them that we can provide sufficient power. Its good to have more people who have a grudge against the Divine Race.”

Lizzy understood Zhao Hai’s words, in the simplest form, Zhao Hai just expressed that an enemy of an enemy is a friend. If those Gods have a grudge against the Divine Race, then as long as they see Zhao Hai’s strength, then these people would certainly help out. With Zhao Hai, they can unite and destroy the Divine Race together.

However, Lizzy still couldn’t help but express her worry, “But Brother Hai, do these GOds really have a grudge with the Divine Race? If they don’t, then what do we do?”

Zhao Hai’s eyes flashed a cold light, “Then there’s nothing we can do. If worse comes to worst, then we will make God-ranks ourselves. Let’s see which is more formidable, my Space, or the Divine Race.”

At this time, Laura came back, she turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, the order has been passed around. I believe that it wouldn’t take too long before they make the proper adjustments. Do we really have to look away from the Demons?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “We still need to be on guard. However, the Demons aren’t relatively strong compared to the Divine Race. From what I felt today, there are only ten God-ranked experts in their camp. Moreover, with the big move of the Divine Race, the Demons are surely to be on full defensive mode. They are more focused on the Divine Race compared to us. For them, the Divine Race is more dangerous.”

Laura and the others nodded, what Zhao Hai said was true. Both the Demons and the Divine Race weren’t aware that Zhao Hai already had God-rank undead. Since they didn’t expect Zhao Hai’s side to have more strength, then they would definitely suffer in the future.

At this time, Lizzy asked, “Big Brother Hai, did you just say that the Divine Race needed several days before coming out?”

Zhao Hai sighed and said, “Less than seven days. This was something that came out of the Pope’s own mouth. I’m afraid that these seven days would be the most peaceful days of the Ark Continent.”

Laura nodded and said, “Brother Hai, we should have the Dwarves and Elves make the proper arrangements. At the same time, informing the four big Empires would be great as well.”

Zhao Hai nodded. Although the Divine Race and the Demons have already appeared, most of the Ark Continent’s land was still in the hands of the four Empires. And even if the Buddha Empire has been turned into a battlefield, it was still in Zhao Hai’s control. If the Divine Race and the Demons wanted to disrupt the continent, then it was certain that they would send some experts towards the other four Empires, harassing the Ark Continent’s rear.

At this point, Zhao Hai’s most difficult problem was the issue of military strength. One shouldn’t overestimate Zhao Hai’s more than 10 thousand God-rank undead. All of these undead were crucial in the actual battlefield. These 10 thousand undead simply aren’t enough in front of the Demon and the Divine Race. This was what made Zhao Hai very worried.

Without God-rank experts, then any preparation was useless. This made Zhao Hai anxious. Looking at Zhao Hai’s worried expression, Lizzy couldn’t help but comfort him, “Big Brother Hai, how about we return to the Black Wasteland and take a look at the situation. See if any of the 9th ranks have made a breakthrough. If they did, then you can just hand the task of protecting the Empires over to them. As long as they stop the attack for some time, then we can use the Space in order to rescue the people.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright, it has also been a long time since I returned to the Black Wasteland. Let’s go back and have a look.” He stood up and then along with the others, they vanished and returned to Iron Mountain Fort.

Green and the others were currently inside the castle. The Black Wasteland has been extraordinarily busy recently, there were simply too many people here compared to before. The Dwarves had dug out a lot of caverns in Iron Mountain. Moreover, they had also started to deliver iron ores from the mountain every day. The Dwarves already had their own furnace in the castle, all of them were busily making various types of weapons.

The Elves weren’t idling as well, they kept planting trees all around Flower City. At the same time, they were also manufacturing weapons. The Elves were very clear, the Ark Continent was on its way to disaster. It was impossible for them to live like before, wherein they were completely focused on making artware.

Only the Beastmen weren’t present in the wasteland. This was because there was no need to move. The Beastman Prairie was also quite far from the Buddha Empire. Even if the frontlines were shaken to its core, they prairie still wouldn’t be affected. However, the Beastmen were going all out in dispatching its troops in order to help.

The Black Wasteland had already been made known to everyone on the continent. After all, a lot of Human refugees were sent here. But nobody dared to have greedy thoughts when it came to the wasteland. This was because Zhao Hai was a very strong leader. There weren’t a lot of fools that dared to covet his territory.

Green and the others were fairly busy each day. There were a lot of newcomers in the wasteland, their basic necessities were needed to be managed. Otherwise, chaos would ensue. It was great that these supplies were already prepared by Zhao Hai, there weren’t any shortages that happened. Additionally, the various groups also had their own managers, this allowed Green to be less busy than he needed to be.

Green and the others were currently on a meeting. In attendance were representatives from the Dwarves, Elves, Beastmen, and Humans. These people were in charge of managing their respective people. Although the Black Wasteland had a lot of refugees, Zhao Hai still kept his strict rules in place. It was also made clear that the punishments on each rule breaking was the same for all races.

The major leaders weren’t in opposition to this rule. The status and strength of Zhao Hai were too formidable, all of them were very respectful towards his decisions.’

When Green heard that Zhao Hai had come back, he immediately led the managers to see Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai talked to these people, asked them about their situation, and then had them go back to their posts.

After the managers had left, Zhao Hai immediately turned to Green and said, “Grandpa Gree, how are things going? Did any of those 9th ranks from before break through to God-rank?”

Green shook his head and said, “Not a single one. Origin Sword Saint was the closest one. Those 9th rank beasts would have it much harder to reach God-rank compared to the Humans. Young Master, did something happen?”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he reported what happened with the Divine Race to Green. After Green heard Zhao Hai’s words, he knit his brows and said, “This is really quite troublesome. Young Master, I think the most important thing that we need to do is to spread what happened to the Radiant Empire. Otherwise, people from the continent would still think that the Divine Race are good people. If ‘they still held belief in the Divine Race, then they might cause internal problems to our side.

Zhao Hai nodded, “When the time comes, I’ll have the major powers do this. Our main concern is our lack of people. And once the Divine Race discovers about the Black Wasteland, then they would surely come and target it first. First is because this is our root, and the other reason is because they really hate me now.”

Green nodded, then he said, “Young Master, how do you plan to deal with this?”

Zhao Hai thought for a moment before he withdrew the three divine artifacts that he had taken from the Radiant Church. Although these three artifacts had been integrated to the Blood Ghost Staff, Zhao Hai could still take them out. After all, even if the three artifacts had great powers, they were still quite inferior to the Blood Ghost Staff.

Zhao Hai gave the three artifacts over to Green and said, “Grandpa Green, take these three divine artifacts. These things were handed over to the Radiant Church by the Divine Race. Now, they are all under the Space’s control. You can use this sword of judgement. The radiant staff will be given to Grandma Marine while the book will be handed over to Grandpa Kun. Keep these things as a secret. Once the Divine Race attacks, you can use them to resist for quite some time.I will immediately come over and help as soon as I receive word.”

Green wasn’t polite, he took the three artifacts and said, “Alright. Young Master, you need to be careful. Right, how are Berry and Shue doing?”

Chapter 723: Adjusting Strategies

When Zhao Hai heard Green, he couldn’t help but smile lightly as he replied, “They had been great. Shue and Berry managed to comprehend a Domain. Right, in two days, when the second batch of herbs matures, we’ll immediately have Shue promote his clones. At that point, our strength would even be greater.”

Green clapped his hand and said, “Fantastic! We’ll be confident in facing the Demons and the Divine Race by then. Right, Young Master, what are you planning to do in the future?”

Zhao Hai calmly replied, “Let’s wait for the Divine Race to attack us when their shield disappears. At that time, we’ll take the offense to them. I’ll get an army and give them spatial water in order to be raised to 8th rank and then 9th rank. Only this composition could manage to face our two enemies. Even if other people are eager to help, all that would be waiting for them is death!”

Green knit his brows and said, “Wouldn’t that reveal the existence of the Space?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “I don’t think so. The only thing that they would discover is the fact that I have a formula to increase one’s strength, the Space would never be connected.”

Green nodded, “Alright, at the worst, people will die. Young Master, you don’t need to worry about the things here. There won’t be any problems.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Don’t be too strict on the refugees. As long as they don’t make a huge mistake, then that would be fine. After all, these people are in a new environment. If you push them too much, then they might think that we are bullying them.”

Green smiled and said, “Young Master can rest assured, we have yet to punish someone. Everyone here respects the Young Master’s instructions. But if we find someone, then we guarantee that he wouldn’t be punished too hard.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Then that’s good. The continent has been plunged into hard times. The Divine Race had changed the laws of the heaven and earth. This would surely bring about some consequences. The Divine Race are truly scums, they even used such a method.”

Green was confused at Zhao Hai’s statement, he looked at Zhao Hai and asked, “Young Master, is the change in the laws really that serious?”

Zhao Hai forced a smile and said, “Naturally. In the past, the Ark Continent was an independent plane, it had its own laws. Now that these laws had been changed, it had shattered the continent’s division towards the Demon Realm and the Divine Realm. These two higher planes might not find trouble with this, but the Ark continent would surely feel the hardships. With the Ark Continent being disturbed, I’m afraid that we would be susceptible to more invasions from other planes in the future.”

Green stared for a moment before his expression changed, “It’s like that? When that happens, then wouldn’t the continent be destroyed?”

Green’s worries held true basis. The reason why the Ark Continent was invaded by the Demons in the first place was because of the initial action made by the Divine Realm, having a God descend. Now that the laws had been changed even more, the consequences would surely be more severe. The Ark Continent was fortunate that it hadn’t been destroyed in the first place.

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly, this was only his guess. But this guess had been made while he was connected to the heavens because of the Dao Lotus. What he understood was only a few things, so he could only make an intelligent guess at this point.

When Green saw Zhao Hai’s expression, his chest couldn’t help but feel heavy. If what Zhao Hai said was true, then the disaster for the Ark Continent has just started.

Upon looking at Green’s face, Zhao Hai comforted him, “Grandpa Green you don’t need to think about it to deeply. In the worst case scenario, we can all just hide inside the Space.”

Green nodded, then he knit his eyebrows and said, “Young Master, this outcome has surely been thought of by the Divine Race. Wouldn’t it be detrimental for their goals if the Ark Continent were to be unsafe?”

Zhao Hai thought about it, and then he said, “That may be possible, however, we can’t make solid judgements this early on. When we come in contact with the Divine Race, then it may be possible for us to be clear about it. Alright, Grandpa Green, I won’t be staying for long. I’ll be heading to the Buddha Empire now to take a look.”

Green nodded, “Young Master, you don’t need to worry about here.” Zhao Hai nodded, then he gave a signal to Laura and the others before they entered the Space. Then Zhao Hai took Shue and Berry to Rising Sun City.

Rising Sun City was the most forward defense against the Demon Race. Originally, Zhao Hai didn’t want to come here. However, since he was most familiar with the people transferred from Demon City, he decided to upgrade the strengths of the people here first.

Moreover, he came here to trade Shiying. Zhao Hai didn’t have too many God-rank experts. Therefore, he can only leave Shiying here to guard the place. But now, he has a lot of light element God-rank undead. The light element is extremely strong against the Demons. Because of this, Zhao Hai prepared to have Shiying go against the Divine Race while leaving some light element undead here.

Although the Demons have gone silent and had paused their construction, Zhao Hai knew that all of this was because of the changes to the Ark Continent’s laws. The Demon should be revising their plans at this time.

In the past, the laws of the Ark Continent were still present. Even if the Demons wanted to attack the continent, then they wouldn’t be able to send too many God-ranks. Because of this, they decided to build a city and steadily advance, stationing God-ranks on each forward city as they slowly devour the continent.

The laws of the Ark Continent also didn’t allow too many God-ranks inside it. This was the reason why the Demons didn’t dare to send a lot of God-ranks.

The Demons had done a lot of experiments in the past years. Although they didn’t think of changing the laws of the continent like the Divine Race, they were still able to create a concrete plan. These experiments included sending God-ranks to the continent to see how many experts the continent would be able to support, and also how long they could stay.

After constant experiments, the Demons have finally gained their results. The laws of the continent only allowed up to five God-ranks to enter. If a single God-rank enters, then the continent can allow this expert to stay for half a year. But this God-rank also needed to adjust for a month before he can move. After one month, the God-rank would be able to display 70% of his power. In three months, he can show 80%. Then after more than five months in the continent, the expert can achieve 90% of its power. After reaching this peak, the God-rank would then need to leave after half a day.

This was the reason why the Demons opened a spatial rift. And this was also the reason why the Demon Dragon King and the four others were the only ones sent as the vanguard.

For five God-ranks, the continent would only allow them to stay for three months. Half a month to adapt to the laws, then after that half-month, they would be able to use 60%. After one month, 70%. Two months, 80%. Then on the third month, they would return.

This was the law of the Ark Continent. The Demons had regarded this law heavily. They sent out five God-ranks this time in order to secure the Demonic Abyss. They were afraid that the Ark Continent’s people would destroy their city.

The Demons knew that it didn’t matter what they did, as long as they used the Blood Void, then the destructive display would certainly alert the residents of the Ark Continent. Because of this, the Demon Realm didn’t hesitate to send five God-rank experts.

However, when the Demon Dragon King and the others arrived in the Ark Continent, they were immediately met with Zhao Hai, even before they had completely adapted to the laws.

Because they weren’t able to adapt, the Demon Dragon King’s group couldn’t display all of their strength. Although they were God-ranks with strong abilities, their power were still reduced by the continent. Without adapting to the laws, these God-ranks would need to return to the Demon Realm after one month if they decided to disregard the laws. This situation made it hard for the Demons. If they were forced to go back after one month, then Zhao Hai would be able to completely lock them out, seeing that he can use 100% of his strength. Shue and Berry were also present, with them in hand, Zhao Hai would be able to deal with every God-rank that the Demon Realm would send. One could say that the Divine Race had provided the Demons some breathing room for their future plans.

Now that the laws had been changed, there was no need for the Demons to make their city. They can just send their God-ranks in along with their army in order to conquer the entire Ark Continent. They would start by capturing the cities as they advanced to all the corners of the continent.

The Demons needed to be swirt because the Divine Race was already here. If they continued to build their city, then it was possible that the Divine Race would have already conquered the continent. The Demons would be ordering soup without being able to drink it. Because of this, the Demons have decided to change their strategy.

After thinking up to this point, Zhao Hai decided to trade Shiying with the light element undead. Although Shiying wasn’t weak, he wasn’t the strongest Demon either. His techniques were all made in the Demon Realm, it wasn’t ideal for him to face the Demons in the battlefield since he couldn’t display his strength to its full potential.

The light element undead, on the other hand, were different. The light element was used to suppress the Demons. Even if these undead weren’t high-level, only being Demigods, they can still get an advantage due to their numbers. Along with Besmir and the others, they would surely be able to go against the Demon attack.

Chapter 724: Promotion

Besmir was still inside the General’s residence. Although they already had a lot of reinforcements, Besmir still didn’t have a moment of relief. He had seen the fight between Zhao Hai and the God-ranked Demons. To be honest, upon seeing the battle, a deep anxiety rose inside him. The strength that Zhao Hai and the Demons had shown was just too tremendous. Each punch and kick that they did seems to be able to move mountains. Facing enemies like these needed more than just ordinary soldiers, they needed 9th ranks if they wanted to keep up. Besmir was very clear about Zhao Hai’s importance in resisting the Demons and the Divine Race, but the help that Besmir and the others can provide was just too low.

Because of this thought, Besmir worked hard. He completed every single task diligently. This was to minimize Zhao Hai’s worries as he battled the Demon Experts. There was little time when he relaxes, he was almost always inside the battle room. Those who were with him were almost scared of his frantic work.

While Besmir was looking at the sand table, a voice suddenly came from outside, “We have seen Mister!”

Besmir stared, then he quickly recovered himself as he turned around to see Zhao Hai. Besmir immediately stepped forward and gave a salute, “Mister, please come in.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he entered the battle room. He turned to Besmir and smiled faintly, “General Besmir, you’ve been working hard. I came here today because I have something for you to do. Have everyone leave the room. Berry, Shue, go guard the door.”

After hearing this order, Besmir couldn’t help but be startled. However, he immediately had everyone leave the room as Shue and Berry guarded the entrance. Zhao Hai sat on a chair and beckoned towards another in front of him, “General, please take a seat.”

Besmir was quite anxious about Zhao Hai’s actions, however, he still sat down and listened intently. Zhao Hai smiled at Besmir and said, “General, tell me about what you think of this war. No need to hold back.”

Although Besmir didn’t understand where Zhao Hai wanted to take the conversation, he still nodded and said, “Alright. Mister, to be honest, I really don’t feel good about this war. The Demons are just too strong. And since the Divine Race managed to shatter the heavens, causing ripples everywhere, I also reckon that they’re quite strong. The reason why I don’t feel good is because of you, Mister. You are strong, but as for us, we can only do so much. There are too few people in the continent who can provide sufficient help to you. I’m not too optimistic about the future.”

Zhao Hai nodded, he replied, “What you said is true. The present situation isn’t really good. But we aren’t left with nothing. Everyone knows that I have a lot of good things in my hands. And those things are truly unique in the continent. Nobody understood why this was the case. In fact, there really isn’t anything mystical about it, I just happen to have a team that specializes on alchemy and refining. Our goal is to develop a way to quickly improve one’s strength.”

Besmir listened intently to Zhao Hai. When he heard the last words, his eyes couldn’t help but shine. He can now understand where Zhao Hai’s conversation would end up.

Seeing Besmir’s expression, Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Right, the General is a smart person. It seems like you already understood why I came here today.”

Besmir looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Is Mister saying that the potion has been completed?”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Correct. The potion has been finished. It doesn’t have any side effects. After drinking it, average people would reach 8th rank within two days. After reaching 8th rank, they can then drink another potion that can help them reach 9th rank in one day. Only by doing so would we gain a chance against both the Demons and the Divine Race.”

Besmir looked blankly at Zhao Hai. If he wasn’t aware of how strong Zhao Hai was, then he wouldn’t be able to believe any of this at all. He would just think that Zhao Hai was crazy.

In the past, 9th ranks were the top existences in the continent. 9th ranks were very hard to reach for ordinary people. Now, Zhao Hai told him that he can make 8th ranks in two days, and then a 9th rank in one. A 9th rank experts in just three days? This was something beyond crazy.

Zhao Hai smiled at Besmir’s expression, he turned his hand as a bottle appeared, “If you don’t believe me, then go and try it.”

Zhao Hai placed the bottle of spatial water on the table and then said, “Drink this potion. Since you are 7th rank, then you’ll reach 8th rank by tomorrow. When that time comes, I shall give you another potion to promote you to 9th rank.”

Besmir looked at Zhao Hai, and then at the bottle on the table. In the end, he nodded and didn’t say anything before taking up the jar and drank it up in one go.

Seeing Besmir’s action, Zhao Hai faintly smiled and said, “Go and take a rest. Stabilize your breathing. Come see me tomorrow.” Besmir nodded. Then Zhao Hai stood up and said, “Alright, then I won’t be disturbing you any further, take a rest.” Besmir stood up, gave Zhao Hai a salute and then left the battle room. Originally, the General’s residence was the City Lord’s Mansion. The current battle room was the mansion’s lobby. There was a small guest room at the side of the lobby, that room had now become Besmir’s bedroom.

When he saw Besmir leave, Zhao Hai turned around and walked out. Outside the room were the other enlisted officers. All of them were respectfully standing, nobody dared to speak a word.

Zhao Hai looked at them calmly and said, “General Besmir had something to do today. Don’t disturb him. Leave two guards to protect the entrance. If you need anything, then just hold it off until tomorrow.” All of them responded, nobody made a comment. All of them were aware about Zhao Hai’s status. He wasn’t only an elder and a prince, he was a God-ranked expert, a peak existence in the Continent right now.

One must say that in the past, the 9th ranks of the continent could see themselves as Zhao Hai’s equal. But now, nobody would dare do so, Zhao Hai was at the apex of strength.

After the group left, Zhao Hai released Alien and then entered along with Shue and Berry before going back to the Space.

Laura and the others were currently handling material allocation and transport. At the same time, they were also sending letters to the Emperors of the continent, informing them about what happened to the Radiant Empire. This would be used in order to spread information about the atrocities of the church, making the population lose faith in them.

Besides this matter, Zhao Hai also made them ask the Emperors for their most trusted people. Moreover, Zhao Hai also stated that he wanted to promote the strengths of those on the list. As for those people that the Emperors didn’t trust, Zhao Hai wouldn’t bother with them in the future.

The Emperors immediately believed Zhao Hai’s words. They already knew Zhao Hai’s strength. Don’t think that the people in Demon City were all from the Buddha Empire. Among the Adventurers and Mercenaries were spies of the other major powers. Because of this, it didn’t take too long before Zhao Hai’s fight has been made known to the entire continent.

After knowing Zhao Hai’s strength, these people weren’t worried about being fooled anymore. With Zhao Hai’s capabilities, then he would have already acted, he wouldn’t wait until now.

The most happy about this situation were the people in Lyon Empire. Zhao Hai was their current Emperor. Having such a powerful ruler, it wasn’t strange for the population to rejoice.

Because of this as well as other reasons, the Empires immediately sent their lists over to Zhao Hai. They didn’t hesitate a bit and send a huge pile of names. Upon seeing this list, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but chuckle, this was because almost all of these people were 8th ranks.

For Zhao Hai, this was a good thing. This would eliminate the period of turning them into 9th ranks.

But since these people were the trusted people of the major Empires, it would be impossible to direct them to the battlefield. However, Zhao Hai wasn’t counting on them to be on the battlefield. He wanted to use these people as a proof. As long as these people get promoted, then everyone in the continent would have faith on Zhao Hai’s method. When that time comes, then there won’t be any issue whenever Zhao Hai wanted to promote additional people.

After the names were sent, Zhao Hai immediately took some water from the Blood Pond and then had them sent to the different Imperial Palaces for the people on the list to drink while he stayed in the Buddha Empire.

After handling these matter, Zhao Hai finally relaxed. He rested inside the Space as he prepared to go to battle at any time.

Zhao Hai was also waiting for the herbs in the Space to mature. He wanted to make God-ranked potions as soon as possible. The Divine Race were waiting for their shield to expire, only then would they be able to start their invasion of the continent.

After having rested inside the Space, Zhao Hai appeared on the City Lord’s mansion the next morning. At this time, Besmir had also woken up. He had truly become 8th rank. When he saw Zhao Hai, he was very excited, he immediately gave a bow and said, “Mister, thank you very much. I have already reached 8th rank.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he withdrew another bottle, this one had water from the Blood Pond. Then he gave the bottle to Besmir and said, “The potion in this bottle will promote you to 9th rank. After becoming 9th rank, I’ll have to ask you to gather some trustworthy people in Rising Sun City. After gathering them, go and call me. I’ll improve them to 9th rank so that they can have more impact on the future battles.”

Chapter 725: God-rank Army

Standing calmly in front of the Processing Machine was Zhao Hai. He looked at the machine as it swallowed up the materials on the ground, the gold coins on his inventory a million coins less. Then the machine started its timer.

This was the second time that he was making a God-rank potion. Because of this, he was now quite familiar with the process. The only thing he needed to do was wait, when the time comes, Shue’s clones would also become 9th ranks.

One must say that Zhao Hai was very lucky in having Shue as his subordinate. Shue’s cloning ability was just too formidable, it was basically a one-man army. Now that he can drink another God-rank potion, his clones would now become 9th rank as well. This thought was just too scary.

At this moment, Zhao Hai was worried whether Shue’s God-rank clones would also be able to establish a Domain. If they did, then it would be very good for Zhao Hai’s side.

The timer beeped down unceasingly. Zhao Hai couldn’t help but let out a long sigh as he said, “I hope our time is enough.”

The one who heard him was the nearby Berry, she looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Feel relieved, Brother Hai, we certainly have enough time.”

Shue looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Young Master, rest assured, this Shue will definitely be of use, definitely.” Zhao Hai smiled faintly and patted Shue on the shoulder as he said, “Everything will be alright, there’s no need to worry about it too much. You will certainly be a huge help. In the future, you and your clones would be part of the main army. A man that can turn into a thousand would be terrifying in the battlefield. Hahaha. The Divine Race wouldn’t come soon, but even if they do, we still don’t need to be afraid of them. To be honest, I want the Divine Race to come sooner, I really wanted to see how strong they are.” Shue nodded, but his eyes were still firm. Then Shue looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Young Master, can I ask you for one thing?”

Zhao Hai stared, then he smiled and said, “Say it, there’s no need to be too polite to me.” Shue nodded and then said, “Young Master, can you promote Shun next time? Out of all the people on our side, Shun is the most compatible to be my partner in the battlefield. But if the Young Master has any plans, then you don’t have to consider my request.”

Zhao Hai laughed, and then he patted Shue on the shoulder and said, “Hahaha, I thought that it was something serious. Don’t worry, focus on having your clones become God-rank first. After that happens, then your Young Master would help Shun become 9th rank.” Shue was overjoyed by Zhao Hai’s reply, he quickly replied, “Thank you, Young Master.” Zhao Hai patter his shoulder once more and said, “Alright, let’s head back in. Let’s drink a couple of cups. We’ve been too busy these days, we need to relax.”

Zhao Hai’s heart felt warm after listening to Shue’s request. Shue hadn’t asked for anything ever since he followed him. This was the first time that Shue made a request, but it actually wasn’t for himself, instead, it was for a friend. After becoming God-rank, Shue didn’t forget about Shun. This made Zhao Hai very happy.

After they arrived at the Space, Zhao Hai made Meg prepared several dishes. Then he sat with Shue in the dining room while having a few cups of liquor. On the other hand, in every city in the Buddha Empire, people who had been placed on the list have emerged to be 8th ranks, some even got promoted to 9th.

These 8th ranks can be promoted later on. As for these 9th ranks, Zhao Hai asked Cai’er to observe their current actions.

A 9th rank expert was a significant person in the Continent. Although these people were elected, it was still difficult to be assured that they won’t do anything excessive upon becoming 9th rank. But if they do, then Zhao Hai would definitely be impolite.

Besmir was now 9th rank. Aside from him, there were also quite a number of people who had become 9th rank in Rising Sun City. These people included Elves, Beastmen, and Dwarves.

As the number of 9th ranks increase, Besmir’s mood had become better and better. A lot of 9th ranks meant that Rising Sun City’s fighting strength was strong. For Besmir, this was truly a good thing.

Additionally, among these 9th ranks were Elves, Beastmen, and Dwarves, races who found it hard to upgrade their strength. However, once these people become 9th ranks, their strengths would be a lot more than any Human experts.

Besmir’s current emotion wasn’t unique, it had also propagated all throughout the continent. In the Buddha Empire, 9th ranks started appearing in each of the cities. This caused the people to have their morale increase.

However, although these people had become strong 9th ranks, nobody dared to act arrogantly. Earlier, there were some people who had become 9th ranks who thought that they were already great. Zhao Hai might not care about normal arrogance, but when these people started to do evil things, Zhao Hai immediately sent and undead to seize this person. After that, the undead didn’t hesitate to execute this person in front of the whole city before turning the person into an undead.

Zhao Hai’s lightning-fast methods truly frightened everyone. This caused the recently promoted 9th ranks to behave themselves.

Two days had already passed by, Zhao Hai and the others were in front of the Processing Machine. The timer on the machine was quickly approaching zero. When the timer turned zero and the beeping stopped, the God-ranked potion immediately appeared in front of them.

Zhao Hai didn’t hesitate as he took the potion and handed it over to Shue, “Shue, drink this immediately. I reckon that the Divine Race would be here soon. We need all the strength we can muster.”

Shue didn’t waste any words, he immediately took the potion and downed it in one go. This time, Shue didn’t need to stabilize himself. His body just shone a blue light for a moment, then after the light vanished, Shue turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Young Master.” Then another Shue appeared on his side. Zhao Hai can sense the aura of a God-rank expert on this clone of Shue.

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Good, good. Right, does he have a Domain?”

Shue nodded, “He has, Young Master. After all, he is another version of me. The only reason he isn’t’ God-rank before was because there wasn’t enough energy in the first potion. Now that I had enough, my clones’ immediately got improved. He will have everything that I have, including my Domain.”

Zhao Hai felt great happiness, “Great. That’s fantastic! Hahaha. I really am envious of your divergent ability. Good, good. Let’s go out and see when the Divine Race would arrive. I can’t wait to see their expressions.” Then Zhao Hai took Berry and Shue out of the Space.

The three of them went out and arrived inside Upper Bank City.. This city was also one of the big cities in the Buddha Empire. But now, the place was completely deserted. It was actually part of Zhao Hai’s initial plan for defense, however, due to the sudden appearance of the Divine Race, they had no choice but to vacate this city.

Zhao Hai wanted to have his first clash with the Divine Race in this city. This was because of its good position as well as it being the first city to be encountered if one were to come from the Radiant Empire. It would be impossible for the Divine Race to miss this city.

The reason Zhao Hai was assured was because he knew how arrogant the Divine Race were. From the way they act to the way they talk, these Divine Race people would definitely place their crosshairs on Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai just killed the Pope in front of them while also taking three of their divine artifacts. In this situation, Zhao Hai doesn’t need to go to the Divine Race, the Divine Race would be the ones who will go to him.

After all these considerations, Zhao Hai felt relieved as he waited inside the city. He must teach the Divine Race a lesson, let them understand that the Ark Continent wasn’t their own backyard. They couldn’t just take a walk here whenever they wanted. The Ark Continent wasn’t their pig pen, and its residents aren’t their farm animals. If they wanted to conquer the Ark Continent, then they would need to show real skill. Even if they went all out, the end result was still completely unknown.

Originally, Upper Bank city held a population of a million people. Additionally, this was also the closest Buddha Empire city from the Radiant Empire. It itself held great strategic significance. Because of this, the walls of the city were quite thick. Moreover, the city was also protected by a magic formation. Although this formation was nothing in Zhao Hai’s eyes, it still proved how valuable this city was.

After Zhao Hai’s group of three appeared in the city, Laura and the others followed them out. These days, the women were very busy inside the Space, they went out this time to taste some outside air.

Even if the environment inside the Space was very good, staying for too long inside it would also make people depressed. A change of scenery was always good.

The group stood on top of the city wall, looking towards the distant Radiant Empire. At this moment, Lizzy opened her mouth, “The population of this city used to be 1 million. Now it had turned into a ghost town. Sigh, Human affairs are truly unstable.”

Zhao Hai turned to Lizzy before looking at the empty city streets, “This is already good. If you go to the Radiant Empire, not only would you see a dead atmosphere, you would also see dead bodies strewn around. Seeing all those dead people just on the streets would make you gasp, that scene was just too terrifying.” Lizzy felt her complexion pale, she couldn’t speak. At this time, Shue turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Young Master, we should see whether we can make good use of this city’s magic formation. Although it can only be used for defense, it is much better than nothing.”

Chapter 726: Crystal Stone

Zhao Hai looked at how big the city was. With this size, it was impossible for it to not have a defensive magic formation. However, the capabilities of this formation was too limited when facing a God-rank expert.

But this didn’t mean that formations were useless. On the contrary, magic formations came in many types. Moreover, the size of the formation also needed to be taken into consideration.

The defensive capabilities of these magic formations mainly depend on the crystal stones used. If the energy inside these crystals was formidable, then the formation would be formidable as well. If the energy of the crystal was too low, then the magic formation would also be weak.

The issue with this was the fact that the Ark Continent rarely had big crystal stones. The current crystal stones on the Ark Continent couldn’t even block the attacks of 9th rank experts, much less God-ranks.

Naturally, Shue knew about all of this before he told his idea to Zhao Hai. After seeing that Zhao Hai was considering it, he added, “Young Master, have forgotten about the crystal stones that you discovered back in the Northern Icefield? Those crystals were very full. You can try and see what effects those would have on the city’s magic formation.

Zhao Hai stared, then he patted his head and said, “I actually forgot about those. Good, then I’ll try it immediately. Shue, you take care with the installation of those crystals while I head out of the city. After those crystals are installed, you go and feel the energy of the formation, see if it can produce sufficient energy for our use. Record all of your findings.”

Shue understood what Zhao Hai meant, if this experiment ends with a success, then its impact for the continent would surely be huge.

Shue nodded as he made his clones appear. Zhao Hai waved his hand, withdrawing a pile of crystal stones and gave them to Shue. The clones immediately took the crystals and placed them alongside the city’s magic formation.

Zhao Hai was now outside the city. He quietly observed the situation to see if the crystals would be useful in protecting the city.

Not long after Zhao Hai went out, a layer of protective shield covered the city. This shield wasn’t the same as what Zhao Hai saw before. In the past, the protective shield that Zhao Hai saw had a pale yellow color. On the other hand, the shield in front of his was actually blue in color, one could even see some ripples occurring here and there.

Zhao Hai stared at this protective shield, he couldn’t help but place his hand on its surface. It didn’t take too long before a chilling cold air was felt. Zhao Hai gawked, but he wasn’t surprised. After all, the crystals that he put out were ice crystal stones.

Then Zhao Hai established his Domain, he waved his hand as a giant palm appeared. The palm made a fist as it attacked the protective shield.

The result surprised Zhao hai, the shield actually wasn’t destroyed. Conversely, the the protective shield blasted out a cool air, freezing the big hand.

Zhao Hai didn’t think that this protective shield would have this effect. He shook his Domain and attacked the protective shield with full force. The protective shield rippled, but it wasn’t broken. Moreover, Zhao Hai can feel the waves of cold air transmitted from his Domain. This chilling wave was very strong. If a Demigod were to be careless, then they would definitely be injured by this shield.

Zhao Hai nodded and then retrieved his Domain. After that, he turned to Shue as the latter dissolved the magic formation.

After Zhao Hai returned to the City, he immediately went to Shue and said, “What did you get? How much energy did my attack take from the crystals?”

Shue promptly replied, “Young Master, the crystals are very formidable. Your attack took almost no energy away from the crystals. Moreover, I discovered that as long as one injects energy into the crystal, it can recharge itself indefinitely.”

Zhao Hai was shaken,then he immediately took a new crystal stone from the Space and poured his energy into it. Strangely, no matter how hard he injects his energy, he couldn’t do it. Zhao Hai stared for a moment, then he turned to Shue and said, “Shue, give me one of those used crystals.”

Shue nodded, then he took a piece of crystal and gave it to Zhao Hai. Upon receiving the crystal, Zhao Hai immediately tried to inject his energy into it. This time, it didn’t take too much effort for the crystal to accept energy. Before long, the crystal was filled to the brim. Zhao Hai made some calculations, the energy that he had injected was the same energy it took for an ordinary attack. It seems like the magic formation didn’t consume too much energy and it can also be used repeatedly.

After thinking up to this, Zhao Hai took a used crystal and then gave it to Laura, “Laura, try pouring your energy into this crystal.”

There was a reason why Zhao Hai did this. After becoming God-rank, one’s energy would undergo a change, it would become much purer than before. Moreover, it would also lose its original attribute, it was simply pure energy.

Such pure energy can surely power a crystal. However, the general strength of the continent only involves 9th ranks. One must know that 9th ranks still had their attributes. Laura’s attribute was fire, which happened to be the exact opposite element to the ice crystal. Zhao Hai wanted to see whether Laura can pour her energy to charge the crystal.

Laura tried it for a moment before she shook her head and said, “Brother Hai, it’s no good. I can’t pour anything into the crystal.” Zhao Hai nodded, then he turned to Megan and said, “Megan, you try.”

Megan nodded, then she received the stone from Laura and then tried to pour energy into it. She didn’t expect that she would be successful. Before long, the crystal was filled. Megan turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Elder Brother Hai, I can pour my energy into it. The crystal has been filled.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then took another used crystal and gave it to Meg, having her try. In the end, Meg was unable to pour her energy inside. Zhao Hai can now affirm that the crystal would only attract energies of the same attribute or God-rank energy. Other attributes were no good.

Zhao Hai turned his head to Megan and said, “Megan, how much energy did it take you to fill the crystal up?”

Megan recalled for a moment and said, “Not that much, approximately about 1% of my total energy. I can recover it after a while.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he smiled faintly and said, “That’ good. Let’s see how those Divine Race fellows attack me this time.”

At this moment, Laura turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, are you planning to have these crystals power the magic formations in the continent?”

Zhao Hai nodded, “You should be aware of the situation regarding the major cities in the continent. Aside from our help, they really don’t have much in terms of defense against the Divine Race. If the Divine Race decided to cause large scale trouble, then the continent would surely be placed into turmoil. If our rear gets chaotic, then our job in the frontline would be affected.”

Laura understood what Zhao Hai meant. The present situation was like this. Even if the Divine Race were yet to appear, they still needed to make sure that everyone was completely safe.

Iron Hammer said that the Divine Realm was much different compared to the Ark Continent. Newborn children in the Divine Realm were already 8th ranks. When they grow up, they would freely enter 9th rank. Upon cultivation, they can easily reach God-rank. This was a terrifying thing to think of.

Think about it, a plane that allows the existence of God-ranks, even if the amount of this God-ranks wasn’t a lot, they would still add up to a terrifying amount. Because of this, Zhao Hai needed to prepare in dealing with the Divine Race.

Laura looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, since these crystals can replace ordinary crystals, then would they work on magic cannons as well? Will the power of the cannons increase?”

When he heard Laura, Zhao Hai stared, then he immediately nodded and said, “This is a good idea. Let’s go and make some experiments.” Then the group’s figures vanished as they used the Space to transfer to the Lyon Empire.

No matter what, Zhao Hai was still the Emperor of the Lyon Empire. Doing his experiments here would certainly have no issues.

Although Zhao Hai was the in-name Emperor of the Lyon Empire, the one running everything here was actually Evan. The entire Lyon Empire knew that Zhao Hai was busy in the frontline, battling with the Demons and the Divine Race. Because of this, the Empire followed Evan’s instructions.

Fortunately, Evan had ruled the Purcell Duchy, so he had great experience in management. He knew what to do with great Nobles, therefore, there weren’t much troubles in the Lyon Empire. At the same time, these Great Nobles didn’t dare to cause any trouble. Everyone in the continent knew about how powerful Zhao Hai was. If they drag Zhao Hai behind, then they would definitely suffer.

As soon as Zhao Hai and the others arrived at the Lyon Empire’s Imperial Palace, they immediately went towards the Great Hall. When the Great Nobles saw Zhao Hai, all of them immediately bowed and said, “We have seen His Majesty. Long live!”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he looked at the Nobles and said, “I have something I need to do. Go find me a quiet place, it must be very spacious. Prepare some magic cannons as well. Remember to make this thing known to as few people as possible. Find people who are trustworthy and make them help out.”

Although these Nobles didn’t understand what Zhao Hai wanted to do, all of them still nodded and prepared everything. Evan looked at Zhao Hai, confused, then he asked, “Little Hai, what’s happening? Did you discover something?”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he retold his discovery of the wondrous properties of the crystal. He also took out a crystal and handed it over to Evan. This crystal had great energy within, however, Evan can’t feel the energy when he held it in his hand. There wasn’t any cold and chilling sensation when holding the crystal, but Evan can see the formidable energy inside, it can truly wound a Demigod expert. This crystal was truly unusual.

Chapter 727: Experiment

There was a valley not too far from the Lyon Empire’s capital. This valley held no specialties, only rocks, nobody lived here. This place was called Stone Valley.

It was a different day in the generally empty Stone Valley. In this virtually unnoticed place came many people. Moreover, these people were the most influential personages in the Lyon Empire. A single cough from one of them would be able to move an entire Lyon Empire army.

Why would powerful people come to a place where birds won’t even defecate in? Along with these group of people were the cavalry of the Lyon Empire. These soldiers were carefully selected so there wasn’t any problem with them.

Zhao Hai came in using an ordinary carriage this time, he didn’t want anyone to know that he was here. This time, he came to do some experiments, so he brought ten magic cannons for the tests.

The soldiers in the valley quickly set up the magic cannons before they went to the sides. Zhao Hai didn’t dare have the soldiers operate the cannon, he was afraid that accidents would happen, killing someone in the process.

Zhao Hai went towards a magic cannon and inspected it carefully. This magic cannon was the most advanced and powerful weapon in the continent. But this magic cannon didn’t look like the cannons that were seen back on earth, it looked more like a satellite receiver rather than a cannon. The power of this magic cannon depended on the crystal stone. People would place the crystal in the middle of the cannon, then they would activate the magic formation to gather the energy inside the crystal. Then the energy would pass through the edges of the cannon and reflected onto a small plate in front of the cannon. This metal plate also held a magic formation in it, when sufficient energy gets gathered, then the cannon would proceed to fire.

The fired beam would then be sent towards the target, reaching the energy level equal to the crystal used. However, it is a pity that the crystal stones used to fire these magic cannons were of inferior quality, making its power quite weak. This was the reason why magic cannons weren’t used in the battle between the Demons and the Divine Race. But this time, the crystal that Zhao Hai had brought was not the same as those inferior ones. With the high energy contained within them, Zhao Hai prohibited soldiers from manning the cannons lest an accident would happen. The cannons were operated by Zhao Hai’s undead. At this moment, Zhao Hai took out a piece of crystal and handed it over to the undead who then placed it on the middle of the cannon and then pressed the activation button.

Not long after the button has been pressed, the entire magic cannon suddenly shone a blue light. The blue light went on to circle the magic formation before being focused on the metal plate on the middle. Upon arriving at the small plate, a beam of blue light immediately shot out.

The blue light  looked the same as a laser beam. The light penetrated the surface of the mountain but to Zhao Hai and the others’ surprise, nothing happened. There wasn’t an explosion nor were pieces of rock being thrown around, everything was as normal as they were before.

Zhao Hai stared, then his figure moved and approached the wall of the mountain. He wanted to know what happened to the wall, and he couldn’t believe that the blue light did nothing. Just as Zhao Hai arrived by the wall, he immediately felt a chilling cold air. The cold was quite strong that Zhao Hai could already feel that he was in world of snow and ice just a meter away from the wall. Although there were no changes on the wall, it was evident that the soil around it had turned into permafrost.

Zhao Hai immediately dug into the mountain wall. Only after digging through five meters of rock did the mountain return to being warm. In other words, the chilling effect had actually penetrated through five meters of solid mountain wall.

This was a good result. Three meters would already be good enough, but it actually managed to make it five. From this trial, it can be seen how powerful the magic cannon attack was.

Zhao Hai made some calculations. If this beam hit a 9th rank, then they would certainly turn to ice in mere seconds. God-ranked experts would also feel afraid of this cannon attack.

The others who had gathered here were also surprised by what happened. They knew about the power of a magic cannon. Even 100 magic cannons wouldn’t be able to exhibit this effect.

Zhao Hai nodded, then he returned to the cannons. He made the undead continually fire the magic cannon. He  wanted to see how many attacks it would take before the crystal ran out.

Before long, blue light flashes repeatedly until the crystal had been exhausted. Zhao Hai counted and saw that it would take 2318 shots before a full crystal gets depleted. 2318 Demigod-level attacks, this wasn’t a small number.

Zhao Hai took the empty crystal out and examined it. The crystal was fully transparent, no energy was seen inside.

Zhao Hai turned his head and called an 8th rank expert over to input his energy into the empty crystal. The 8th rank quickly complied and poured some energy into the crystal. The crystal actually turned red from the original white, evidently showing that the energy placed inside was of the fire element.

Zhao Hai nodded, he can now understand what this white crystal was for. After a crystal was used up, then one could place energy of whatever element inside it. However, if there was still a sliver of ice element energy inside, then it would be impossible to place other types of energy into it.

However, Zhao Hai still had a question. Would this crystal be recharged over and over? Can it be used infinitely? This seemed to be unlikely.

Zhao Hai waited before the 8th rank completely used all of his energy up. Then he took the crystal and examined it. Zhao Hai found out that an 8th rank expert can only fill up to a fifth of the total capacity of a crystal. It seems like it needs five 8th rank experts in order to completely filly up one empty magic crystal. Zhao Hai recorded all of his findings, these would definitely be useful in the future.

Zhao Hai didn’t fill the crystal up to full. Instead, he handed it over to the undead to use it. This time, the magic cannon fired a beam of red light. When this red light got in contact with the mountain wall, a loud explosion was immediately heard. A huge hole was blown out of the mountain face, ten meters across and three meters deep.

Such might wasn’t small, but Zhao Hai’s purpose this time was to consume the energy inside this crystal, so he didn’t really care much about it. After having the undead fire the magic cannon and consume the energy inside the crystal, Zhao Hai placed a bit of energy inside the crystal and fired it again. This process repeated for ten times, after the tenth firing, the crystal finally cracked, rendering it useless.

Zhao Hai recorded this result and then he turned his attention to the magic cannon. He was quite sure that the magic cannons  would also wear off. After being used multiple times, these cannons should become broken. Zhao Hai wanted to see at which point the cannons would break down.

Zhao Hai inspected the current state of the cannon. Although it can still be used, cracks were already seen on its surface, it seems like its life was soon to be used up.

Zhao Hai nodded and then traded the magic cannon for another one. The experiments continued, one cannon after another. In the end, Zhao Hai found out that magic cannons can fire 2000 to 2500 times.

Upon completing his experiments, Zhao Hai returned to the Lyon Empire’s Imperial Palace. Then when they arrived at the Great Hall, he turned to the Great Nobles and said, “I came back this time to see the capabilities of these crystals. These stones have been acquired by me back when I was exploring the Northern Icefield. The energy inside these crystals are very formidable, you should have seen it on the magic cannons earlier. The usage of these crystals aren’t limited to magic cannons, they can power protective formations as well. When I return to the frontlines, I shall leave some of these crystals to you. Every instruction for its operation and properties shall be written carefully. Have these crystals delivered to the cities in the Lyon Empire for defensive purposes. If I were to discover that someone has been hoarding these crystals, then I will definitely be impolite.”

These Nobles in the Lyon Empire were aware about how precious these crystals were. But they also needed to take Zhao Hai’s threat into consideration. If Zhao Hai deemed them to be enemies, then they would be in opposition to the entire continent. With Zhao Hai’s status, nobody would dare disregard his orders. Because of this, every single Noble replied, “Your will shall be done, Your Majesty.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Remember, only hand these crystals over to people that you absolutely trust. Take care of them extremely well, there shouldn’t be any mistakes. When the Divine Race comes, these crystals would be extremely helpful in dealing with them.

The Nobles issued a sound of affirmation. Zhao Hai nodded, then he took out several crystals and handed them over to the Nobles present.

After completing all of these, Zhao Hai turned around and returned to the Space to head towards the Rosen Empire. Since he already did his experiments, he can immediately hand the crystals over to the major Empires. He introduced their uses and properties and how they would be used to resist the Demons and the Divine Race. With these crystals, ordinary people could now be assured of their safety inside the cities of the continent, this was an extremely good thing.

Chapter 728: Shue of the Thousand Shadows

Heads covered with silver helmets, bodies donned with shiny silver armor, a long silver spear on their hands as well as a silver longsword on their waists. Although they were wearing full silver armor, they didn’t seem to be encumbered at all. Their bodies were stably floating in mid-air.

At first glance, once couldn’t see where this sea of silver men ends, they were just too numerous. All of them were just standing there quietly, as if waiting for something.

In front of this army was a group of white robed people. The ages of these people varied, but each and every one of them gave off a consecrated aura.

If Zhao Hai sees them, then he would definitely know that these people were of the Divine Race. The army of the Divine Race was no less than a million. They were now concentrated on the edge of the descended land, the soldiers were waiting for their inquisition.

In fact, they had a reason for being here, they weren’t standing here for no reason. Today was the day that the protective shield would disappear. Once it was gone, then they would immediately start to conquer the entire Ark Continent.

What the Divine Race didn’t know was the fact that Zhao Hai had long been aware of their action. Although Zhao Hai hadn’t come to the new land for a while, he already had the Blood Ghost Staff explore the area. Because of this, he can always use the monitor in order to see the situation at the protective shield’s vicinity. It would be impossible for Zhao Hai to miss this huge army concentrated on the border.

Zhao Hai was now inside Upper Bank City, ready to meet the Divine Race. In the past few days, he had sent people to the various Empires and delivered the crystals. Moreover, Zhao Hai also sent his crystals to all the cities in the Buddha Empire. Although the occupied cities weren’t a lot, they could still support themselves using the magic formations as well as the magic cannons.

At this point, the Ark Continent was prepared and is waiting for the Divine Race attack. Naturally, Zhao Hai didn’t relax on his monitoring of the Demon Race. The God-ranks in the Demon camp had gotten more and more, their army increased while the construction of their city had become faster. What made Zhao Hai feel strange was the fact that the Demons were yet to attack the Ark Continent. Even Demon City that was the closest place faced no Demon invasion.

But after thinking further about the actions of the Demon Race, Zhao Hai didn’t take too long to understand what they were doing. The Demons were waiting for an opportunity. They knew that the Divine Race would attack the Ark Continent first, and not them. Because of this, the Demons planned to keep their position and wait for any substantial result to come out.

If Zhao Hai and the others were defeated by the Divine Race, then the Demons would immediately dispatch their troops and attack Rising Sun City. If the Divine Race suffers a loss, then Zhao Hai and the others would certainly have some losses as well. When that time comes, the Demons would dispatch their troops and kill Zhao Hai.

To be honest, the Demons were currently dreading Zhao Hai. With his formidable undead, Zhao Hai would be able to become an Overlord in the Demon Realm. With this enemy, it was assured that the Demons would pay Zhao Hai their utmost attention.

At the same time, the Demons were also happy with the Divine Race’s move. The Demons were lucky that the laws of the Ark Continent had been changed, otherwise, with Zhao Hai in the Ark Continent, it would be difficult to mount an invasion.

The Demons respect experts, and Zhao Hai was such an expert that was worthy of this respect. Because of this, although the Demons hated him, they also couldn’t help but admire his strength. Zhao Hai didn’t use any underhanded moves when waging war with them. After a battle, Zhao Hai would allow both sides to peacefully retreat. Although he was still hateful for what he did to the Demon Dragon King’s group, the Demons still had to recognize that Zhao Hai was strong.

Because of this, the Demons decided to stand by and watch. When the results of Zhao Hai’s clash with the Divine Race comes, it wouldn’t be too late for them to make their action.

Zhao Hai had a faint idea about this plan, however, he didn’t have the means to do anything about it. The Demons not making their move had also given him some breathing room. After all, his manpower was insufficient for a two pronged war.

Zhao Hai was sitting in the Space while looking at the monitor. The Divine Race were peacefully standing in their current position. Aside from the white robed individuals in front who were casually chatting, the other people were acting like wooden stakes, just standing there, motionless.

After seeing this scene, Zhao Hai’s expression couldn’t help but sink a little. These small details can tell the might of an army. This was the reason why the Chinese army paid great attention to their standing army positions. Military posture might sound simple, but this was a good testing point of an army.

These Divine Race soldiers had stood there motionless for a long time. There weren’t any unnecessary movements on even a single one of them. For all of them to stand there showed how great their willpower was. This was certainly an elite army.

At this time, Zhao Hai noted that the outer edge of the new land had suddenly rippled. Then the protective shield surrounding it started to crack, silently breaking itself apart.

Zhao Hai really couldn’t believe that a protective shield that blocked the advance of God-rank experts would just vanish silently like this.

But the Divine Race’s movement stopped Zhao Hai from his thoughts. When the Divine Race saw that the shield was gone, they immediately gave a command to the army, leading them to kill towards the Ark Continent.

After seeing this situation, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but take a deep breath to calm his emotions down. Then he turned his head to Laura and the others and said, “Laura, Ruyen, I’ll leave the logistics to you two. Lizzy, Megan, I’ll hand the command of the undead over to you. Shue, Berry, come with me.”

The group nodded, then Zhao Hai led Berry and Shue out of the Space. As soon as he arrived outside, Zhao Hai immediately released two million undead. These undead immediately formed a cube formation as they quietly waited for the Divine Race to come.

At the same time, Zhao Hai also sent some undead towards the city’s magic formation. He also took out 100 magic cannons from the Space and placed them on the walls of the city.

After his experiments, Zhao Hai decided to keep 100 of these magic cannons with him. After all, these cannons were now able to contend with God-ranks once they’re were powered by the powerful crystals. At the moment, most undead that Zhao Hai had were 9th ranks, if these undead were to fight against God-ranks, then it was certain that they would suffer a loss. But now that the magic cannons were on play, the undead’s capabilities have increased, this was a huge advantage for Zhao Hai’s side.

The Divine Race didn’t disappoint, just two hours after Zhao Hai exited the Space, they arrived.

Their move was very daring. After they came out of the new land, they didn’t stop for a moment and just headed straight forward. From this point, one could see how proud they are.

Zhao Hai was currently standing on his Bone Dragon as he stared at the slowly approaching army. His facial expression stayed calm, he also didn’t make an initiative to attack. He knew how proud these Divine Race people were, to demonstrate their superiority, they would definitely spout out a few words before beginning their attack.

And just as Zhao Hai expected, when the Divine Race army reached a kilometer away from the city, they stopped. Then the white robed God-ranks slowly flew towards Zhao Hai’s direction.

Zhao Hai felt how strong these people were. In this 1 million army, 50% of them were unexpectedly God-rank. This startled Zhao Hai. Moreover, although the other half weren’t God-rank, they were still 9th ranks. The Divine Race were truly going hard with such a lineup.

Zhao Hai commanded his Bone Dragon to meet these white-robed people. Both sides stopped when they were 50 meters away from each other. The one leading the white robes was the one Zhao Hai took the three divine artifacts from.

That old God-rank looked at Zhao Hai, he couldn’t help but coldly smiled and said, “Zhao Hai, I didn’t think that we’d meet this early.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly at the old man and replied, “Why aren’t you expecting it? Didn’t I say that I’ll be waiting for you? Right, how is your face doing ever since I took those three Divine Artifacts away?”

When the God-rank heard Zhao Hai bring this matter up, his complexion couldn’t help but turn cold. He looked straight at Zhao Hai and coldly snorted, “Hmph, there’s no point in flaunting your lucky encounter. After all, you will die today. Remember the name of the Divine that will kill you, Silver Shuke!”

When Zhao Hai heard this old man’s name, he couldn’t help but laugh and said, “Interesting, too interesting. Such a dignified Divine actually had that kind of name, why does your name sound like it belongs to a thief? It seems like the I have overestimated the Divine Race too much.”

When the Divine Race heard Zhao Hai, they couldn’t help but change their expression. Divines had their own pride, they always claimed that they were a cut above the people from the Ark Continent. They weren’t able to bear being mocked by Zhao Hai. One Divine went forward and coldly said, “Brat, you dare mock my Divine Race? Do you dare have a duel with me?”

Zhao Hai looked at the Divine Race as though he had seen an idiot, then he said, “What? You still do duels? I didn’t think that you would still resort to such ancient way of fighting. You Divines really do disappoint me. But since you dared to issue me a challenge, then I will give you what you want. Shue, kill this fellow!”

Shue gave a nod before his figure moved and appeared in front of Zhao Hai. He looked at the challenging Divine and said, “If you want to fight, then come. But at your level, you are unqualified to fight against my Young Master. If you want to fight him, you have to come through me first.”

The Divine went on to throw his robe away, Shue also went forward. Zhao Hai and the other God-ranks took a step back to give the two people some space.

Shue looked at his opponent, then his expression turned serious, he wielded his axe on one hand before he shouted, “Buda Clan’s steward, Shue of the thousand shadows!”

Chapter 729: Sly Divine Race

Shue’s opponent didn’t think that Shue would become polite. This made his stop on his tracks and stare. This was because the Divine Race would usually declare their names before they attack. Cheap attacks weren’t something that the proud Divine Race would do.

Because of this, the Divine Race was shocked by Shue’s performance. He didn’t that Shue, who was rude earlier, would suddenly declare his name.

It wasn’t only Shue’s opponent who was startled, the other Divines did the same as well. They didn’t know how to handle such an action.

Zhao Hai looked at Shue and smiled. Before the battle, Zhao Hai already discovered that this Divine Race person was stronger than Shue. Shue was now God-rank, and his opponent would surely be a level above him at least. Zhao Hai had Shue battle the enemy because of Shue’s divergent ability. Shue’s clones would be able to overwhelm this person, so Zhao Hai was confident in sending Shue over.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t think that Shue would make a smart move. Although Shue’s words were unnecessary, Zhao Hai knew that Shue’s true intention was to break the arrogance of the Divine Race.

Shue was also aware that this Divine Race expert was very strong. And when the Divine Race person made the challenge, he was quite mad, his morale at its peak. If Shue went on to fight him at this state, then even if he won, he would still make a lot of effort to do so. Since this person was consumed by anger, his attacks would surely be fierce. Moreover, the other party surely has reached 2nd level Domain, his attacks would definitely be strong.

Because of this, Shue used this little method of being polite, shaking the Divine Race expert and resetting his mindset.

Although Zhao Hai understood what Shue wanted to do, he still kept quiet and just calmly looked at the opposing party. He wanted to know whether the enemy would continue with his anger or declare his name.

If the Divine Race expert decided to continue on his frenzy, then it shows that the Divine Race didn’t care for their reputation. On the other hand, if he declared his name, then it meant that the Divine Race were rigid people whose reputation is much more important to them than their lives.

Different enemies required different methods. Because of this, Zhao Hai paid great attention to the other party’s response.

After staring for a moment, the Divine expert’s complexion turned pale. However, he still restrained his anger as he gave a salute to Shue and said, “Divine Race’s Raging Fire General, Tiger Huan!”

After saying his name, the Tiger Huan immediately gave a shout and charged towards Shue. But Shue had enough time to prepare, his figure moved as he established his own Domain.

Tiger Huan didn’t think that Shue would also be a God-rank Expert who had comprehended a Domain. When he saw Shue establish his Domain, Tiger Huan couldn’t help but stare for a moment. Then he also made his move and established his own Domain.

His offensive rhythm was also destroyed for a second time. However, after seeing Tiger Huan’s Domain, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but frown.

Tiger Huan’s Domain was a human shaped Flame Demon. Naturally, this was a 2nd level Domain. Moreover, since it was a fire element Domain, its attacking strength would surely be strong while its defensive ability would be quite decent. Seeing that the other party had such a Domain, Zhao Hai felt that he wouldn’t be very easy to deal with.

Shue didn’t think too much about this, no matter what kind of enemy he was faced, he would still go on and fight them. Zhao Hai wanted him to deal with the enemy, and no matter who it was, Shue needed to accomplish the task, he didn’t want Zhao Hai to lose face.

Of course, Shue understood that the enemy wasn’t easy to deal with. He immediately made his move, along with his Domain, several other Domains also appeared, these were all made by his clones.

This action didn’t fail to make Tiger Huan stare, he just saw multiple Domains, and all of them were just like Shue’s. The first time he saw this, he immediately thought of illusions. He reckoned that Shue’s Domain had something to do with tricking one’s enemies. Aside from Shue’s original Domain, everything else was fake.

Since Shue only had a 1st level Domain, then Tiger Huan’s spiritual force should be stronger compared to him. Because of this, Tiger Huan thought that this illusion Domain was useless to him. He didn’t worry much about it as he swept the numerous Domains with his Divine Sense and looking for the real one among the fakes.

However, just when his divine sense swept through the Domain, he discovered that the Domains he thought were fake turned out to be real. This made him stare, but he still disregarded it, he thought that it was a type of advanced level illusion. Although he couldn’t completely understand it, Tiger Huan still coldly snorted and had his Flame Demon move. The Flame Demon made a loud cry before it raised its arms and formed two Fire Dragons that attacked towards Shue’s Domains.

Tiger Huan wanted to use this attack to bring out Shue’s real Domain. However, what he wanted to happen didn’t happen. At this moment, Shue had released five clones. This meant that six Shues were fighting Tiger Huan. Tiger Huan wasn’t expecting any of these at all, he thought that Shue had an illusion Domain, this wrong assumption had proven to be deadly.

Just as Tiger Huan released the two Fire Dragons, Shue immediately made his move. Two clones went forward to meet the two fire dragons. The three clones then went on to attack Tiger Huan using their axe Domain.

Shue didn’t fight with his clones for a day or two, additionally, all of them were tied by heart, their coordination was perfect. Shue commanded his Domain to chop the middle of the Flame Demon, as for the three clones, one chopped towards the Flame Demon’s head, another went for the neck, and the last one went behind the Demon, preventing it from escaping.

Tiger Huan immediately felt that things weren’t going well, however, it was too late to make a counter-attack. But still, Tiger Huan was still a God-rank expert who had a 2nd level Domain. Although he couldn’t escape, he still didn’t lose heart. He controlled his Flame Demon and made it turn into a defensive stance, capitalizing on the fact that its defensive capabilities were also quite good.

The three axe Domains hit the Flame Demon, rendering Tiger Huan into a miserable situation, he gave off a scream as blood spurted out. However, Tiger Huan continued to steel himself, as the axes fell down, he immediately changed the shape of his Domain, making the Fire Demon turn into a spherical shape. Not only did this remove the targeted parts of the Flame Demon, it also made the axe attacks deal half their intended damage.

Still, this damage injured Tiger Huan. But even so, he still didn’t retreat, instead, he became angry. He didn’t think that a strong God-rank like himself would actually be wounded by a person from a lower realm. How could a proud person like himself bear this humiliation.

Tiger Huan shouted ferociously as his Domain turned back into a Flame Demon. Then a fiery sword appeared on the Flame Demon’s hand before it attacked Shue’s axe Domain.

Naturally, Shue wasn’t held back by this development. He immediately directed his axe Domains to attack the Flame Demon once more. At this time, Tiger Huan was already aware that Shue’s Domain were not illusions, all of them were real, and their attacking strength wasn’t weak.

Although Tiger Huan couldn’t understand how Shue did it, he still knew that it had to be a secret technique. He knew that if he didn’t kill these clones as soon as possible, then the damage that they can inflict could only increase as the battle went on.

Tiger Huan’s attack was very fierce, however, Shue wasn’t intending on facing it head on. At this moment, Shue was like a pack of wolves attacking a lone bison. Whenever the Flame Demon made a move, Shue’s clone would just retreat while the others continue to make cheap shots. This would make the Flame Demon target another clone, that clone would then retreat while the others make their attacks. This cycle would continue until Tiger Huan would get tired.

When Zhao Hai saw how Shue fought, he couldn’t help but nod. To be honest, Shue’s method was very simple, but this method was very hard to deal with. However, this action needed almost perfect coordination from all the participating attackers, otherwise it wouldn’t be as effective.

Breaking this method was also very simple. One was to fight and entangle on of the attackers, making it difficult for other people to come in and join. However, this method needed one to be flexible and more powerful than the other.

The second method was strength, overwhelming strength. If one could wipe out an attacker after each attack, then it wouldn’t take too long before the attackers would get consumed.

However, it was quite obvious that Tiger Huan was unable to do these two methods. Because of this, he was plunged into a difficult situation by Shue and clones. But Zhao Hai still paid attention to the fight, he was on guard against the other God-rank experts as well as the army behind them.

While Shue was continuing to fight, Lizzy’s voice suddenly came, “Big Brother Hai, there’s a change in the Divine Race Army. People have come around, intending to do a sneak attack. What do we need to do?”

Zhao Hai stared for a moment, then he looked at the opposing Divine Race and coldly snorted. It seems like the Divine Race wanted Zhao Hai to focus his attention on the fight while they sent out an army to circle around to give a fatal strike whenever convenient. This was a good method, ordinary people would definitely fall for it.

The people that the Divine Race sent were all God-rank, and their attacks were much more effective compared to the undead. If they attacked an ordinary person, then they might be able to completely succeed.

But unfortunately for the Divine Race, Zhao Hai wasn’t an ordinary person.

Chapter 730: Blood Lightning Bead

After Zhao Hai heard Lizzy’s report, he said, “There’s no need to care about them. Just prepare some undead to be dispatched. When they attack, immediately release undead on both of their sides, we’ll eliminate them first.”

Lizzy paused for a moment, then she said, “Big Brother Hai, then what do we do about the enemies in front?”

Zhao Hai coldly snorted and said, “We’ll deal with them as well. Make sure to release a batch of undead behind them to prevent them from leaving. Then we’ll have three groups of undead clash with their army, let’s see how formidable the Divine Race’s army really is.”

When she heard Zhao Hai, Lizzy didn’t say anything more, she just complied with the instructions and started to prepare. While this conversation happened, Shue was still attacking Tiger Huan. Since he couldn’t face Tiger Huan dead on, Shue continued to attack him with wolf tactics.

On the other hand, the other Divine Race people looked at Shue and Tiger Huan’s battle with an ugly expression. They didn’t think that Tiger Huan would be placed in such a position by someone like Shue.

If they didn’t have their own plans, then they might have already mounted an attack. They were currently waiting for their army to be in their positions before starting their plan to attack and kill Zhao Hai’s group.

Zhao Hai has been observing these Divine Race people. He found that although they seem to be paying attention to the battle, their eyes were actually focused in front, which was the place right behind Zhao Hai. There might even be a hint of anxiety between their expressions.

Zhao Hai knew about what these people were thinking, but he didn’t make a move. He knew that the undead had already shifted the magic cannons to the appropriate direction while keeping it a secret to the Divine Race. The magic formation has been primed as well, waiting for the moment to be activated.

Zhao Hai understood that the Divine Race had some understanding regarding these magic cannons. After all, the Radiant Church has been in the continent for many years, it would be impossible for them to be clueless about this matter.

The Divine Race knew that the capabilities of the magic cannons were limited. Not to say them, but even in the continent these magic cannons can only harm 6th ranks at most, 7th ranks will have no problem resisting them. Because of this, when the Divine Race saw Zhao Hai flaunting his magic cannons, all of them had a mocking thought inside their hearts.

At this moment, there was a change in the battlefield. Tiger Huang has been forced into a corner by Shue, he knew that if he didn’t make a move, then he would fall here. Therefore, he suddenly screamed and then punched his own chest as he threw up some blood. Then his fingers moved as he muttered an incantation. The blood that came out suddenly floated in the air, and along with the incantation, it began to tumble until it looked like boiled water. Then the red blood slowly receded and turned black, forming a bead.

Tiger Huan gave a shout as he threw the bead over to Shue’s clones.

Shue’s clone felt something wrong with this bead, so it sent out an attack using the giant great axe, targeting the approaching bead.

However, what happened next made Shue stare. Just as the attack got in contact with the bead, the energy within it was suddenly being absorbed. After absorbing the attack, the bead started to appear clearer.

When Zhao Hai saw this bead, his complexion changed. Although he didn’t know what this bead was, he was certain that it wasn’t simple. Moreover, he can feel a sense of danger coming out from that bead.

Zhao Hai knit his brows, then he looked at the other Divine Race and saw their happy expression as they looked at Zhao Hai’s group. Zhao Hai knew that the reason of their expression was the army had already arrived behind him.

After thinking about this, Zhao Hai didn’t wait as his figure moved and appeared right by the bead. Then he waved his finger as a spatial rift appeared in front of the bead, absorbing it into the Space.

The Divine Race didn’t expect Zhao Hai to make a move. This caused them to be caught off guard, however, Silver Shuke immediately responded, “Zhao Hai, since you dared to disturb the duel, then don’t blame us for being impolite. Begin!” Then the army started to charge towards Zhao Hai.

At this moment, Tiger Huan felt that the Blood Lightning Bead, which he had lost contact with, suddenly restored their connection. With a thought, he immediately compelled the bead to explode.

This blood lightning bead was a type of mixed magic. It was a combination of blood magic and fire element magic along with a hint of black magic. This kind of magic was very demanding with regards to its users, only people who had reached God-rank, like Zhao Hai would be able to use it.

However, even if Zhao Hai were to know of this magic, he would still opt out in using it. This was because the foundation of this magic lay on the user’s blood essence.

Blood essence wasn’t just ordinary blood, it was something that was connected to one’s life force. To each person, this blood essence was a very important thing. If a person lost his blood essence, even if they didn’t die, like Tiger Huan, they would still find their strengths being knocked down a level. In other words, after Tiger Huan used his blood lightning bead, his present strength as a God-rank expert has been reduced to Demigod-level.

Naturally, Zhao Hai wasn’t aware of this magic, after all it was a spell unique to the Divine Race. But even if Zhao Hai didn’t know about the bead, he still didn’t dare to underestimate it. Because of this, he made a move and absorbed the bead into the Space. After having the bead in the Space, he immediately threw it back out onto a place away from Shue and in the middle of the Divine Race army.

When Zhao Hai absorbed the blood lightning bead, the Space immediately issued a prompt. Only a short contact with the Space was needed to unravel the mysteries of the bead.

In general, the Space’s prompt described the bead as an aggressive hybrid energy bead. The Space can use the Blood Pond in order to manufacture it and also the Dao Lotus to provide the lightning aspect. With these ingredients, the might of the Space’s blood lightning bead was much stronger than the one Tiger Huan just made,

When Zhao Hai heard this prompt, he was immediately thrown into happiness. This was an extraordinary attacking method. If he didn’t have the Blood Pond, then he wouldn’t have the requirements to do this attack. But since he absorbed God’s blood in the past, he can now use this magic an unlimited number of times. This was extremely good news for Zhao Hai.

While Zhao Hai revelled in his happiness, the thrown blood lightning bead had exploded in the middle of the Divine Race army. The blood lightning bead was truly worthy of being called a first-rate God-rank spell. This single blast along cleared a circle fifty meters across the Divine Race army.

Every single Divine Race in this 50-meter circle was killed by the explosion. But fortunately, the formation of the Divine Race was quite spacious, the blast only killed less than ten people, their losses weren’t serious.

When Silver Shuke gave his order, Shue made use of the opportunity to attack the weakened Tiger Huan. Using one of clones, he killed Tiger Huan in one fell swoop. When Tiger Huan died, a spatial rift immediately appeared right by his body as it was absorbed into the Space. Then after reappearing, Tiger Huan looked completely restored, no injury can be spotted, but his face was paler than normal, Tiger Huan has been turned into a zombie.

However, it was a pity that although Tiger Huan has been turned into an undead, he wasn’t able to promote the levels of the undead. This disappointed Zhao Hai.

Judging by the Domain that Tiger Huan used, he should be of the fire element. In Zhao Hai’s mind, Tiger Huan should be able to turn the fire element in the Space into God-rank. Even if their level wasn’t too high, they should be Demigods at the very least. Unfortunately, the Space didn’t issue any prompt.

But since Silver Shuke had started their move, Zhao Hai didn’t have the mood to think about any of these. His figure moved as he pulled Shue and Berry away from the approaching army. At this moment, a war cry was heard behind him, it was the silver Divine Race army.  Silver Shuke couldn’t help but make a smug look towards Zhao Hai, he wanted to see the startled expression on Zhao Hai’s face. He even wanted to say some disparaging words, knocking Zhao Hai’s pride down a notch.

But much to his disappointment, Zhao Hai wasn’t startled at all. On the contrary, he was looking at the Shuke with a smug look. Silver Shuke couldn’t help but stare, then an unlucky premonition suddenly rose in his mind.

“Is he hiding something?” The Shuke muttered to himself. Then he immediately found the answer, coming from the walls of the city were blue beams coming towards the army, the magic cannons had started to fire!

The Silver Shuke was startled by Zhao Hai’s magic cannons, however, his heart immediately calmed down, he couldn’t help but sneer and said, “Magic cannons? Hahaha. Zhao Hai, you you really think that you can deal with us using inferior weapons such as magic cannons? I thought that you’re much smarter than this.”

Zhao Hai looked at the Silver Shuke and then sneered, “Really? Inferior magic cannons?”

100 magic cannons weren’t a lot, however, an entire salvo coming from all of them looked quite frightening. The Divine Race just neglected them since they thought that they weren’t anything serious.

However, this thought made them suffer a loss. Those who were hit by the magic cannons didn’t care much about it. Some of them might cast a defensive magic, but most of them were too lazy to do cast anything. They intend to use their own physique to defend against the attacks of the magic cannons.

Only when the blue light hit their bodies did they discover that something was wrong. A powerful chill immediately rushed into their bodies. After their initial shock, they immediately went on to push the cold air out, however, they discovered that their meridians had been sealed with ice!

Chapter 731: Machine Gun and Artillery

The Divine Race who were turned into ice were immediately absorbed into the Space and were quickly turned into undead.

The attack of the magic cannon made the Divine Race army surprised. They never expected that the simply useless magic cannons would actually kill a hundred of them. This made the Divine Race army startled, but this disturbance quickly calmed down.

The silver commander looked at this with shock. He didn’t think that the Ark Continent’s magic cannons would actually be this powerful.

At this time, Zhao Hai led Berry and Shue back to the city. Then when they managed to enter it, the magic formation immediately activated.

When the magic formation got up, Zhao Hai laughed towards Silver Shuke and said, “Silver Shuke, are you convinced of our magic cannons now?” Then Zhao Hai’s figure vanished as he mounted a sneak attack on the approaching Divine Race army.

Silver Shuke stared, but he knew that he couldn’t underestimate the magical formation of the city. Although the protective shield didn’t look any different, he still made a careful order, “Let me break the formation first!”

The Divine Race army complied, then they reformed their square formation before Silver Shuke went to the skies and wielded his sword to attack the blue protective shield.

However, Zhao Haid didn’t care about them at this time. His attention was currently on the sneaking army from behind. These people weren’t a lot, only about ten thousand people, however, they were all God-rank experts. But even with their current strength, this army still found themselves in a bad situation. They were currently faced with undead both in their front as well as their back.

They were veterans in the battlefield, so it only took them a single glance to tell that the undead numbered about 2 million, this was a fearful sight for a small army such as them.

They wanted to do a sneak attack, going behind the enemy and eliminating them in one fell swoop. But who would’ve thought that they would actually be the ones who were caught in a trap. It seems like the enemy was aware of their actions and was already waiting for them here.

First was the magic cannon eliminating 100 of their kind, and then there was this undead ambush. Moreover, the army that could reinforce them had actually been blocked by the defensive formation of the city.

Although these soldiers were God-rank, they were too few in the end, only ten thousand people. On the other hand, they were faced with 9th rank undead that numbered in the millions. In this case, without Silver Shuke’s group, they would certainly meet a quick and unfortunate death.

After knowing about their situation, the small Divine Race army steeled themselves. They knew that as long as they resist for a long time and wait for Silver Shuke’s aid, then they would have a chance to survive. However, if they were to fall into Zhao Hai’s hand, then they would definitely be exterminated.

These Divine Race fellows weren’t fools. They came to the Ark Continent and also saw what happened to the Radiant Empire. Not a single citizen was left alive, and sole reason for this was the Divine Race’s magic formation.

These people were nothing in the eyes of the Divine Race. In their minds, these people were no different to magic beasts, they didn’t care no matter how many died.

However, the Divine Race also understood that their slaughter would definitely cause an irreversible hatred from the Ark Continent, especially Zhao Hai.

Even the Divine Race had heard of Zhao Hai’s name, this person had destroyed a lot of plans that the Radiant Church had made. If not for Zhao Hai, then they wouldn’t have been compelled to use their magic formation. But even then, Zhao Hai still had a grudge with the Radiant Church, and similarly to the Divine Race. If Zhao Hai were to forgive them, then that would certainly be very strange.

At this time, the trapped Divine Race army still believed that Silver Shuke would be able to break the formation in a short time. As long as the protective shield gets broken, then Zhao Hai wouldn’t have the time to deal with them. When that time comes, they would use the opportunity to escape the undead entrapment.

However, these people have extremely underestimated Zhao Hai’s strength. Although these people were God-rank, they were still ordinary God-ranks. And in Zhao Hai had a lot of God-rank undead in his hand.

When these people started to form their battle formation, preparing themselves to battle Zhao Hai, he suddenly made a move, throwing blood lightning beads towards them.

These God-rank experts didn’t expect Zhao Hai to throw blood lightning beads one after another. Just as they were dumbfounded, the blood lightning beads exploded.

After a loud bang, several gaps were seen in the Divine Race’s formation. Zhao Hai was very satisfied with the might of the blood lightning beads. However, he was also disappointed by the fact that the explosions of the blood lightning beads immediately turned the God-rank corpses into dust. When this happens, it would be impossible for him to turn them into undead.

However, when he saw that the formation has been broken, Zhao Hai immediately shouted, “Kill them, spare nobody!” Then Zhao Hai waved his hand as all the God-ranked undead that he had charged towards the opposing Divine Race army.

Shue also made his move, 1000 of his clones simultaneously threw themselves towards the Divine Race Army. In addition, Berry, Shiying, and the light element undead as well as Zhao Hai’s own attacks also flooded towards the Divine Race army. All of a sudden, the Divine Race army was divided into different independent squads.

However, these people were worthy to be called elite. After their initial disturbance, they quickly stabilized themselves and started to resist.

These people were God-ranks who had comprehended their Domains. At this time, they simultaneously made their DOmains appear. What surprised Zhao Hai was the fact that their Domains were actually the same, all of them formed a long spear.

When Zhao Hai saw this, his heart couldn’t help but turn cold. He didn’t care about these ten thousand people, what he cared about was the might of the Divine Race.

Selecting 10 thousand God-ranked experts with the same Domain wasn’t easy. For them to do so was a testament to their military might. This was too astonishing.

But even if Zhao Hai was startled, he still went on and continued his assault. He knew that the formation wouldn’t hold up for too long against Silver Shuke’s constant attacks. At the same time, the opposing 1 million army wasn’t something that can just be disregarded. Although Zhao Hai had placed a lot of crystal stones on the city’s formation, he knew that they couldn’t support the protective shield indefinitely. Therefore, he needed to eliminate these people as soon as possible.

Zhao Hai’s present strength was much more formidable than any ordinary God-rank. These people simply couldn’t resist Zhao Hai’s attacks. One after another, Domains were broken and people were killed before being turned into undead. In turn, these new undead would then turned on their previous allies, this was the convenience of black magic.

At this moment, Zhao Hai felt that the defensive formation of the city started to fluctuate, then it vanished. However, Zhao Hai didn’t turn back, he waved his hand and released close to ten million undead to charge towards the approaching Divine Race army.

Silver Shuke’s eyes were now red, he didn’t think that their first conquest would have this disappointing result. Under his own eyes, 10 thousand elite soldiers were being killed. This was something unforgivable, he needed to kill Zhao Hai’s group in order to satiate the hatred in his heart.

However, after he saw the dense and numerous undead, Silver Shuke knew that his hatred needed to be reeled in. He clenched his teeth as he gave a command, “Battle formations! Kill them all!”

The Divine Race army immediately grouped themselves accordingly before establishing their Domains. Almost immediately, all kinds of Domains appeared in front of Zhao Hai’s undead army.

One must say that the Divine Race really did have the real skills. Not only did they gather similar Domain, they also grouped them into teams. With this arrangement, these people would be able to support each others’ Domains in order to oppose the enemy. With how well coordinated they were, their might would surely be very formidable.

However, the Divine Race didn’t expect that the undead would suddenly form their own formations. Then all of a sudden, blue light suddenly fired off. Every single person hit by this blue light has been frozen, then they vanished before coming back as an undead.

This was a type of formation that Lizzy and Megan had developed. They would use large bodied undead, such as the Dragons, and then place magic cannons on their bodies. They would then be able to be used as mobile turrets, allowing more flexibility in the usage of the magic cannons.

Although this method was good, the magic cannons on Zhao Hai’s hands were just too few. He simply couldn’t just use it to pressure the Divine Race.

However, they still had other means which were the blood lightning beads. If the magic cannons could be used by Zhao Hai as machine guns, then these blood lightning beads would be like artillery shells. A lot of undead had these blood lightning beads in their hands and would occasionally thrown them into the Divine Race army.

But Zhao Hai also discovered the the might of these blood lightning beads were also limited, especially to those God-ranks who had their own Domain. The blood lightning can still affect them, but only when it exploded in close range, of which the Divine Race could just eliminate the undead.

Although the blood lightning bead and magic cannons were limited regarding its capabilities to suppress the Divine Race, they still managed to divert some of the Divine Race’s attention. With the possible lethal consequences of these two things, the Divine Race also needed to consider dodging their attacks. As the matter stands, the Divine Race was currently mired in a sticky situation of the battlefield.

Silver Shuke was starting to worry. Their side only had about a million people while Zhao Hai’s undead numbered to ten million. At this time, Zhao Hai’s 100 magic cannons changed their crystal to fire type ones. The red beams coming from these magic cannons were now causing explosions, which was also quite lethal to the Divine Race army. These actions actually made it impossible for the Divine Race army to make a counter-attack.

Chapter 732: King of Kings

Since they cannot repel the undead, then they can’t rescue the 10 thousand trapped soldiers. Silver Shuke can just watch as they get slaughtered by Zhao Hai.

For the first time, Silver Shuke felt being powerless. This feeling only came to him when he fought with other races in the Divine Realm. He didn’t expect to have this feeling while in the Ark Continent.

The 10 thousand troops that went on to sneak attack Zhao Hai  suffered serious casualties. At this point, 2000 of them were already left after the others were killed and turned into undead, and this number continued to decrease.

Nobody could blame the Divine Race army for being unable to fight back. After all, they were now being assaulted by more than 10 thousand God-ranks, and some of them were even their former comrades. These undead allies weren’t weak, and all of them were even able to establish their Domains. It was no wonder that they had been completely suppressed.

More than 10 thousand people attacking 2000. Moreover, their strengths were almost identical. For the 2000 Divine Race army to be able to defend up to this point was already laudable. However, they were now beginning to get tired.

These people haven’t used spells like the blood lightning beard. This was because they knew that even if this magic was useful to humans, they were completely useless to the undead.

When the Divine Race went to fight the undead, they discovered how formidable the durability of these undead were. Even if their arms and legs were crippled, they could still fight for quite some time. This ability was something that was absent from these Divine Race people.

Zhao Hai didn’t have the mood to care about what the Divine Race was thinking. All he wanted to do right now was to quickly eliminate this army so that he can turn to deal with Silver Shuke’s group.

After about half an hour, the 2000 remaining soldiers were finally eliminated by Zhao Hai. Then Zhao Hai turned to Silver Shuke’s group as well as the battle that was currently happening.

One could see the miserable losses that the undead had suffered. The attacks of the Divine Race army wasn’t a joke. The might of their combined Domains wasn’t any worse than the attack of the magic cannons. With how clumped up the undead were, it was no wonder that the losses were what they were.

Zhao Hai asked Lizzy and the others about their casualties, of which Lizzy provided the answer. From the time the city has been attacked to the present, the undead losses had already numbered to more than 20 thousand.

This figure was within Zhao Hai’s expectations. After all, the undead that he had sent were all 9th ranks. Naturally, they would be in a very disadvantageous place against the Divine Race. It can be said that if Zhao Hai wasn’t able to discover the might of the magic cannons as well as acquire the blood lightning beads, then there would be even more casualties. Once Zhao Hai killed 10 thousand Divine Race soldiers, then he might have already lost undead that numbered to the millions.

Zhao Hai’s new undead in the Space now counted up to twenty thousand, majority of them were from the prior Divine Race army. Only a few of them were acquired from the magic cannon attacks.

Although Zhao Hai has been doing well in dealing with the Divine Race army, it was still impossible for him to repel them. After all, the God-ranks in his hand were too few.

Silver Shuke also noticed that Zhao Hai had turned his head to their direction. His blood red eyes looked straight at him. The troops under his command had just been exterminated by this Human in front of him. Moreover, they were turned into undead, this made Silver Shuke angry. But since he was embroiled with the battle with the undead, he still couldn’t order a full charge.

One must say that Silver Shuke was an outstanding military man. He knew that keeping a clear mind in the battlefield was essential to being an effective commander. If his thoughts were to slip, then he might get killed.

A reason why he hadn’t ordered his army to mount a full charge was because he was afraid of the blood lightning beads in the hands of the undead. To be honest, Silver Shuke didn’t look to highly upon blood lightning beads in the past. In his opinion, although the might of these beads were strong, the time to prepare them was also quite long. Moreover, after being launched, one couldn’t control them. If the opponent doesn’t dodge and just stood there, then they might get destroyed, otherwise, the bead would just be useless.

However, after seeing Zhao Hai’s undead army and the blood lightning bead on their hands, Silver Shuke discovered that his previous thoughts were very wrong. Blood lightning beads could actually be used as an ultimate weapon, it almost single handedly blocked the advance of the Divine Race army.

If these undead only threw the blood lightning beads, then Shuke wouldn’t have been worried since the explosions can just be easily avoided. As long as they coordinate well, then they can definitely avoid the blood lightning beads.

However, Shuke was quick to discover that the undead had another method of using the blood lightning beads. As long as a soldier takes the initiative to clash, then the undead would immediately take several blood lightning beads and directly detonates itself near the soldier. This would ensure mutual destruction to both parties. This was the method that gave Silver Shuke the most headache.

The undead weren’t afraid of death, however, it was a different matter regarding the Divine Race. Although they had formidable strength, they were still people in the end, they were also afraid of death. Because of this, the suicide attacks of the undead had made them afraid to proceed any further.

Actually, Zhao Hai didn’t want to use such a methods. The undead in the Space were intelligent, they weren’t any different from a normal person. In this case, making the undead kill themselves by explosion left Zhao Hai a bad taste in his mouth.

However, if he didn’t do this, then he wouldn’t be able to block the attacks of the Divine Race. This method wasn’t Zhao Hai’s original thought. Back on Earth, he had seen suicide bombers in the TV, bombs in driven cars or even just inside walking people. Whenever he sees these, he would groan, but he didn’t think that he himself would have do it.

In the end, Zhao Hai had to recognize how effective this method was. After a few suicide bombings by the undead, Silver Shuke began to hesitate in launching a full scale attack. This caused both sides to be in a stalemate.

Zhao Hai also looked at the other big contributors in this war, which were the magic cannons. After discovering the use of the crystals, the power of the magic cannons have been increased, becoming terrifying weapons in Zhao Hai’s hands.

But Zhao Hai was still not satisfied with this. He had all the alchemist in the continent unite and start to develop a new magic cannon. He had three requests for them, make a powerful cannon, make it more durable than the existing ones, and make them waste as less energy as possible.

Before the new magic cannon was developed, Zhao Hai had already told Patriarch Billy about it, having the Dwarves help with the process. Zhao Hai wanted to produce the ultimate magic cannon that was fit to be used in the war.

The newly promoted 9th ranks now had a new purpose, they were now in charge of refilling the empty crystal stones.

Zhao Hai had a lot of these crystals in the Space. Moreover, he has Bubble, so the Space can produce these crystals over and over. However, Zhao Hai didn’t like the crystals produced by the Space, this was because most of them were of the water element. Although water element crystals were still formidable, they weren’t really geared towards offensive attacks. What Zhao Hai liked to have were fire element crystals since they had an explosive effect, causing the most amount of casualties in the battlefield. Therefore, Zhao Hai wanted to have fire element crystals to be supplied towards the frontline.

Fortunately, crystals can store energy of a different element once they are used up, making it possible to have a lot of fire element crystals. In order to meet his demand, Zhao Hai adjusted his criteria to promote people who had the fire attribute to 9th rank. He wanted to have as much fire element 9th ranks to charge the crystals.

The people on the continent had no qualms regarding Zhao Hai’s action. At this point, everyone knew about Zhao Hai’s efforts in the frontlines against the Demons and the Divine Race. Therefore, they did as much as they could to not pull on Zhao Hai’s leg.

The continent’s most powerful nation’s Emperor, the Rosen Emperor, was Zhao Hai’s father in law. In the Lyon Empire, Zhao Hai was the acting Emperor. The Buddha Emperor currently had his people take refuge in the Lyon Empire, so naturally, he would give Zhao Hai some face. At the same time, the Aksu Empire was too far from their previous power. And even if they were in their heyday, they would still refrain from going against Zhao Hai. Not only are they adjacent to the Rosen Empire, they were also right beside the Black Wasteland, of which Zhao Hai’s elite troops were stationed in. In this case, nobody in the continent would dare bare their fangs towards Zhao Hai’s direction.

Just as the Dwarf prediction said, Zhao Hai had now become the Ark Continent’s King of Kings. Although he wasn’t explicitly crowned, every single resident of the continent were still listening to his words.

At the same time, the other races of the continent also didn’t have any problems with Zhao hai. Although Zhao Hai promoted a lot of Humans to 9th ranks, he wasn’t neglecting the other races. Beastmen, Dwarves, Elves, Fishmen, all of them were given spatial water and blood pond water in order to have their own 9th ranks.

Because of this, the other major races gave Zhao Hai their approval, giving him their complete support. Zhao Hai can now be said to be the uncrowned King of the entire Ark Continent.

While the research for the new magic cannon was ongoing, Zhao Hai also sent an order to all of the races. He wanted them to search for crystal stones. Zhao Hai didn’t believe that only the Northern Icefield had these crystals. He believes that these crystals also existed on other parts of the continent, it was just that nobody paid any attention to them. Zhao Hai wanted to scour the entire continent for these crystals in order to aid the continent in the future war.

Although crystals can be recharged, they still had their breaking point. This meant that the crystals were consumable. They would certainly need as much crystals as then can in order to curb any shortages that may happen in the future.

While Zhao Hai was thinking about the magic cannons, he suddenly felt a deep and hateful gaze. He turned his head to look and saw that it was Silver Shuke!

Chapter 733: Formidable Diamond Ape Tribe

Silver Shuke’s fiery eyes were looking straight at Zhao Hai. If looks could kill, then Zhao Hai would have already died 10 thousand times. Shuke’s hatred towards Zhao Hai couldn’t be described through words.

Of course, Zhao Hai wasn’t intending to become friends with him. After all, the Radiant Empire’s citizens have been used by the Divine Race to activate their formation. Zhao Hai and the Divine Race’s enmity had now reached a point of no return.

Zhao Hai wasn’t a hero, and to be honest, he didn’t want to be. If not for the Demons and the Divine Race forcing him, then he wouldn’t have stepped forward. He wasn’t afraid to live off of two acres of land with his wives, have a kid who would give him headaches, and even a cow to take care of. Inside his heart, Zhao Hai really didn’t have that much of an ambition.

However, the pressure brought by both the Demons and the Divine Race had compelled him to fight for survival, making him end up to where he is today. He didn’t want to be a hero, but he already made a lot of connections in the continent, he had friends, relatives, loved ones, his home, and he didn’t want all of them to get affected.

The people in the Radiant Empire had nothing to do with him, he hadn’t even visited the country before. He thought of it as the lair of the Radiant Church, his biggest nemesis. Therefore, how could he visit such a place.

However, he couldn’t help but be enraged when he saw the fate of the Radiant Empire’s citizens. This meant that the Divine Race didn’t see the people in the Ark Continent as people, and this angered Zhao Hai.

In fact, in Zhao Hai’s eyes, the Divine Race were no longer people. They were monsters in humans skin, they were beings that would forever be his enemies.

Zhao Hai looked at Silver Shuke and then smiled faintly. He gave Silver Shuke a small bow as he said, “Thief Shuke, do you still want to decide victory and defeat today?” Silver Shuke knew what Zhao Hai meant. Before, Zhao Hai said that his name sounded like a thief’s name, so he called Shuke Thief Shuke. To be honest, Zhao Hai’s naming had made Shuke feel uncomfortable, however, he couldn’t do anything about it.

After Zhao Hai said this, Shuke looked at the army that he brought. Some of his men were turned into undead by Zhao Hai, and more than 20 thousand of them were blown up by the blood lightning bead. The losses of this battle had exceeded 30 thousand. This didn’t count the wounded, their losses absolutely weren’t small.

Although Shuke’s army numbered a million, they were also the vanguard forces. The vanguard shouldn’t have too much losses upon entering the continent, otherwise, the succeeding armies would find it hard to transfer here.

After thinking up to here, Silver Shuke coldly snorted and said, “We’ll let you off today, Zhao Hai. Just you wait, when the main Divine Race army comes, then we will certainly eliminate you.” Zhao Hai smiled faintly and replied, “If you think you are confident, then feel free to do so.” Silver Shuke snorted, then he ordered, “Reform your ranks and slowly retreat!” It didn’t take too long before the Divine Race army formed their ranks and slowly went back.

Zhao Hai didn’t pursue them, he just calmly looked at Shuke’s army. Shue and Berry were also right beside Zhao Hai. Shue received his clones while Berry went out of her stealth. All of them looked at the retreating silver army. At the same time, Silver Shuke was also paying attention to Zhao Hai.

When the army got back to the Radiant Empire, Zhao Hai, Berry, and Shue immediately went back to the Space.

Upon reaching the Space, Zhao Hai immediately turned to Lizzy and said, “Lizzy, have you calculated our losses?” Lizzy nodded and said, “We did, in the battle, we used a total of 892 crystals. The undead casualties surpassed a hundred thousand. However, we also received about twenty thousand God-rank undead. Moreover, the Space just gave a prompt, all fire element undead had now been upgraded to God-rank, but they only have Demigod level strength.”

Zhao Hai was happy, “A prompt? Why haven’t I heard of it? I may be too focused on the fight. Anyway, that’s good. We have more fire element undead compared to the light element ones. How many new God-rank undead do we have?”

Lizzy smiled and said, “Right now, we have more than 20 million undead in the Space. However, majority of them are marine life forms, so almost all of them have the water attribute. In comparison, we don’t have that much fire element undead. In total, we have less than two million fire element undead. Although they only have Demigod strength, they aren’t that weak.”

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “Good, fantastic. With these undead, the Divine Race would surely be surprised at our next clash.”

Lizzy nodded and smiled, “With these many undead, along with the magic cannons and crystals, we could definitely block the next advance of the Divine Race. However, things wouldn’t be that easy, Big Brother Hai, we just went to take a look, the Demon army has increased significantly. The God-ranks in their camp had already reached a thousand. Moreover, this number has been constantly increasing.

Zhao Hai nodded, although it looks like the number of the Demon Race’s God ranks were incomparable to the Divine Race, he still didn’t underestimate them. The Demon Race’s fighting prowess can be seen as the strongest out of all the parties currently in the Ark Continent, it had something to do with how they lived back in the Demon Realm. Additionally, according to Cai’er, the Demon population was much more than the Ark Continent. And with how formidable their 9th ranks were, Zhao Hai didn’t dare to neglect them.

Zhao Hai let out a long sigh and said, “The Demons shouldn’t be acting for quite a while, however, I will still send light element undead to face them. Once we have the light element undead stationed there, then we can rest assured. After all, we now have a lot of God-rank undead, separating 10 thousand wouldn’t be much of a loss for our side.”

Lizzy nodded, at this time, Laura walked in. Zhao Hai looked at her and said, “How is it?” Zhao Hai was asking about the state of the crystals. In this battle, they had used more than 800 crystals. This rate of consumption wasn’t small. After having emptied the crystals, Zhao Hai immediately had them sent to the Space and then to the different parts of the continent, making the various 9th ranks input more energy into them.

For the battles, they would need fire element crystals with a small amount of earth element as well. The fire element had the strongest attacking power while the earth element had the strongest defense. The earth element crystals would be used in the defensive formations, they should be much better compared to the water element.

When she heard Zhao Hai’s question, Laura smiled faintly and said, “It’s going alright. They had already started to recharge the crystals. However, the energy of those 9th ranks are still too low. It takes several people to fill up an entire crystal.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Don’t worry, just take your time. Filling those 800 crystals shouldn’t take too much time. Right, how is the situation with the magic cannons, are they being done?”

Laura smiled and said, “Rest assured, you might not be aware of the Dwarf craftsmanship, but they used to be experts in making weapons like these. However, they still need to familiarize themselves. They are able to make 30 magic cannons per day at this point, but this rate would surely increase in the coming days.” Zhao Hai nodded, “That’s great, with the Dwarves’ help, we can relax even more. Right, how about the Diamond Ape tribe, how are they doing?”

The Diamond Ape Tribe was a powerful warring race. Their attacking strength was very strong, and upgrading their levels was something that Zhao Hai saw as important. Because of this, when he thought of promoting people, he naturally couldn’t forget about them. Moreover, he was also placing more importance regarding their development.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t think that the Diamond Ape tribe’s potion consumption was vastly greater compared to the other races. Even the Elephant tribe would need less in order to promote to 9th rank. This fact astonished Zhao Hai.

After undergoing multiple investigations, Zhao Hai finally found the root of the problem. The reason why the Diamond Apes were slow to promote to 9th ranks was because both the Diamond Ape and their giant ape companion needed to be 9th ranks together in order for them to be promoted. Otherwise, it would be difficult for a Diamond Ape to promote on his own.

After having this discovery, Zhao Hai didn’t hesitate and immediately promoted both Diamond Apes as well as their companion beasts. Then Zhao Hai tested how strong they got.

The tests gave Zhao Hai a glimpse as to why the Diamond Apes were called the kings of the Beastman Race. After rising to 9th rank, the Diamond Apes would undergo a huge change. Each of them would be able to acquire a new innate skill. This skill had a great relationship with their giant ape companion, this skill was even called synthesis!

After a Diamond Ape uses this skill, their body would combine with their giant ape companion. Not only would they be able to command the actions of the giant apes, but their strength, speed, and defensive capabilities would also be greatly improved. It was a genuine, real type of fusion.

Zhao Hai estimated that the Diamond Apes now had the strength that rivalled God-rank experts. And this was regarding a Full God, not a Demigod.

However, since the Diamond Apes were still 9th ranks in the end, they weren’t able to establish a Domain. But still, once the Diamond Apes use their innate skill, their combat capabilities would improve, and they would then be able to contend with God-rank experts.

This discovery filled Zhao Hai with joy. He immediately went on and promoted the Diamond Apes en masse. But even if the Diamond Apes’ strengths had been promoted, Zhao Hai still didn’t make them go to the battlefield. The Diamond Apes had been fighting for their lives in the Northern Icefield for many years. Zhao Hai wasn’t cruel enough to plunge them into battle once more.

The Patriarch of the Diamond Apes had even told Zhao Hai countless times that they wanted to be in the battlefield. But Zhao Hai still didn’t take them there. Instead, he told them that he wanted them to guard the Black Wasteland. He discussed this matter with the Patriarch. The Black Wasteland was now Zhao Hai’s root, once the Demons or the Divine Race finds out that about this place, then they would definitely target it in their future attacks. It wouldn’t be good if a powerful guard force wasn’t stationed here. Because of this, Zhao Hai appointed the Diamond Apes to be the guardians of the wasteland, of which the Patriarch agreed. Therefore, Zhao Hai was now relieved with regards to the security of the Black Wasteland.

Chapter 734: Storm Clouds Approach

When she heard Zhao Hai’s question, Laura couldn’t help but smile and said, “They’re doing very well. The Diamond Ape Tribe currently has thirty thousand 9th rank experts. With their strength along with Grandpa Green’s group as well as Cai’er, there certainly wouldn’t be any problems in the Black Wasteland. Right, there is also a piece of good news, Origin Sword Saint has broken through to God Rank. He is the first God-rank that the Ark Continent had produced in thousands of years.” Laura’s statement was true. Origin Sword Saint was really a God-rank that managed to reach his level without the help of the Space.

Zhao Hai was glad with this news, he looked at Laura and said, “Really? Then that’s fantastic! The Ark Continent finally had its own God-rank expert. However, after arriving at God-rank, senior Origin Sword saint would still need to comprehend his own Domain. Zhao Hai said, “How about this, since we already have magic cannons as well as the crystals, he wouldn’t be needed in the Black Wasteland. Let’s have him go with us first, then I’ll have him participate in the battles. Maybe he can comprehend a Domain there.” Laura nodded and replied, “Alright, I’ll go and approach Grandpa Green about this so that he can tell Senior Origin Sword Saint. Brother Hai, when do you think the Divine Race would attack again?” Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “I don’t know. But when they decided to retreat, I was sure that they would be waiting for reinforcements. Otherwise, it would be impossible for them to deal with us with their current numbers.”

Laura nodded, then she sighed and said, “Once the Divine Race reinforcements arrive, then we wouldn’t be able to live peacefully anymore. I didn’t expect the Divine Race to be that strong.” Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Fortunately, we have several means to deal with the Divine Race. Otherwise, we would really be in trouble. We might even be compelled to move the entire continent’s population into the Space.”

Laura agreed, “But things have been very strange. I thought that after killing a fire element expert, then the Space’s fire element undead would also reach God-rank. I didn’t expect that Tiger Huan wasn’t enough to promote them. Moreover, when they did get promoted, they only had the power of a Demigod.” Zhao Hai nodded, “It really is quite strange. When we got Shiying, the Space immediately promoted all the undead assassins. But now, only after we have killed a lot of God-rank Divine Race experts did the Space decide to promote the undead. It seems like the Space’s requirements had become much stricter compared to before.” At this time, Megan replied, “Although we have a lot of God-ranked experts in our hand, majority of them still have Demigod strength. We really lack undead that have Full God strengths. On the other hand, most of the God-ranked experts in the Divine Race army have already comprehended their Domain. In terms of overall strength, we are still a few steps behind. We’re lucky to have the magic cannons to supplement this weakness. Brother Hai, currently, we have magic cannons installed in big undead such as the Dragons. But I think it would be safer it the cannons were placed inside their bodies. This way, the cannons would have a sort of protection against external attacks.”

Laura agreed and said, “But in this case, we need to have the magic cannons be fixed inside the bodies of the undead. How would we be able to do this?” Zhao Hai thought for a moment and said, “When the Dwarves make the cannons, we can have them install a few steel chains under the cannon. When they are used, those chains could latch onto the bodies of the undead, securing them in place.”

Laura nodded, “Alright, I’ll inform the Dwarves regarding this matter. With the magic cannons on the way, we would be more prepared for the future. If the Dwarves get unbearable busy with work, we can just have more blacksmiths transported from the other cities in order to help out.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and replied, “Good, then I’ll hand it over to you. However, make sure to ask the Emperors about this first. We can’t have them be dissatisfied lest we risk having a fire in our own backyard.”

Laura nodded and then turned around to leave. At this time, Zhao Hai turned his attention back to the monitor. The image shown right now was Silver Shuke’s group as well as the situation with the Divine Race.

After Silver Shuke’s group retreated from the city, they went straight back to the new land. But since they aren’t constrained to the new land like before, they had started to clean the surrounding lands and cities. All the dead people and beasts have been cremated. Obviously, they had a similar idea with the Demons. They wanted to make a foothold inside the Ark Continent.

When Zhao Hai saw that they weren’t planning on another attack, he shifter his gaze towards the Demons. The Demons were now becoming numerous. Additionally, they had already went on and occupied Demon City. With how close they were to Rising Sun City, the latter had already started to be in full alert.

However, there still weren’t a lot of God-ranked Demons in their side, this made them refrain from attacking Rising Sun City. Naturally, the Demons understood that if they have fewer experts than the Divine Race, then even if they occupy Rising Sun City, the Divine Race could just take it away from them. The Demons wouldn’t make a move until they have more experts than they had right now.

When Zhao Hai saw the state of the Demons, he became worried. If the Demons attacked frantically, then Zhao Hai wouldn’t have been worried. But they were too calm, and this was a scary matter. Having strong and calm Demons invade the continent didn’t bode to well for the residents of the Ark Continent.

But seeing that there weren’t any movements from the Demons, Zhao Hai became relieved. Then he turned his attention to the continent. The Ark Continent was still very peaceful. Although the Buddha Empire had been transformed into a battlefield, the other parts of the continent still remained to be unaffected. With Zhao Hai’s careful preparations, the Ark Continent remained very stable.

In the Accra Mountain, a defensive line has already been setup. This defense has been taken care of by Zhao Hai. A large number of people participated in this defense, it included even the Beastmen and the Fishmen. Zhao Hai wanted to rely on the Accra Mountain to mount a long defensive battle against both the Demons and the Divine Race.

Not only the surface of the Accra Mountain, even the space that the Demons had dug out was made use of. This huge space was used as a huge shelter as well as warehouse for the defenders’ needs. The blood formation here had already been used and cannot be reused, so the place had become a handy area for the forces of the Ark Continent.

Since the Accra Mountain was now devoid of any Demon presence, the movements made here was all in secret. The entire Accra Mountain had become a busy place. Even the area where the Dragons had lived had become a small base. Zhao Hai made use of the place to house his Blood Hawks.

In order to speed up the preparations, Zhao Hai assigned a lot of large magic beasts from the Space to work there. This ensured that the progress was very fast.

Seeing that nothing was wrong, Zhao Hai made a sigh of relief. He scanned all the undead in the Space and took out the big ones to be used as mobile cannons. He also assigned some undead to act as cannoneers for these moving weapons. Zhao Hai even used his metal manipulation technique to install chains and attached them into the bodies of the undead. Only when they are secured would they be more convenient to use.

The next matter was the blood lightning beads. Although the beads had their shortcomings, the Space had an unlimited supply of them. In order to prepare for wartime, Zhao Hai also started to stockpile a bunch of these beads.

Time went by as Zhao Hai’s group were busy in preparation. Laura would often take magic cannons made in the continent into the Space. Then Zhao Hai would facilitate in installing them inside the large undead.

Three days went by in a flash. While Zhao Hai was busy fixing the cannons into the undead, Cai’er suddenly flew over to him and said, “Young Master, quickly come and see this.” Zhao Hai stared for a moment. He was busy with his things inside the Space all this time, so he had Cai’er manage the monitoring of both the Demons and the Divine Race. Cai’er certainly had news regarding the Divine Race since there weren’t much changes with the Demon Race.

Zhao Hai and the others immediately went to the living room. The monitor was currently showing the current situation in the newly descended land. At this moment, a group of Divine Race people were emerging out of the new land. This time, they were flying.

This was a huge group, and in addition to the silver soldiers that Zhao Hai saw before, there were also huge magic beasts mixed in. These magic beasts weren’t the same as those seen in the Ark Continent. They were mostly white and although they were huge, they seemed to be quite docile.

These magic beasts were pulling some carts. These carts were probably made out of saint light wood due to their color. Inside those carts were large quantities of resources. But what made Zhao Hai worried was the magic cannons that were carried over. These magic cannons looked similar to the ones in the Ark Continent. However, they were much bigger, moreover, their magic formations looked more complex.

After seeing these magic cannons, Zhao Hai’s expression couldn’t help but turn ugly. He was aware that the Divine Race also had their own magic cannons, but he didn’t expect that they would look this menacing. The Divine Race’s strength was already much stronger than the Ark Continent, if the continent’s magic cannons were weak, then the cannons would’ve already been rendered useless. But now, the Divine Race had brought their own magic cannons. And from how they look, it seems like they are much more powerful than the Ark Continent’s version. This was huge trouble!

Chapter 735: How To Deal With It?

However, Zhao Hai was quick to discover an issue. The magic cannon of the other party seemed to be very heavy. Most magic beasts weren’t able to pull it at all. Although it was placed in a cart, it looked strong and powerful. From the looks of the magic beasts that carried it, it seems like it wasn’t something that one can conveniently carry. This was good news for Zhao Hai.

But when Zhao Hai saw the Divine Race people behind the magic cannons, his face couldn’t help but change. These people were different than the ones that he had clashed before. In the previous battle, the Divine Race army that he faced were infantry. On the other hand, the ones he saw right now were cavalry.

The mounts of these Divine Race cavalry were quite strange. It was a kind of horse magic beast with wings and a horn, pretty much like how a person from Earth describes a unicorn pegasus. Just by looking at them on the screen, Zhao Hai was quite sure that these magic beasts weren’t anything simple.

Each and every one of these cavalry soldiers wore light and comfortable armor. They had spears in their hands while a sword was hung on their waists. On their backs were their shields while a bow and a quiver of arrows was present on their saddles. One could see the capabilities of this Divine Race cavalry just by looking at their equipment.

In the back of this cavalry was another type of magic beast cavalry. It seems like these ones were part of the Divine Race’s heavy cavalry. All of them were in full body armor, they looked like iron golems. Their mounts were a type of rhinoceros magic beasts. Metallic gloss flashed from the skins of these beasts, they also had a dangerous gleam in their eyes, making them look violent.

Zhao Hai immediately identified the two groups as Light and Heavy Cavalry. With these two troops joining the Divine Race, their fighting strength would surely be much more formidable, it would be difficult to deal with them easily. Zhao Hai was frowning as he looked at the monitor. He wanted to see what other groups the Divine Race had brought. Before long, another group appeared. But this group made Zhao Hai rub his eyes, they didn’t seem to be soldiers. These people rode on gorgeous carriages as they talked, laughed, and drank with each other. They looked more like noble children than people who were going to war.

However, all of them were wearing all kinds of magic robes. They also had magic staffs, it seems like they are the Mage group of the Divine Race.

Zhao Hai counted the number of Mage carriages that appeared on the new land. Each carriage had, on average, five Mages, and in this caravan, there were several hundreds of carriages. In other words, the Mage group numbered a minimum of a thousand people.

But what made Zhao Hai confused was the fact that when a person reaches God-rank, their energies would undergo a change. Whether they be Mage spiritual force or Warrior Battle Qi, they would be transformed into another type of pure energy. This energy was able to be used in both warrior and mage techniques. Because of this, there really weren’t any division between Mage and Warrior when one becomes God-rank. But yet the Divine Race had all of these Mages, what was this all about?

Although he couldn’t understand it, Zhao Hai still managed to have a general idea of how many Divine Race people arrived in the continent. There were a lot of newcomers, 5 million to be exact. And this didn’t even count the logistics personnel that were assigned as support.

This number made Zhao Hai’s expression even heavier. If one counted the logistic corps, then the Divine Race group that had arrived in the Ark Continent would reach near ten million. Moreover, Cai’er also reported that the total number of magic beasts brought to the continent had numbered to 50 million. Such colossal numbers had arrived in the Ark Continent, the future seemed more worrying at this point.

Laura and the others also had a heavy heart as they stood by Zhao Hai’s side. They didn’t expect the Divine Race to send such numbers in one go.

After some time, Zhao Hai let out a long breath and said, “It looks like the Divine Race had really decided to destroy us. But this is also good. Now we can finally see the strength of the Divine Race. However, I think that these aren’t the only troops that the Divine Race had. After all, the Divine Race still had enemies, and they need their troops in order to defend against them.”

Laura was puzzled by Zhao Hai’s statement, “Where did you get that from, Brother Hai? Why haven’t I heard of that before?”

Zhao hai smiled faintly and said, “It’s because the Divine Realm is much larger than the Ark Continent. Just as Iron Hammer said, the Divine Realm is divided into 13 different continents. It is possible that the one we are facing right now were the forces from one continent. The other continents still haven’t arrived. Moreover, haven’t you discovered that the Divine Race army has been made up of veteran troops? They are very different compared to those who only finished their training and hadn’t been in the battlefield before. Otherwise, they wouldn’t have their current temperament.”

When they heard this, Laura and the others immediately turned their gazes towards the Divine Race army. And just like Zhao Hai said, most of these people seemed to be battle hardened veterans. Their temperament was very different compared to any greenhorn.

Then Zhao Hai said, “Since they had gone to the battlefield, then it meant that they had enemies. Because of this, I am fairly certain that they had more troops than this. And from what I heard from Iron Hammer, it seems like their enemies were the Gods of the foreign races.”

Laura nodded and said, “Right, Brother Hai, since you have turned some Divine Race into undead, haven’t you asked them about the Divine Race? And did you ask them about the current power distribution in the Divine Realm?”

When he heard Laura, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but give a force smile and said, “I haven’t really done that, I was too focused on the current battle to turn them into Advanced level undead. But from the method of making low-level undead, I’m quite sure that they haven’t retained their memories. Even if we ask them right now, then we wouldn’t be able to get anything.”

Laura nodded and said, “And what now? What do we do?” Zhao Hai looked at the Divine Race at the monitor and said, “We do what we need to do. After all, things will happen even if we don’t do anything. Fortunately, we had made ample preparations in the past few days. We’ll still be using the Buddha Empire in order to deal with them.”

At this time, Lizzy gave a nod and asked, “That’s the only thing we can do. Big Brother Hai, I think that the Divine Race’s Heavy Cavalry aren’t able to fly. So they should only be able to do ground battles. However, from what I can see, I’m afraid that their might is something that the Ark Continent wouldn’t be able to contend with. Have you thought of ways in order to deal with them?”

Zhao Hai looked at the Divine Race cavalry, especially the Heavy cavalry. Although the Heavy Cavalry mounts looked very heavy, they actually weren’t that slow. Even if the Ark Continent had their own heavy cavalry, they still wouldn’t be able to contend with the Divine Race. After all, the mounts of the Divine Race were at least 8th ranks, one would be hard pressed to look for those kinds of mounts in the Ark Continent.

Moreover, having this cavalry unit wasn’t only about their mount, their training would take a long time as well. There really wasn’t any heavy cavalry unit in the Ark Continent that can directly confront the heavy cavalry of the Divine Race. The closest ones who can face them would probably be among the Beastmen. But even the Herculean Bulls wouldn’t be able to face them head-on. Zhao Hai thought about it for quite some time before he turned to Lizzy and said, “It’s really hard to deal with the heavy cavalry of the Divine Race, their charges would definitely be very strong. I’ve thought of something, we can ask the Dwarves to have their iron armor beasts deal with these guys. The Dwarven cavalry is mainly composed of their iron armor beast. Since the Divine Race’s heavy cavalry can’t fly, then we can just leave them to the Dwarves.”

Lizzy thought about Zhao Hai’s suggestion and nodded, “Having the Dwarves deal with them is indeed a good idea. How about their light cavalry? Will we have the Elves deal with them?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “It seems like the Elves are the only ones that can go against those light cavalry. There is no doubt that the winged horses of the Divine Race are able to fly. Moreover, although they are mainly equipped with spears, they also have bows and arrows equipped. With our Blood Hawks, the Elves should be able to have the capabilities to fight them.”

Lizzy nodded, “It seems like we cannot just rely on our own power in order to deal with the Divine Race. They are just too strong, we can’t stop them ourselves. We should adjust the armies of the continent and ask them to come over and help.”

Zhao Hai agreed, “Right, we should have the Dwarves and the iron armor beasts, the Elves and the Blood Hawks, Rosen Empire’s heavy infantry, and the Lyon Empire’s magic beast cavalry move over. The Buddha Empire’s heavy cavalry is just too slow, if we have them fight, then they would definitely suffer huge losses. We’ll have the Rosen Empire’s heavy infantry guard the walls of the city. At the same time, we should get some of the faster cavalry units from the Beastmen and have them prepare for the battles in the Buddha Empire.”

Lizzy nodded, “Alright. Also, we should be on guard about their magic cannons. When the fight comes, we should do our best to snatch a couple of them. Then we’ll take them back and have them studied.”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “I’m afraid that would be difficult. Haven’t you noticed? The Divine Race are overly protective of their magic cannons. All of them are placed in the middle of a team of soldiers who are also in the middle of a large army. Dealing with those people wouldn’t be easy. However, moving those cannons should be very hard, so I’m not too worried about them at this point. What I’m worried about is another group of people.”

When Lizzy heard Zhao Hai, she recalled the newcomer groups, then her expression turned stern as she said, “Big Brother Hai, is it about those groups of mages?”

Chapter 736: Adjusting The Army

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Iron Hammer said that once one reaches God-rank, then their magic and battle qi would transform into a new type of energy. The Divine Race calls this Origin Force. I don’t know if it is really called that, but I can confirm that this energy can be used in both magic and battle qi applications. So in this case, why would there be a division between mage and warrior? It is impossible for the Divine Race to overlook this aspect. However, there are people in Mage attire in the Divine Race army. Don’t you think that this is strange?”

When Lizzy and the others heard Zhao Hai, they couldn’t help but gawk before knitting their eyebrows. They haven’t been paying attention when Iron Hammer talked about Origin Force, so this was the first time that they had heard about it from Zhao Hai. If what Zhao Hai said was true, then the Mages in the Divine Army really did seem very strange.

Megan looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Elder Brother Hai, are you saying that these Mages have some special skill? And this was the thing that made you unsettled?”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Right. I suspect these Mages to have something special. Otherwise, the Divine Race wouldn’t have given them this much importance. However, what did they have that made them important? The Ark Continent only had magic and battle qi while origin force is just equal to an upgraded version of the two of them. If these mages were only capable of magic, then they wouldn’t have been this respected.’

Megan knit her brows and said, “Origin Force is a transformation of battle qi and magic, so there should be no need to have mage training. Right, Brother Hai, can origin force be used to summon creatures for battle?”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare at Megan’s statement. He really didn’t know about this matter. All of his undead were taken care of by the Space, so there was no need for him to expend any energy. Because of this, he paid no attention to matters such as these.

Zhao Hai looked at Megan and said, “What you mean is, those people who look like Mages, are actually Summoners?”

Megan nodded, then said, “It’s highly probable. You can look at the Demon Lich, they have their own special summoning spells for battle. These spells would surely be useful when one becomes God-rank. Although most Mages weren’t into summoning magic, the Divine Race had fought for a long time, so they should be able to see the advantages of summons. Because of this, I reckoned that those people with Mage clothing were actually the Divine Race’s special Summoners.”

Zhao Hai nodded, he thinks that Megan’s speculation held some ground. However, this was still a guess and wasn’t proven, so he said, “That might be true. In any case, we’ll find out about them in a battle or two. Right now, we need to spread the word to the leaders of the continent, tell them about the might of the Divine Race so that they can prepare in advance. Have the citizens enter the big cities with magical formations.”

Lizzy and the other complied and then went on to do their job. At the same time, Zhao Hai continued to observe the movements of the Divine Race. After the new group arrived, they didn’t move immediately. Instead, then occupied the surrounding cities, seemingly taking a break before beginning their conquest.

Zhao Hai wanted to see how they will be arranged. But unfortunately, the Divine Race were careful. Whenever they talk about important things, they would cast isolation magic to cover the place where they would discuss. Even with Zhao Hai’s efforts, he still wasn’t able to find out about anything.

Although he couldn’t see anything significant, Zhao Hai was still paying careful attention towards the Divine Race. Even if he had limited intel, he could still see when the Divine Race would attack.

But after looking at it for a while, Zhao Hai handed the task over to Cai’er. Then he went out of the villa and continued to load the magic cannons into the undead.

At this point, the magic cannons have become their main weapon against the Demons and the Divine Race. So naturally, these things needed to be carefully taken care of. These days Zhao Hai had been very busy.

Although the Divine Race reinforcement has arrived, they didn’t immediately make a move. This caused Cai’er to continue her monitoring while Zhao Hai felt relief. The day after the Divine Race reinforcement arrived, Zhao Hai started to bring the Dwarf Iron Armor Beast Cavalry, the Elven Blood Hawk Cavalry, the Lyon Empire Beast Cavalry, the Beastman Race’s Wolf, Dog, Cat, and Horse tribes into his current location. The Rose Empire Heavy Infantry has been brought over as well. The entire city has been transformed into a huge military barrack.

Fortunately, Zhao Hai’s prestige was quite high with these groups. There was no chaos when those groups arrived in the city. Zhao Hai also allocated camps for each of them so that he wouldn’t worry too much.

However, coordinating them for war has become an issue. The foreign races only listen to Zhao Hai, while the two people sent by the Rosen and Lyon Empire to lead the army both had the same status. None of the two wanted to listen to the other.

In the end, Zhao Hai sent Lizzy to have the job of commander for the unified army. This made people surprised, however, upon thinking of Lizzy’s status, all of them agreed.

Lizzy was the Rosen Empire’s princess, and she was also Zhao Hai’s wife. These two titles aren’t simple, especially her being Zhao Hai’s wife. This made those present in the city behave.

The thing in the minds of these people was the same in the minds of the Lyon Empire nobles. The reason why Zhao Hai had Lizzy command the war was only for show, and Zhao Hai would still be the person being in command in the background. However, they didn’t expect that Lizzy was actually more skilled in commanding a battle compared to Zhao hai.

Although this was the first time that Lizzy commanded a diverse army, she still had an experience in handling a huge army in the past. Moreover, Zhao Hai also had Megan add into the discussion and express her abilities in front of the people. With the Megan and Lizzy coordinating together, it  didn’t take too long before the whole city got into order.

Zhao Hai didn’t dare to spoil the two of them. Although both Lizzy and Megan were beautiful women, they were truly skilled in command, they had a huge potential to become generals. In the past, they were lacking in terms of battle experience. However, after experiencing battles back in the sea as well as in the fight against the Demon Race, Zhao Hai was now assured of the two’s ability.

It took two days for the armies to arrive. The reason for their quick travel was Zhao Hai’s Space, every minute was crucial. Zhao Hai also wanted the soldiers to be familiar with the surrounding terrain, which would benefit them in the future battle.

Moreover, the Divine Race reinforcement had arrived, and it was possible for them to attack at any time. In this case, Zhao Hai couldn’t afford to have the armies arrive in a slow rate.

Back in Demon City, Zhao Hai had the confidence to deal with the Demon Race. Even if he didn’t attack on his own, he was still confident in his ability to defend.

However, when he saw the Divine Race Army, Zhao Hai knew that it was impossible to fight with them with his own strength. Average soldiers in the Divine Race army were 9th ranks. At the same time, the numbers of God-ranks that the Divine Race had was much more than the God-ranks in Zhao Hai’s side. If he wanted to defend against the Divine Race with his own strength, then he definitely wouldn’t be able to defend for several days. All of the undead in his hands were not enough to block the attack of the Divine Race.

In this case, Zhao Hai had to let the other powers into the City to defend against the Divine Race together. This would also awaken the continent, making them aware about how serious the frontline has become.

Besides having them fight in the city, Zhao Hai also wanted to make the various parties see the situation with their own eyes. They needed to see how powerful the Divine Race were.

Ever since the Divine Race arrived in the continent, the powers of the continent haven’t really had a proper battle with them. This made the groups of the Ark Continent ignorant to the real strength of the Divine Race. This time, Zhao Hai asked for troops in order to make them aware of the strength of the enemy.

The reason why Zhao Hai thought of this idea was because of his observations in the past few days. In the various territories in the continent, he discovered that although the countries were placed into a state of war, the people had actually turned idle, all of them were thinking that the war was too far from their own place. Because of this, their mindsets had taken a form of distance towards the frontline. Zhao Hai thought that this wasn’t a great thing.

Such mentality cannot continue. Zhao Hai knew that if people were to think like this, then the upper powers would surely exhibit it sooner or later. If this was the case, then the future cooperation would slowly crumble.

Zhao Hai discovered that this issue was especially strong in the Rosen and Aksu Empires. The citizens weren’t as anxious compared to the residents of the Lyon and Buddha Empire. The citizens of the Buddha Empire were far away from their homes, so it was natural that they felt strong attachment towards this war, and this sentiment was carried over to the Lyon Empire citizens. However, this sense of crisis seemed to be lacking in both the Rosen and Aksu Empires.

Through this matter, Zhao Hai had found out that he was being overprotective towards the people of the Ark Continent. This caused them to forget about how cruel war could be. If they continue to think this way, then the consequences would be disastrous when the Divine Race decides to send small teams to wreak havoc in the backlines of the Ark Continent.

Because of this, Zhao Hai decided to invite large armies into Upper Bank City.

Chapter 737: The Fight Begins

Zhao Hai was currently standing on top of the city wall. The protective formation was already in place and the army were properly positioned. Everyone present here were looking at the direction of the Radiant Empire.

This wasn’t a practice run, they were now in full preparation to resist the incoming army. Cai’er already told Zhao Hai that the Divine Race army had started to make their move. This time, the Divine Race placed both of their cavalries up front, supported by their infantry and Mage corps. They were preparing to rush straight into the city and break through it in one go.

It was because of this that Zhao Hai’s side had started to behave like this. It has been three days since all of the Ark Continent’s powers had sent their troops over to the city. To be honest, the Divine Race refraining from making their attack had made Zhao Hai quite worried. It was only now that they made their move did Zhao Hai felt relief.

If the Divine Race didn’t attack, then it meant that they had a bigger plot in their hands. If they attacked, then it meant that there weren’t any sneaky plans. It seems like the three days were used in pure recuperation.

In Zhao Hai’s side was a Dwarf, an Elf, a heavily armored man, a cavalry soldier, some Beastmen, as well as Lizzy, Megan, Berry, and Shue.

These people were the city’s management staff. Zhao Hai wanted them to see how fierce the Divine Race looked.

On the walls beside them were the Rosen Empire’s heavy armor infantry. Although these troops were used generally for field battles, they were still able to defend a city comfortably. After all, they were Rosen Empire’s elite. At this moment, magic cannons were strewn all around the city’s walls. Zhao Hai didn’t make the undead control these cannons, instead, he handed them over to the heavy armor infantry.

Zhao Hai stood calmly on the city wall, although the army had yet to come, the whole city was full of anticipation. There was a sense of breathlessness emanating among the troops.

The Dwarf standing next to Zhao Hai muttered as he stared at the Radiant Empire’s direction, “Why haven’t they appeared yet? I can’t wait all day.”

Zhao Hai turned his head to look at the Dwarf. This Dwarf wasn’t an elder, he was a General of the Dwarf Race, the commander of the Iron Beast cavalry. This time, the Dwarves had sent over a hundred thousand iron armor cavalry, this wasn’t a small number.

Moreover, after arriving at the city, the Dwarves started to make their move. In the plains outside the city, they had made a lot of tunnels. These tunnels would allow ordinary troops to pass through safely without any issue. However, once the Divine Race’s Heavy Cavalry walks on top of them, they would immediately collapse, and the Dwarves would be waiting underground to ambush them. As long as they go under, the Dwarves, in their natural habitat, would gain absolute advantage.

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Baker, no need to be anxious. They will arrive soon.”

The Dwarf Baker smiled faintly and said, “I’m quite anxious to see how formidable those Divine Race fellows really are. For me to be able to help the elder is a great blessing. You might not know, but when the clan voted me to be sent over, the other Generals almost fought with me over it.”

Zhao Hai laughed and then replied, “Are you sure you won’t regret it? You’re going to battle right now, but I don’t want you to die. Baker, remember to have safety as your utmost priority.”

Baker nodded and said, “Elder, rest assured, we’ve already prepared for it. The Dwarves wouldn’t die so easily.”

At this moment, a Beastmen inserted, “We aren’t afraid of death as well. Prince, when will you send us out to attack?”

Zhao Hai gave a slight smile and said, “Don’t worry, you will have the chance to fight. Even if the main actors this time are the Dwarves and Elves, you should still prepare yourselves for battle. All of you, remember to make ranged attacks as much as possible. Especially the Elves, the enemy’s cavalry isn’t weak.”

Standing on the wall was a male Elf, he had a handsome but messy face. He always had a cold expression but when he heard Zhao Hai he gently nodded and said, “The elder can rest assured, the Elves aren’t afraid of death as well.”

Zhao Hai sighed and then said, “I know that you don’t fear death. However, I didn’t take you here to die. You could be said to be the continent’s first batch of troops to fight against the Divine Race. As long as you survive, then you would understand the attack patterns of the Divine Race. Their tactics cannot be understood in just one or two days. You must keep on living and teach the others about how to resist against the Divine Race. I hope that we can repel the Demons and the Divine Race with as little losses to the continent as possible.”

The group nodded, then Zhao Hai continued, “This war isn’t going to good for our side. Both the Demon and the Divine Realm is much larger than the Ark Continent. And their residents are leagues stronger than us. Because of this, we cannot have the mentality of sacrificing ourselves in battles. It’s not that I’m afraid of death, I just don’t want unnecessary deaths. Do you understand?”

The group nodded once more. Although these people wouldn’t generally listen to other race’s words, it was a different matter when it came to Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai’s influence had been spread out to all of them. At the same time, their groups were also grateful to Zhao Hai. This was the reason why there were no problems when it came to him making the decisions.

At this time, sound of rumbling was suddenly heard in the distance while the earth shook at the same time. As long as one had experience, then they would surely know that this was due to the movement of Heavy Cavalry. The charge of a heavy cavalry unit was the most imposing thing that one can see in the battlefield. Their movements alone could make the earth shiver, if any other troop dared to clash with them at this state, then they would certainly get crushed.

Every person on the walls were attracted towards this rumbling noise. Before long, a silver film had started to fill the grounds in the distance. This silver film approached quite quickly, and their imposing aura could be felt as they kick up dust while they approach.

Zhao Hai turned his head to Baker and said, “Baker, you go. Remember, the number you kill doesn’t matter. Just make sure to protect your lives. It still isn’t time to go all out against the Divine Race.” Baker gave a nod before he turned back an entered the tunnels.

Then Zhao Hai turned to the Elf and said, “The Divine Race’s light cavalry should be arriving soon, you should prepare yourself as well. Remember, just like what I said to the Dwarves, the kills doesn’t matter. Just make sure to protect your lives. The Blood Hawks are fast, take good advantage of this.” The Elf gave a salute before he turned around and left the wall.

Then Zhao Hai turned his head towards the group of Beastmen and said, “You go prepare as well. Head outside the city using the back door. Coordinate with the Dwarves. Although the cavalry speed of the Divine Race isn’t slow, they still couldn’t catch up to your troops. Don’t think of going all out, just fight with the intention of finding out about their strength.”

The Beastmen nodded then they gave a short bow before leaving. Zhao Hai turned his head to Lizzy and Megan, “The undead command will be handed over to you. Cai’er, come out and help. Berry, Shue, let’s go.” Then Zhao Hai summoned his bone dragon as he flew out of the city. At this time, Cai’er appeared in Lizzy’s shoulder. Cai’er waved her hand as a screen appeared in front of Lizzy and Megan. This will help them facilitate the battle more conveniently.

Lizzy and Megan looked at the projection and saw a group of green lights approaching. They were already aware that the green lights were the enemies while the red lights were their allies. Since they had yet to release the undead, the red lights this time were only composed of Zhao Hai’s group as well as the Dwarves in the field.

Zhao Hai was also starting to see the other party’s light cavalry. The horned pegasus were flapping their wings as they flew forwards. All of them flew with grace, but were not so fast. However, Zhao Hai didn’t dare look down on them. These horned pegasus naturally weren’t using their maximum speed. When the battle starts, their actions certainly wouldn’t be like this.

However, Zhao Hai’s main attention wasn’t in these flying cavalry. Instead, he was focused on the Mage corps behind the light cavalry. Although Megan speculated them to be Summoners, nobody knew for sure whether this was correct. This compelled Zhao Hai to pay more attention to their group compared to the others.

When the horned pegasus were several kilometers away from Zhao Hai, a clump of red cloud suddenly appeared behind the city. Naturally, this red cloud was the Elven Race’s Blood Hawk cavalry.

After the Blood Hawk cavalry flew out of the city, they immediately dashed towards the Divine Race’s light cavalry. This made the horned pegasus cavalry stare. The Divine Race were aware of the races in the Ark Continent, therefore, they certainly had some understanding regarding the Elves. However, they didn’t know that the Elves had managed to have their own aerial troops.

To be honest, nobody could blame the Divine Race for this. After the Radiant Church suppressed the Elves, their understanding of the race had become too few. Although they had sent some spies towards the Elven Forest, their main purpose was to control the race and not to report back on their findings. Since this was the case, the spies didn’t go out of their way to exit the forest. This also made it possible for the Elves to hide their aerial troops.

However, even if they were discovered, the Elven Race’s original aerial troops were composed of soundless soundbirds. But the voiceless soundbirds had no fighting prowess, they were completely herbivorous. Because of their docile nature, it would be impossible for the Elves to teach them how to fight.

But now, the Elves had the Blood Hawks. These were phantasmal beasts that were made by Zhao Hai’s Space. Their fighting strength were very strong. Even if the Divine Race were aware of the Elves’ aerial cavalry, they still wouldn’t be aware of the Blood Hawks.

However, the main reason why Zhao Hai was confident in sending the Elves to deal with the Divine Race’s light cavalry was because he had given the Elves a secret weapon. As long as the Elves us this, then they would become much stronger than the Divine Race’s light cavalry. They light cavalry unit would surely suffer heavy losses in the Elves’ hands.

Chapter 738: The Dwarves’ First Accomplishment

Secret weapon, but in fact, it wasn’t much of a secret. What Zhao Hai gave the Elves were actually blood lightning beads! The bow and arrow that the Elves use were generally based on shooting stone beads. Zhao Hai doesn’t know how they do it, but not only could they shoot round objects, they can shoot them extremely accurately. It can be said that they are the most skilled archers in the entire Ark Continent.

Because of this skill, Zhao Hai prepared a lot of blood lightning beads for the Elves to use. The might of these beads, when used on a bow and arrow, certainly wouldn’t be small.

The blood lightning bead that Tiger Huan had before definitely wouldn’t work in this manner. His blood lightning beads needed to be activated using spiritual connection. On the other hand, Zhao Hai’s blood lightning beads would produce an explosion on impact, which was more convenient to use.

The beads were the reason why Zhao Hai was confident in having the Elves face the Divine Race light cavalry. He didn’t only give the beads to the Elves, he gave some of them to the Dwarves as well. However, because of the Dwarves’ battlefield, Zhao Hai gave them instructions to not use the beads wantonly. If necessary, not use them at all.

Conversely, Zhao Hai gave the beastmen a big supply of blood lightning beads. The Beastmen were mounted warriors. Since they cannot use magic cannons, their second best choice would be the blood lightning beads.

Although Zhao Hai didn’t stop upgrading the strengths of the major races, time was still quite limited. Therefore, the average strengths of the races still weren’t up to par. To combat this disparity in strength, Zhao Hai can only provide them with blood lightning beads.

One must say that Zhao Hai was really thankful towards Tiger Huan. If it weren’t for his blood lightning bead, then Zhao Hai wouldn’t have known about this magic. They were the most efficient things to have in dealing with the Divine Race.

The Elven Blood Hawk cavalry slowly approached the Divine Race. Naturally, horned pegasus cavalry also noticed the approaching enemies. They immediately separated a small group in order to meet the Elves. The Elven cavalry quickly performed a retreat, but not before sending a barrage towards the approaching horned pegasus group.

The Elven Race’s beads were also special since they held a magic formation within itself. Although its strength was inferior to the blood lightning bead, their might was still formidable when fired towards the enemy.

However, it soon become obvious that those beads were ineffective towards the Divine Race. The horned pegasus cavalry immediately hoisted their spears as they held their shields in front of them, easily blocking the incoming attack. Zhao Hai paid attention to the shields and saw Divine Race formations engraved on them, no wonder they were defensively effective.

The Elves didn’t use their blood lightning beads yet. Zhao Hai understood their decision, they wanted to wait until the Divine Race lowers their guard before they give them the full brunt of their attack.

Zhao Hai stopped thinking about these as he released large quantities of undead. At the same time, he moved the undead mobile cannons in front, meeting the Divine Race advance.

While waiting for the enemies to get closer, Zhao Hai turned his attention towards the heavy cavalry on the ground. These Divine Race heavy cavalry naturally weren’t expecting an ambush. They were just simply and uncaringly charging towards the city.

Zhao Hai looked at the heavy cavalry and silently calculated their strength. When he came to it, Zhao Hai discovered that this heavy cavalry unit wasn’t very strong. On average, they only had 8th rank strength. This made Zhao Hai surprised.

These heavy cavalry seemed to be the worst of the Divine Race army. At first, Zhao Hai didn’t understand what was going on, but after looking into it and asking Cai’er, he finally understood.

These heavy cavalry weren’t actually completely composed of the Divine Race. Them and the Divine Race had some differences in their appearance. It seems like this heavy cavalry were completely different people!

Their foreheads were low, their mouth was slightly protruding and looked like a monkey’s mouth, completely unlike a human’s. Their body hair was also very thick. However, their bodies were big and strong, it wouldn’t be a good idea if one were to provoke them.

The weapon in their hands were also special. It was a weapon that Zhao Hai hadn’t seen before, it looked like a long sword but was actually a hammer.

Each hammer looked like it wouldn’t weigh less than fifty kilograms. Even average 8th ranks wouldn’t use such weapons for battle. An 8th rank’s battle qi would allow them to carry a 10 jin sword and fight for several hours. However, if they carry a 100 jin(50 kgs) hammer then they can carry them for an hour, at most. Aside from innately strong people, nobody would use such heavy weapons.

The Divine Race heavy cavalry seemed to be wild men. Each and every one of them were wearing heavy full body armor. They were brandishing their hammers as thought they were light. One couldn’t help but recognize their strength upon seeing such a display.

As the heavy cavalry were charging through, the ground under them suddenly collapsed. Moreover, it wasn’t a small hole, it was big enough to swallow about a thousand heavy cavalry soldiers.

Zhao Hai knew that this was the move of the Dwarves. One must say that when it came to digging, the Dwarves were the supreme masters of the art. The holes that they dug were enough to support a number of troops. But when that capacity reaches the target, then the ground would immediately collapse, eating up the unfortunate victims. This tactic had been effectively used by the Dwarves in their previous battles against mounted armies.

As the first batch heavy cavalry fell into the pit, there were also troops from behind who weren’t able to stop in time, which also caused them to fall into the pit.

The hole was actually filled with numerous stone spikes. If these spikes were used normally, then they wouldn’t have been very effective. But in this occasion, their lethality had increased by many folds. When the heavy infantry units fell into the hole, they were immediately killed by those spikes.

The Dwarves didn’t even appear from beginning to end. When these cavalry soldiers died, they immediately vanished from the pit. Those who looked into the whole only saw bloodstains, nothing else.

The remaining heavy cavalry unit couldn’t help but be surprised. But at this time, a shout can be heard behind them, compelling them to move around the pit and continued to charge forward, gradually approaching the city. However, as they went around the pit, they were once again met with a pit that was filled by stone spikes. But this time, aside from the careless ones, the hole had been rendered completely useless.

At the same time, a bunch of yellow light appeared in front of the cavalry unit, allowing them to step across the hole without falling into it.

Zhao Hai made Cai’er look into this situation. It seems like the Divine Race had used earth element magic which was evidently better than the ones used by the Dwarves. At the same time this magic also killed about a hundred Dwarves while injuring dozens.

Zhao Hai frowned, it seems like the Divine Race were quite experienced about these types of arrangements. They were very efficient in their ways of countering the Dwarves. The fluidity in their action wasn’t something that can be practiced in such a short time.

Then Zhao Hai changed his mind as he guessed the reason. The Divine Race surely had their enemies in the Divine Realm. Perhaps it was against foreign gods that used the same tactics as the Dwarves. Or perhaps they themselves were using such tactics. This explains why they were able to deal with it very quickly.

Zhao Hai didn’t actually care about this. The heavy cavalry units wouldn’t be a huge threat to the city. Additionally, with the Beastmen in coordination with the Dwarves, the situation should be placed under control soon.

Zhao Hai turned his focus to the other enemies in front of him, the horned pegasus cavalry and especially the Mage corps. He wanted to see what they would bring to the battlefield.

The horned pegasus cavalry were still gracefully flying towards Zhao Hai’s direction. The light cavalry unit numbered in the hundreds of thousands, much greater than the about hundred thousand Elven cavalry. The horned pegasus cavalry didn’t even chase the Elves. In their minds, sending a small team over should be enough to deal with them.

The Divine Race were really arrogant, but they would surely pay the price for this attitude. Zhao Hai coldly snorted, he had more than 1 million undead behind him, several hundred of which were equipped with magic cannons. Moreover, these several hundred undead didn’t carry only one magic cannon, they had multiple inside of them. Their killing power wasn’t something to be underestimated.

It was quite obvious that this horned pegasus unit was much stronger than the heavy cavalry. Although they were composed of mostly 9th ranks, they also had God-ranks among them.

Before long, the horned pegasus cavalry stopped a kilometer away from Zhao Hai. They just stood in place as they looked at his direction. They didn’t move and they didn’t speak, it seems like they were waiting for something.

Zhao Hai didn’t speak as well. He looked as the infantry behind the light cavalry arranged themselves. Then the Divine Race mages started to fly towards him.

Zhao Hai looked at these people, he didn’t know what they wanted to do. However, Zhao Hai made up his mind and decided to cope with the events as they happen.

Chapter 739: Projection?

Before long, the Divine Race’s magic cannons arrived at the forefront of the battlefield. At this time, the formation had changed. The light cavalry divided itself into two wings and went to both sides of the formation while the infantry took up the position of the center. It was a well-performed change to a winged formation.

Zhao Hai calmly looked at the other party’s arrangements. He had already prepared his cube formation and was waiting for the enemy to come. But seeing that they didn’t charge immediately, it seems like the other party wanted to exchange a few words.

And Zhao Hai’s guess was right. The Divine Race’s formation stopped in its tracks as a person wearing a mage’s robe flew forward. Zhao Hai felt that this person was strange, however, he really didn’t know why he felt this.

He was wearing a snow white robe while he held a nearly transparent magic staff. In the staff’s head was actually a winged statue of a young girl. The statue emanated an angel’s holiness. And under his feet were clouds, giving him a look of a holy saint.

Wait! Clouds? Are those clouds under his feet? Zao Hai thought about it and gawked. It was now that Zhao Hai understood the strangeness of this person. It was actually because of the clouds on his feet.

One must know that their current altitude wasn’t high enough for clouds to appear. However, this person was actually stepping on a bunch of them, this was what made Zhao Hai feel strange.

But Zhao Hai was also quick to discover that the clouds on this person’s feet weren’t just decorations, they should be weapon themselves.

Although Zhao Hai can also make clouds appear as long as he uses water magic, it would still be water vapor in the end. Being attractive and mystical wasn’t something that a simple water spell could do.

The cloud that this person was stepping on was different. The clouds themselves look like they were their own entity. The clouds were soft, and whenever the person steps on them, they would even sink a bit.

Zhao Hai’s eyes unconsciously narrowed. It seems like this Divine Race person wasn’t so simple. Just his clouds were enough to surprise Zhao Hai, there was no need to say about the staff on his hand.

The Divine Race person was also sizing Zhao Hai up. He had an ordinary face, a black mage’s robe, a blood red magic staff, and was standing on top of a bone dragon. It wouldn’t take too long for one to see that he was a Dark Mage.

The Divine looked at Zhao Hai and then bowed, “Mister Zhao Hai? Thine is the Divine Race’s High War General, Cloud Ying. I have finally seen ye.”[1]

Zhao Hai didn’t think that this person would be polite. He stared for a moment before he quickly gave his reply, “This is indeed Zhao Hai. I have seen War General Cloud Ying.”

Cloud Ying looked at Zhao Hai and laughed. He didn’t look like an enemy at all. He seemed more like a good friend, a very good friend.

When Zhao Hai saw Cloud Ying’s action, his heart couldn’t help but feel more vigilant. He knew that people like Silver Shuke weren’t the true dangerous characters. Those who looked like Cloud Ying were the real monsters.  This person was basically a smiling tiger, one who calls you brother while he stabs you in the chest.

Zhao Hai didn’t make any noise as he continued to look at Cloud Ying. This made Cloud Ying surprised, he didn’t think that Zhao Hai would be in such a good condition, he wasn’t angry at all. It was at this moment that Cloud Ying also placed Zhao Hai in his list of dangerous people. Cloud Ying knew that the situation cannot stay this stiff, so he said, “Doth hath heard of mister’s name for a long time. Mister’s name is as commons as the clouds whenever the Ark Continent gets discussed. This Cloud Ying had always admired mister, it is a great fortune for me and my party to be able to meet you today.”[2]

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but feel sour at this point. Although he liked to read ancient literature, opportunities to speak like them was too few. Cloud Ying’s way of talking wasn’t something that Zhao Hai was used to.

However, Zhao Hai still replied, “Mister is overpraising me. I am no more than an ordinary citizen of the Ark Continent. It should be me who needs to feel honored. The Divine Realm is very large and populous, for mister to have his current standing is something that is extremely laudable. This Zhao Hai is very honored to have met you.”

While Zhao Hai’s expression was calm, he was actually feeling quite sour inside. However, since the other side wanted to talk nonsense, then it was only good manners to reply with nonsense as well.

Zhao Hai’s reply made Cloud Ying stare he didn’t think that Zhao Hai would have this kind of response. He also felt disgusted, but he couldn’t say anything. Cloud Ying was starting to feel that Zhao Hai was very hard to deal with.

However, Cloud Ying still replied to Zhao Hai, “It seems like mister also has some understanding with regards to the Divine Realm. Mister should know that the dream of the people in the Ark Continent’s people was to enter the Divine Realm and become a member of the Divine Race. This time, our Divine Race went against the laws and broke the space to enter the Ark Continent. So why would mister meet us with hostile intentions?”

Zhao Hai looked at Cloud Ying and then smiled faintly, “You’re right, the people in the Ark Continent really wanted to ascend to the Divine Realm and become a member of the Divine Race. However, why haven’t there been any ascensions in the past tens of thousands of years? Shouldn’t Mister Cloud Ying be aware of this reason? Since the Divine Realm doesn’t want us, then the Ark Continent naturally wouldn’t reach out for friendship. We decided to live our lives peacefully but we didn’t think that you would actually want to disrupt our lives. Now, tell me, why shouldn’t I meet you with hostility?”

Cloud Ying didn’t expect Zhao Hai to suddenly be impolite, his words suddenly turning sharp. Cloud Ying’s expression couldn’t help but sink as he said, “So mister is saying that my Divine Race had disrupted the life of the Ark Continent? The continent is a plane under the jurisdiction of the Divine Race, it belongs to us. This means that the residents of this plan is of a lower life form compared to the Divine Race. For us to open the space to the Ark Continent is akin to giving you face. But mister is actually ungrateful, isn’t this quite ironic?”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but laugh out loud, “You Divine Race really are what I heard you to be. You actually think that your invasion of the Ark Continent is a sacred task. Hahaha. This Zhao Hai has seen shameless people in his life, but I haven’t seen people who are as shameless as you. You broke the Space? Then let me ask you, what did it take for you to break the space? You actually used the flesh and blood of my people, millions of them. It is a shameless crime to claim their sacrifice as your own merit. Let this Zhao Hai give you an advice. You want to rule the Ark Continent? Then make sure that you manage to kill every single one of us. Otherwise, I will lead the people of the Ark Continent towards the Divine Realm and slaughter the Divine Race!”

At the end of his speech, Zhao Hai’s killing aura had reached the heavens. Cloud Ying couldn’t help but change his expression as he saw Zhao Hai. Then his voice turned cold as he said, “Since mister doesn’t want to hand the Ark Continent over. Then we shall identify it as a rebellion. Mister fighting with us will only bring ruin to the Ark Continent. However, we don’t know if the other people in the continent shares this idea.”

Zhao Hai looked at Cloud Ying and smiled faintly, “Mister doesn’t need to worry about this matter. To be honest, I am very worried for mister. The Demons had also arrived in the Ark Continent. Have you taken them into account? If the Divine Race suffers heavy casualties in the Ark Continent, then are you still able to keep your territory in the Divine Realm?”

When Cloud Ying heard Zhao Hai, his complexion couldn’t help but change. Zhao Hai’s understanding of the Divine Realm was extremely good. This made him quite confused. The Radiant Church has rewritten the history of the Ark Continent. At this point, the Ark Continent shouldn’t have any records pertaining to the matters of the Divine Realm. Where did Zhao Hai acquire such information?

Seeing Cloud Ying’s change in complexion, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile, “Talking here would be a waste of breath. What are you waiting for? I’ve been waiting here for a long time, I wanted to see how strong the people that the Divine Race had sent this time.”

Cloud Ying gawked, when he saw Zhao Hai’s smiling face, he couldn’t help but coldly snort and said, “Do you really think that we couldn’t deal with you? You think that your undead are able to stop the Divine Race? You are completely dreaming. Today, I shall let you witness the might of the Divine Race. I shall let you know that whoever blocks our path would die!”

The Cloud Ying waved his hand as the staffs of the Mages behind him shone. Then the Mages waved their staff and released a white light which combined with each other. It formed a huge light ball before it blasted out and made a rift in the sky. And then from that rift, a shadow of a person suddenly came out.

When Zhao Hai saw this person, he couldn’t help but stare. The person was wearing an ash gray close fitting gown. The hair on his head was very long but was tied by a silver headpiece. The person wore soft bottom leather shoes and was carrying a folding fan on his hand.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but be shocked with this image. This figure shouldn’t appear in the Ark Continent, it shouldn’t even appear in the Divine Realm. This was because the figure looked exactly like an ancient Chinese rich Young Master. This person had a faint yellow skin, black hair, black pupils and looked Chinese. What was going on?

However, Zhao Hai was quick to know that this person was only a phantom. Although Zhao Hai couldn’t feel that the person wasn’t there, he was certain that the figure wasn’t a real person, but a projection instead.

* * *

It can be translated as Cloud Shadow(Yun Ying) But I liked how the Divine Race were named before(Tiger Huan, Silver Shuke) so I decided to only translate the first character when it came to this one.

Pardon my archaic english attempts, xD just assume the Cloud Ying talks like an ancient man in this context.

Chapter 740: Immortal Cultivator?

Although Zhao Hai was certain that it was just a projection, he still didn’t dare to underestimate it. This was because the figure was giving him a strong pressure, a pressure that Zhao Hai had felt for the first time. Zhao Hai was certain that this person was extremely strong.

As soon as the projection appeared, he turned around to look at the scene. Then he showed a look of disappointment on his face as he turned to Cloud Ying, “Why did you invite me over?” Zhao Hai noticed that this person was being impolite to Cloud Ying. He even addressed him by ‘you’. At the same time, he also said ‘invited’, not called or found. It seems like this person’s status was much higher than Cloud Ying.

Sure enough, Cloud Ying became subservient to this person as he replied, “I have seen the Deity. I came here to perform the Deity’s work. But this person is obstructing us. I’m afraid we have to ask the Deity for help.”

Then the person looked over to Zhao Hai and said, “It’s just a puny Foundation Establishment brat. Why are you having troubles in dealing with him.”

It seems like Cloud Ying was afraid of this person. He immediately lowered his head and said, “Replying to the Deity. Although the strength of this person is ordinary, he had all sorts of tricks that are very hard to deal with. Me and the others simply don’t have the means to deal with him in such a short time. Therefore, we decided to ask the Deity for help.” The person looked at Zhao Hai and said, “You and the others are handling matters for me, so it is natural that I would help. As long as you remember your jobs, then I shall deal with this person.” Then he addressed Zhao Hai, “Boy, it looks like you had a few achievements despite being young. Its a pity that you shall fall to my hands.”

Zhao Hai looked straight into this person and said, “Are you the one who taught the Divine Race how to change the laws?” The person didn’t think that Zhao Hai would ask this question, he became more curious towards Zhao Hai as he laughed, “You certainly aren’t ordinary. Hahaha. Right, it was I who taught them. Otherwise, they would waste materials on pointless methods. Boy, if it was any other occasion, then I might accept you to be my servant. But unfortunately, you will die today.”

Zhao Hai coldly replied, “I am not interested in being another person’s dog. If you want to kill me, then do it. Since you came to this plane, I’m fairly certain that you will have restrictions on yourself. You might even be reduced to a few steps down from your current strength. Moreover, I wonder how long you will be able to stay here.”

When this person heard Zhao Hai, he couldn’t help but gawk, he looked straight at Zhao Hai and said, “Boy, you’re quite smart. Correct, I cannot stay too long in this place and I cannot use my complete strength. However, dealing with you should be easy enough.”

Zhao Hai actually laughed and said, “You’re just a projection. Even if you are strong, you are still bound to a few steps down from your actual strength. Even if you are a Nascent Soul expert, you still aren’t enough to kill me!”

When this person heard Zhao Hai’ words, his expression couldn’t help but change. He looked coldly at Zhao hai and said, “Who told you that? Nobody in this place should be able to know what a Nascent Soul expert is. Who are you?”

Zhao Hai calmed himself, he coldly looked at the person and said, “And why should I tell you?” Zhao Hai said the word ‘Nascent Soul’ as a probe. This was because he had heard ‘Foundation Establishment’ from before!

These words aren’t strange when it came to the novels back on Earth. As long as one looks at a xianxia novel, then there will be a high chance that these stages of cultivation would appear. Because of this, Zhao Hai tried to use the word ‘Nascent Soul’ that he usually read about. If this person hadn’t heard of this, then he would have no response just like Cloud Ying and the others. It was clear that the Divine Race were completely clueless what these words were, which explains their lack of response.

‘Nascent Soul’ usually came after Foundation Establishment in xianxia novels. Therefore, Zhao Hai took this word out to test the person. He actually didn’t expect that he would take the bait this easily. This made Zhao Hai’s heart sink. He knew that Foundation Establishment was no more than an entry level stage in cultivation. In other words, he had just touched the boundary and had just become an Immortal Cultivator.

Although he didn’t know which realm this person was from, but it was evident that Foundation Establishment was the lowest stage in his realm. In this case, then there were even more mysterious people behind the Divine Race. It seems like the enemies that they will face had become much stronger.

The man was evidently irritated by Zhao Hai, the look on his eyes was proof enough. The man said, “Good, good. Nobody has dared talk to this Deity this way in many years. Boy, prepare to have your soul sucked out of your body and refined. You will neither be alive nor dead.”

Zhao Hai simply replied, “Try it if you can.”

The person didn’t waste any breath, he immediately shouted, “Mountain River Fan!” The waved his hand as his fan flew out. The fan became bigger and then a big river suddenly flowed out of it and went straight to Zhao Hai. When Zhao Hai saw this situation, he immediately made a retreat as he placed all of his undead, as well as Berry and Shue into the Space. Zhao Hai had no idea about how strong this man was. The only thing he knew was that this man had called him foundation establishment. And it seems that this person was much stronger than Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai’s figure moved as he established his Domain. Then his Domain changed into a cube that had a whirlpool in the middle, directly welcoming the incoming river.

The river that the man released was very heavy, and its impact was quite strong. In a blink of an eye, the river clashed with Zhao Hai’s Domain. The Domain was constantly shaking, and Zhao Hai’s face started to get pale. The impact was really heavy.

The attack wasn’t a joke, the river was nothing like the spells in the Ark Continent. The river itself was a weapon that held concealed energy. Although it stopped after hitting Zhao Hai’s Domain, the river stayed mobile and attacked the Domain by waves. The first wave of impact brought enough energy that it deformed the Domain.

This was the first time that Zhao Hai had encountered an attack like this. Due to its strength, he couldn’t help but cough up blood. Zhao Hai knew that the person had used a magic weapon, otherwise, the attack wouldn’t have been very strong.

At this time, Zhao Hai suddenly felt that everything around him had turned dim. Then a huge mountain suddenly appeared overhead. Zhao Hai became startled. If he were to block this mountain, then he would become fully exhausted. Resisting the mountain was impossible.

With an intention, Zhao Hai moved his Domain and transformed it into a rotating sphere, negating the strong attacks of the river. However, the mountain still pressed on. Zhao Hai shouted as his Domain changed into a big hand. The hand grasped the mountain, slowing its descent down.

When the person saw Zhao Hai’s performance, he couldn’t help but be surprised. “I didn’t think that a puny foundation establishment brat such a you would actually be able to block my mountain river fan. Although the mountain river fan is just a projection, it could still exhibit a sixth of its strength. For you to block it is surely surprising. I thought that all of the cultivation methods of this plain are pure rubbish, it seems like I have to rethink my thoughts.” Zhao Hai didn’t have the leverage to answer right now. He made a small grunt as a blue water ball appeared in his hand. Then he threw this water ball towards the attacking river.

Although it looked like this, the water ball was actually Bubble. Bubble was said to be the source of myriad water, so Zhao Hai wanted to see if he could deal with this river with the use of Bubble. Therefore, he had Cai’er ask Bubble.

Bubble actually said yes. When Zhao Hai threw him, Bubble immediately changed his appearance into a small child made of water. Then he rotated in place as he pulled the river in. Before long, Bubble disappeared within a large spinning lake.

Then Bubble shrank his body as he returned to Zhao Hai’s Domain. Zhao Hai immediately made his move and took Bubble back to the Space. Zhao Hai felt that after Bubble absorbed the river, he had actually become unstable. Bubble would need some time before he would be able to digest it.

Although the process seemed slow, it actually happened quite fast. Zhao Hai taking Bubble out, absorbing the water, and then returning to the Space only took a blink of an eye.

When the man found out that something was wrong, Bubble had already sucked the river into his body and had returned to the Space. The man couldn’t help but get enraged. Although he only came with his projection, he would still need to expend some energy in order to maintain it, making this projection a type of avatar that once forcibly broken, then it would damage the main body. At the same time, his magical treasure also had their own treasure spirit. Their projection also held a piece of the spirit’s self. When this projection gets broken, then it would definitely cause some damage to the treasure, it might even fall a level.

One must know that for an immortal cultivator, magical treasures were very important. Each cultivator would do everything in their hands in order to upgrade their own treasures. A treasure being downgraded was the same as damaging the vitality of a cultivator, it would definitely have a direct effect in their fighting strength.

When the person saw that Zhao Hai took the river’s projection away, he couldn’t help but get startled as he shouted, “Brat, you dare!” One must know that the river was not made out of any ordinary river. It was actually made out of Profound Moon River, a water that was rich in yin force. It had an effect of strengthening Ghosts and held a corrosive effect towards other treasures. The man took great effort in order to refine this water for his own treasure. Who would’ve thought that its projection would actually be absorbed by Zhao Hai. The effect of this action towards the Mountain River Fan wasn’t small. So how could he not be startled, how could he not be angry?

Chapter 741: Pressed to Defend

When Zhao Hai heard the person shout, he turned to look at his and sneered, “If you want to kill me, then you naturally need to pay a price.” Since Bubble had absorbed the river, the pressure on Zhao Hai had lessened. The only thing that he needed to deal with right now was the huge mountain.

Zhao Hai discovered that the Mountain River Fan’s mountain was inferior in attacking strength compared to the river. Although the mountain looked very formidable and had the ability to give strong pressure, that was its only attack. On the other hand, due to the dark energy inside the river, its attacks got more powerful as the waves continued to clash towards Zhao Hai’s domain.

And Zhao Hai didn’t guess wrong. The mountain and river were both part of the Mountain River Fan. However, the river was the more powerful one of the two. The water from the river was refined in the River of Nothingness. The water in that river was a treasure in their world, its power was enormous, which aided the attacking power of the river. On the other hand, the mountain was just an ordinary mountain. It was just used in order to fulfil the requirements in making the mountain river fan. Because of this, it was impossible for the mountain to be on par with the river.

The person’s face was pale as he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Good, good. It seems like I had underestimated you. Still, you will have to die today.” Then he waved his hand as a sword came out of his ring.

The sword was three feet long and three inches wide. It was blood red and had quite a long hilt. The sword floated in the sky before the person pointed his finger to Zhao Hai and said, “Go!”

Then the scarlet sword flew straight straight towards its target. Just from its appearance, Zhao Hai knew that this sword wasn’t simple. However, he wasn’t afraid of it. He waved his hand as he sent his blood ghost staff to meet the sword.

The person couldn’t help but show a smile on his face. In his mind, Zhao Hai was simply courting death. How could something made in the Ark Continent contend with the treasures that he has. In his opinion, although Zhao Hai’s staff was beautiful, it still wouldn’t be able to defend against the flying sword.

However, the immortal cultivator was soon to discover his mistake. When the magic staff and the sword was about to clash, the magic staff suddenly extended a hand and went on to capture the sword, stopping it in its tracks.

The person couldn’t help but be surprised. This was also because he felt that his control had was slowly diminishing. He immediately used is control method as he shouted once more, “Go!”

The sword fiercely vibrated, seemingly wanting to escape from the magic staff’s grasp. But at this moment, another hand appeared in the magic staff, grabbing it once again. With two hands suppressing it, the sword found it impossible to break free.

This shook the man internally, he didn’t think that his scarlet sword would actually be stopped by Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai already broken two of his treasures. At this point, the person didn’t dare identify Zhao Hai as an ordinary foundation establishment cultivator anymore.

The man’s expression was heavy, then he muttered a few words while his hand made some movements. The mountain that was pressing Zhao Hai was collected back into the mountain river fan. Then the person waved his hand, placing his fan into his ring while also withdrawing a black flag.

The black flag was quite large, and on its surface were drawings of horrific ghosts. The flag emanated a very gloomy aura.

The person waved the flag as numerous Evil Ghosts departed from it. At the same time, the sunny sky was suddenly drowned out by dark clouds. As Zhao Hai looked at the black sky, the evil ghosts started to scream and rush towards him.

Zhao Hai quietly looked at these evil ghosts. He was thinking about methods to deal with these ghosts, but he didn’t expect them to rush in an instant. It didn’t take too long before ghosts started biting Zhao Hai’s domain. Then Zhao Hai suddenly felt that his mind was going unstable. This gave Zhao Hai a surprised, he immediately released some undead to see whether they were able to deal with these ghosts.

The undead appeared outside the Domain and immediately threw themselves towards the evil ghosts. These ghosts were not physical beings, so they shouldn’t be afraid of the undead. However, the undead suddenly opened their mouths and sucked in. The ghosts started to scream as they got swallowed by the undead. The undead seemed to benefit from this ordeal as the fire in their eyes started to get brighter. Then they went on to swallow another ghost.

When the man saw that the undead were eating the ghosts of this ten thousand ghost flag, he immediately became anxious. He knew that the ten thousand ghost flag wasn’t easy to refine since it used the souls of countless people. In long term battles, these evil ghosts would worsen wounds and even corrode magic weapons. They were very powerful. But the man didn’t expect that Zhao Hai’s undead would actually be able to eat them up.

The evil ghosts were beings of yin, the undead were also beings of yin. However, the undead were much stronger compared to the ghosts. The yin qi present in the ghosts simply couldn’t contend to those inside the undead. In the end, the ghosts can only become food for the undead.

Seeing that his ten thousand ghost flag was being eaten up, the man couldn’t help but flare out in anger. He immediately took his flag away as his two eyes gave a blazing gaze towards Zhao hai, “Good, good. I have greatly underestimated you, boy. I didn’t think that you would have real skill. It seems like a needed to use this.” Then he waved his hand, making a tiny pagoda appear. This tiny pagoda was black all over. Ghost images were ever present in its 9 storeys. Each level of the pagoda had eight sharp horns in it. In each horn were wind chimes, which were made out of skulls.

The person gently shook the pagoda, making the wind chimes give out a light sound. This sound was not clear, but one could still hear something akin to a wailing ghost. It had a direct impact on the mind of a person.

Zhao Hai was still inside his Domain, so he didn’t think that he would still be affected by this spiritual attack. He was pressed to defend as the attack slowly crawled into his mind. Zhao Hai couldn’t bear the pain on his head, he held his head with his hands as he gave a loud grunt.

Since Zhao Hai was affected by a spiritual attack, then it was natural for his Domain to be broken due to lack of control. The man had a wicked expression as he waved his hand and let go of the pagoda. The pagoda grew into a tower that was more than a hundred meters high as it covered Zhao hai.

Zhao Hai was currently recovering from the spiritual attack, so it was impossible for him to deal with this move. Seeing that Zhao Hai had been swallowed up by the pagoda, the man couldn’t help but laugh and said, “Boy, you have now been absorbed into this Deity’s Soul Eating Pagoda. You should be proud, I will make you into the Pagoda’s main soul!”

When Zhao Hai was taken into the soul eating pagoda, the tower immediately underwent a change. It rotated fast as a huge mouth appeared on its bottom and bit towards Zhao Hai. Since Zhao Hai was still resisting the spiritual attack, he didn’t have the capacity to evade it. His mind was still blank, it was impossible for him to evade the mouth of the pagoda.

But at this critical moment, a spatial rift suddenly appeared, taking Zhao Hai out of the pagoda and into the Space.

Upon entering the Space, Zhao Hai immediately felt more energetic, easing some the pain that he felt. Zhao Hai stared for a moment, and then knew that this was Cai’er’s doing. At this time, Laura and the others ran over, they looked at Zhao Hai as Laura asked, “Brother Hai, are you alright? What just happened?”

Seeing the worry on their faces, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile faintly and said, “I’m fine. But its fortunate that Caier’ managed to pull me over. Otherwise, I would really be placed in a dangerous position. It seems like I had been negligent. Right, let me go and rest for a while.”

Laura and the others nodded, and then stopped themselves from disturbing Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai proceeded to sit cross-legged, he endured the pain on his head as he controlled his divine sense towards his body.

He looked at the monster core in his lower dantian first, it was still doing well, it wasn’t affected. Then he went towards the Dao Lotus, it was still good, nothing happened. Then Zhao Hai controlled his divine sense to probe his upper dantian. As soon as his divine sense entered the upper dantian, he immediately merged with the small figure. As soon as his divine sense came into contact with the small person, Zhao Hai immediately felt that his spirit had become better compared to before. His spirit seemed to become stronger as well.

Zhao Hai gawked, then he immediately understood. This must be because of the small man. Zhao Hai was in his present predicament because he had failed to make use of this small version of him. Otherwise, he wouldn’t have been affected by the spiritual attack.

Zhao Hai’s own divine power centered on this small man. Then the small man slowly opened his eyes. Zhao Hai immediately felt his body being washed over, he felt very good. Then his divine sense spread outward, covering the Space and mapping all of it inside his mind.

Zhao Hai stared, then he suddenly had the urge to see if he could make this small man move his body. He couldn’t help but think about moving its hand and feet.

Surprisingly, Zhao Hai discovered that his own body had actually stood up. It moved its hands and feet with just a mere thought. This feeling was very bizarre. Zhao Hai felt that he was controlling his own body while also being detached from it. He seemed like a puppet master, with his own body as the puppet.

Although the control was very fluid and Zhao Hai felt good about it. He still couldn’t help but feel strange with all that just happened.

At this time, Zhao Hai suddenly felt that the uncomfortable feeling had slowly disappeared. The feeling of controlling a puppet also slowly vanished, he was now starting to feel like he was moving his own body. Zhao Hai became glad at this development. Then Zhao Hai started to feel the small man in his dantian, it was still there, it seems like nothing has changed. Then when Zhao Hai withdrew his divine sense, he discovered that he had recovered to full!

Chapter 742: Surrender

After a few more experimentations, Zhao Hai came to understand that the small man was where his spiritual force lied. Although this was brought through when he was promoted, he didn’t actively make use of this small man, which was also his spiritual strength. Only when his body and spirit fully combined did his spiritual force gained sufficient strength.

Zhao Hai relaxed, and then he opened his eye. The painful sensation that he had felt before had completely vanished. Moreover, he can also feel unprecedented strength in his own spiritual force. It was time to deal with that immortal cultivator.

When Laura and the others saw that Zhao Hai had opened his eyes, they immediately went towards him. With a caring tone, Laura asked, “Brother Hai, how was it?”

Zhao Hai gave a faint smile and said, “I’m alright. I just became careless and allowed myself to be affected by the enemy’s spiritual attack. But now I’m feeling good, I should be able to deal with him. However, its very strange, the magic treasure that he used this time didn’t have the strength of a projection. This tiny pagoda actually had form, it was too bizarre.”

Laura and the others didn’t quite understand what Zhao Hai was saying. However, they can tell that the immortal cultivator was anything but simple just by looking at his powerful attacks. Additionally, although he was a person summoned by the Divine Race, the Divine Race were the ones who were subservient towards him. This was enough to explain how strong he was.

Because of this, Laura and the others were very worried as they watched Zhao Hai’s battle. Laura said, “Brother Hai, you should just stay inside the Space. Just as you said, that person wouldn’t be able to stay here for too long. Just wait for him to disappear, then we’ll go and deal with the Divine Race.”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “That won’t be ideal. I must deal with this person. I have settled on his tiny pagoda. I have an inkling that the pagoda would be helpful in upgrading the undead. Rest assured, I will be fine. I’m quite confident.” Then Zhao Hai’s figure disappeared and then appeared inside the pagoda once more.

The man was startled when he found out that Zhao Hai vanished from the pagoda. This tiny pagoda was a treasure that he still hasn’t refined. However, its attack was very strong, it can be seen in how Zhao Hai was affected in its spiritual attack.

As long as one gets covered by the pagoda, the pagoda will slowly refine the victim’s flesh and blood until it extracts a person’s soul and use it to power itself. The more souls gathered, the more powerful the pagoda would become. But the thing that the pagoda lacks the most right now was a main soul.

This tiny pagoda needed a soul in order to run by itself. As long as a main soul was provided, the pagoda’s power would be further improved. A main soul would also make it more convenient to use the pagoda in the future.

The man still hadn’t found an appropriate soul to act as the pagoda’s main spirit. But this time, he had settled on Zhao Hai. Although Zhao Hai wasn’t strong, the strength of his soul was quite formidable. It would be fitting to have him as the pagoda’s main soul.

However, just as Zhao Hai was about to be refined, he suddenly disappeared. The person moved his hand, making the pagoda return. Then with his divine sense, he scanned the insides of the tiny pagoda. When he confirmed that Zhao Hai did indeed vanish, his mind couldn’t help but feel muddled.

One must know that this pagoda was one of the man’s most important treasures. He came to the Ark Continent relying on the might of this treasure. Although the soul eating pagoda can swallow souls, it can also protect the soul of its user. His soul possessed the tiny pagoda and then came to the Ark Continent. The other treasures that he used were all projections, only this tiny pagoda was the real one among them.

Just as the man was puzzled, Zhao Hai suddenly appeared back inside the pagoda. The man stared for a moment before he immediately controlled the pagoda to refine Zhao Hai.

However, he didn’t think that just as Zhao Hai appeared inside the pagoda, he immediately used his crystallization ability in order to deal with physical attacks. Then, his mind delved deep inside his upper dantian and immediately used the small man to launch a spiritual attack!

When Zhao Hai’s divine sense sunk into the small man, the small man immediately opened his eyes. His silvery hair fluttered around as it extended outwards.

The silvery hair became the same property as Berry’s hair. It had turned into numerous filaments as it attached to various parts of the pagoda, then it proceeded its attack.

When the man who controlled the pagoda started to feel that his control was slipping, he couldn’t help but gape in surprise. Then his expression changed, as he made seals using his hands and started to fight for control over the tiny pagoda.

He was very clear, his divine sense was attached to the tiny pagoda, if the tiny pagoda were to be broken through, then his divine sense would vanish, which in turn would cause his projection to disappear.

To be honest, his projection disappearing was nothing to him. He was more concerned about not losing the soul eating pagoda. Once he loses this treasure, then his losses would definitely be huge.

Although he was using his seals, the tiny pagoda was still not in his full control. This made the man anxious, his entire figure disappeared as he entered the pagoda himself.

Zhao Hai was currently attacking the tiny pagoda. He felt that the pagoda was being controlled by a very powerful spiritual force. And now, he was contending for the pagoda’s control with the other party.

Zhao Hai had studied Berry’s attack methods. One must say that the Succubus clan’s achievements when it came to spiritual attacks were extremely great. Spiritual attacks had been honed to almost perfection by them. Because of this, Zhao Hai felt that even if the enemy was strong, it was still possible to take control of this pagoda.

At this time, Zhao Hai felt a formidable spiritual force pouring into the pagoda. The spiritual force was very familiar, it was just like the man in the projection.

Zhao Hai was already on guard against him. So when the man entered the pagoda, Zhao Hai immediately took notice. But Zhao Hai didn’t become anxious, he just continued to use his own spiritual force to fight that person for control.

Zhao Hai discovered that his own spiritual force wasn’t any worse than the other party. But since this was the first time that he used his spiritual force, he wasn’t able to use it in its peak form. For now, Zhao Hai can only fight a back and forth battle with this person.

As Zhao Hai became more comfortable in using his spiritual force, he slowly began to take the upper hand in the battle. Although the person was still resisting, Zhao Hai knew that it was only a matter of time before victory comes into his grasp. At this point, Zhao Hai was being very careful with this man. He was afraid that he would do the same thing as the Demons, self destruct.

And Zhao Hai wasn’t wrong. When the man discovered that he wouldn’t be able to resist Zhao Hai, he became even more worried since he had already used all of his methods in order to secure victory. Because of this, the man couldn’t help but think of his last ditch method and prepared to detonate his divine sense. He wanted to heavily injure Zhao Hai as well as leave a mark on his body. As long as Zhao Hai ascends to the higher realm, the man would immediately be able to sense him. When that time comes, he would go and deal with Zhao Hai.

He was currently a projection, and the strength that his divine sense could display was only a tenth of his true power. This was the reason why he can’t gain victory in his battle with Zhao Hai. If he can exhibit 100 percent of his strength, then Zhao Hai’s only choice would be to hide inside the Space. It would be impossible for Zhao Hai to go head to head with the man.

When the man was about to launch his attack, Zhao Hai suddenly went all out. He poured a huge amount of spiritual force into the pagoda and before the man could respond, Zhao Hai immediately opened a rift and took the pagoda into the Space.

Zhao Hai already wanted to take the pagoda to the Space long time ago. However, it was impossible to snatch the pagoda without having a great lead in controlling it. When his control reached an ample level, only then would Zhao Hai be able to take the pagoda over to the Space.

When he entered the Space, Zhao Hai immediately came out of the pagoda. It didn’t take too long before the Space issued a prompt. “Hostile program detected by the Space. Fixing the program, program fixed.”

“Discovered massive amounts of dark element energy inside the weapon. Weapon can be upgraded by the host using the Processing Machine. The upgrade would require ten thousand year ice, three days, and 100 thousand gold coins. Host can also add a program to your new weapon. Tip: It is best to fuse this program to the recently fixed program that is already installed in the weapon. This will make sure that the upgrade would go well.”

Zhao Hai gawked, then a wave of happiness suddenly washed over him. He didn’t expect the pagoda to be upgraded. Moreover, the tiny pagoda did indeed have some uses for him. And most importantly, the Space had subdued the man’s divine sense. In the future, Zhao Hai can ask this divine sense about where he came from, among other information.

Zhao Hai immediately brought the tiny pagoda over to the Processing Machine. Then he turned his head to Bubble and said, “Bubble, take out some ten thousand-year old ice.”

Bubble quickly complied, his body spun as he released massive amounts of ten thousand-year ice. Then Zhao Hai pressed the start button on the Processing Machine in order to begin the tiny pagoda’s upgrade.

A white light beamed out of the processing machine as it covered the tiny pagoda as well as the ten thousand year old ice. Bubble released ten cubic meters of ice this time, which was more than enough for the Processing Machine to use. After absorbing five cubic meters, the tiny pagoda vanished.

Zhao Hai turned to look as the timer of the Processing Machine started to beat. Then he relaxed as he exited the Space. He was still in a war against the Divine Race, it wouldn’t be great if he were to disappear for too long.

When Zhao Hai vanished along with the man, Cloud Ying couldn’t help but be shocked. He didn’t’ think that Zhao Hai would be this hard to deal with. With Zhao Hai and the Deity vanishing, Cloud Ying didn’t know whether Zhao Hai had been dealt with or whether the Deity failed.

Cloud Ying was confident with the Deity, however, after seeing Zhao Hai’s performance, his confidence couldn’t help but suffer a blow. He had been made aware of how scary Zhao Hai would be. He was hoping that the Deity had eliminated Zhao Hai. Otherwise, Zhao Hai would become a huge threat to the Divine Race’s advance.

Chapter 743: Magic Beast Upgrade

When Cloud Ying saw Zhao Hai disappear together with the Deity, he immediately launched an attack. He commanded the light cavalry to go and overrun the city. No change happened in the city since Zhao Hai’s disappearance and Lizzy and Megan were still inside. They knew that Zhao Hai was fine because of Cai’er, so they were relieved in fighting against the Divine Race.

As the horned pegasus cavalry slowly approached the city walls, Lizzy gave an order to begin firing the magic cannons. These horned pegasus cavalry knew about how formidable these magic cannons were from Silver Shuke. Therefore, they immediately made some evasive maneuvers.

However, the crystals that Zhao Hai used this time were of the fire element. Even if the opposing party avoided it, the explosion would still affect them. This explosion was quite lethal towards the light cavalry.

As the city wall continued their salvo, a distant explosion was suddenly heard. Lizzy and Megan turned to the direction of the sound and discovered that it was where the Elven aerial cavalry was. It seems like the Elves had used their blood lightning beads.

Cloud Ying and the others also heard the explosion. He had information from Silver Shuke that Zhao Hai was able to use blood lightning beads non-stop. It was clear that the explosion came from the beads. Cloud Ying’s expression couldn’t help but sink, it was possible that the routed light cavalry unit had met an unfortunate fate.

Although he was aware that Zhao Hai was able to use an unlimited amount of blood lightning beads, he didn’t care much of it. He knew that even if these beads were strong, it also had a restriction, only its master was able use it, no other. Because of this, he became assured and didn’t bother to think that the Elves might have blood lightning beads. But now it seems like his thoughts were wrong. Zhao hai can actually hand the blood lightning beads over to other people. This was beyond his imagination, the horned pegasus cavalry has been placed in a dangerous position.

At this time, Zhao Hai suddenly appeared in the sky above the city. Upon seeing Zhao Hai,  Cloud Ying’s pupils couldn’t help but shrink. Zhao Hai was present while the Deity was not, what did this mean? Has the Deity been eliminated by Zhao Hai? Was this possible?

Zhao Hai looked at Cloud Ying, but he didn’t bother to spare a word. He immediately released a large amount of undead to join the fight. Among these undead were God-ranks, while others had magic cannons in their bodies. Once these undead join, the horned pegasus cavalry would surely suffer.

At this moment, Cloud Ying waved his hand towards the people behind him. After that, the Divine Race who wore mage robes immediately muttered their incantations. Before long, these mages help their staffs up as it flashed a white light. When the light vanished, large quantities of magic beasts appeared.

These magic beasts were all white, and each of their figures looked fierce. Most importantly, these magic beasts were floating the air, signifying that they are 9th ranks and some were even possibly God-rank. Moreover, their numbers weren’t small. Each God-rank expert had summoned at least 10 thousand beasts. There were even some of them that managed to summon more than a million.

When the magic beasts came out, they immediately threw themselves towards the city, planning to overrun the Beastmen cavalry in the process.

Zhao Hai saw that the enemy Mages were indeed summoners. After the magic beasts appeared, he immediately waved his hand, releasing undead in order to meet the magic beasts. Some of them went down to support the Beastmen, while some went to the skies and fought.

The battle had officially started. The light cavalry was now putting their spears away and went on to grab their bows and arrows before sending a wave of arrows towards the city’s magic formation. The arrows were very powerful, although the protective shield managed to block them, ripples were constantly produced all over its surface, it was possible for the formation to shatter at any time.

Zhao Hai didn’t worry about it anymore after releasing the undead. He went on to establish his Domain as he threw himself towards Cloud Ying’s group. Zhao Hai wanted to go and smash the heart of the enemy camp.

It didn’t take too long before Cloud Ying managed to spot Zhao Hai’s approach. To be honest, Cloud Ying was somewhat afraid of Zhao Hai. This was because Zhao Hai managed to defeat their invincible Deity. For Cloud Ying and his people, the significance of this action was very big.

Because of this, Cloud Ying didn’t dare face Zhao Hai head on. He immediately directed the Divine Race infantry to form a wall in front of the Mages, not giving Zhao Hai a chance to approach.

Cloud Ying was also aware of Zhao Hai’s space divergent ability. In order to make sure that Zhao Hai wouldn’t use his ability to deal with him, Cloud Ying also arranged a few infantry units to surround himself.

Zhao Hai really wanted to deal with Cloud Ying by using the Space. But after seeing Cloud Ying’s arrangements, he knew that it became very hard to accomplish it. Zhao Hai decided to stop pursuing Cloud Ying as he diverted his attention to the horned pegasus cavalry. At this time, Berry and Shue came out, and the three of them formed a triangle  as they directly killed through the mass of flying cavalry.

With Zhao Hai as the tip, Shue and Berry formed an arrow shape behind Zhao Hai. As Zhao Hai went on to his killing spree, Berry was not there, however, one could see people dying without reason from time to time. Naturally, all those kills counted towards Berry.

There was no need to say about Shue’s fighting strength. The three’s triangle formation acted like a sharp knife as it sliced through the light cavalry formation. Their advance was just like a hot knife through butter. It became quite easy for them to rip open a big rift in the middle of the light cavalry formation.

The light cavalry immediately split into groups of a thousand people each. They turned into a square formation as they avoided Zhao Hai’s charge. Then they proceeded to launch attacks towards Zhao Hai.

Naturally, these light cavalry units were very familiar with regards to this way of fighting. Their battle formations were made with good coordination. The light cavalry units that Zhao Hai managed to kill got fewer as the pressure mounting on Zhao Hai’s back got stronger and stronger.

After seeing the change in the light cavalry unit’s formation, Zhao Hai immediately waved his hand, releasing more undead into the field. These undead divided themselves into squads as they proceeded to kill the light cavalry units.

The speed of the horned pegasus was very fast. Although they were fairly huge, they still held flexibility no worse than the blood hawks. No wonder the Divine Race chose them to be their mounts, they were very good.

Most importantly, these horned pegasus also had their own magic, and it was a type of rare lightning spell. The magic wasn’t weak at all. Zhao Hai was very attracted to these mounts. So just as he killed the light cavalry units, he also absorbed a couple of horned pegasus in the Space, intending to raise them in the future.

The magic beasts in the battlefield didn’t only compose of horned pegasus, there were also the magic beasts summoned by the Divine Race. And similarly, Zhao Hai also captured some of them for the Space. The fighting strength of these magic beasts weren’t weak, so Zhao Hai was prepared to raise them. When Zhao Hai captured these magic beasts, the Space immediately issued a prompt, “Magic beasts in the Space has been upgraded. Most magic beasts in the Space have reached 8th rank. Common beasts such as argali and blue eyed rabbits are now 8th ranks, there are also other magic beasts that reached 9th rank.”

This was good news for Zhao Hai. When he heard this information, he immediately released some of the 9th rank magic beast of the Space. This time, he released the most common cattle in the Space. Blue eyed rabbits, argali, and raging bulls were the prominent beasts in the Space. Since the argali and blue eyed rabbits were still eight ranks, they couldn’t be used just yet. On the other hand, the raging bulls had become 9th ranks, so Zhao Hai decided to release them and had them go against the heavy rhinoceros cavalry on the ground.

At this moment, the heavy cavalry were slowly advancing towards the city. Although the Dwarves and the Beastmen were making attacks against them, the heavy cavalry’s defensive capabilities were just too good. Moreover, their mounts were also capable of earth magic. With how strong the cavalry unit was as well as their mounts, there was little that the Dwarves and Beastmen could do in order to stop them.

The impact of the heavy cavalry was very strong. So although they couldn’t fly up the wall, once they go under it and batter the defensive shield of the city, the protective shield would soon run out of energy to rely on. And once the protective formation gets broken, the casualties would then start to pile up. To combat this, Zhao Hai decided to release the raging bulls out into the field.

Although the raging bulls were now 9th rank, their strength still wasn’t that strong. After they reached 9th rank, they only became stronger in two points. First, their strength, and the other was their defense. Upon reaching 9th rank, the raging bulls had became bigger as their defensive capabilities soared up. But unfortunately, unlike the magic beasts in the continent, the raging bulls in the Space didn’t manage to develop their own consciousness. However, Zhao Hai understood why this was the case. Think about it, once a magic beasts gains sentience, they would be able to communicate like a human being. This would be a terrible thing and would make Zhao Hai opt out from eating the magic beasts in the Space.

The quantity of magic beasts that Zhao Hai released was quite big. About a hundred thousand raging bulls suddenly came out of the city’s backside as they went on and clashed with the heavy cavalry unit.

At this point, the horns of the raging bulls had become a meter long each. Their curved horns had become silver in color, each of them looked just like terrifying weapons. It was certain that their attacking strength wouldn’t be weak.

The raging bulls’ iron skins had also become cyan as their defenses got strengthened. Zhao Hai was currently thinking about killing a batch of raging bulls and then having the Dwarves make leather armor out of their skins. This would enhance the defense of the continent’s soldiers, reducing casualties in the process. However, Zhao Hai was not anxious about executing this plan. After all, the raging bulls had just reached 9th rank.

Chapter 744: Repelled

Zhao Hai was not too satisfied with the raging bulls On the other hand, wasn’t aware about how startled Cloud Ying was.

The Divine Race held a lot of power because of their profession called Summoner. These were the people who wore mage robe behind Cloud Ying. The main attack of these people were their summons. And all of their summons were magic beasts who lived in the Divine Realm.

The magic beasts in the Divine Realm and the Ark Continent were different. The weakest magic beasts in the Divine Realm would be 7th ranks. Beasts that had 8th or 9th rank strengths weren’t rare in the Divine Realm.

However, the Summoners in the Divine Realm aren’t any different from the Summoners in the Ark Continent. The magic beasts that they summon also needed to be captured. After capturing their beasts, only then could they store it inside their own summon space. Their spaces were quite big and can accept a lot of magic beasts. Moreover, the more magic beasts they gain, the more space their space would have.

The status of these Summoners was very high among the Divine Race. This wasn’t only because they were able to summon magic beasts, it was also because they were able to summon the Deity.

The Summoners that came along with Cloud Ying were expert Summoners of the Divine Race. Their beasts were mostly 9th or God rank, their fighting strength was extraordinary.

In Cloud Ying’s mind, once the Summoners take their beasts out, then the Ark Continent would have certainly lost. After all, the Ark Continent didn’t have any God-rank experts. Additionally, they only had 9th rank beasts, of which were very few in number. With such quality, how could the continent be able to contend with the Divine Race?

However, what Cloud Ying and the Divine Race didn’t expect was Zhao Hai’s existence. He single handedly broke their preconceptions about the Ark Continent. The undead that Zhao Hai summoned were even 9th rank. Moreover, the amount of undead that Zhao Hai could summon was enough to make a person’s head hurt.

And now, Zhao Hai released a large amount of 9th rank magic beasts. This action made Cloud Ying speechless. Zhao Hai’s methods were enough to shock people even if he was in the Divine Realm. Cloud Ying couldn’t understand how the Ark Continent could possibly give birth to a monster such as Zhao Hai.

It didn’t take too long before the raging bulls clashed with the heavy cavalry. It was at this moment that the Divine Race’s cavalry fully demonstrated their might. Although the raging bulls were 9th rank, they still weren’t able to resist the hammers of the heavy cavalry.

However, the raging bulls were still 9th rank, they still held great strength. At the same time, there were also a lot of heavy cavalry soldiers that had been knocked down from their mounts, and then proceeded to get mercilessly stamped.

Naturally, Zhao Hai wouldn’t let these losses be a waste. Every single raging bull and Divine Race cavalry that died were all absorbed into the Space. His undead were the continent’s main weapon against the Demons and the Divine Race, it would be good if their numbers were to be constantly supplemented.

This was because in the end, the undead in his hands weren’t truly undying. They could still be destroyed by a powerful attack. From the start of the battle until now, Zhao Hai didn’t stop to absorb every single dead enemy body in the battlefield.

After being faced with the raging bulls, the Divine Race heavy cavalry couldn’t help but stop their charge. At this time, the Beastmen had also met with the magic beasts that the Divine Race Summoners took out. Fortunately they had blood lightning beads in their hands. And in addition to their fast mounts, they were able to run away in order to save themselves from the magic beast attack.

This battle also demonstrated how mighty the Divine Race were. Only those who face the Divine Race understood how terrible it would be to fight against them. These people only faced a subpar heavy cavalry unit of the Divine Race. If they faced stronger Divine Race forces, then they could only be faced with a massacre.

What disappointed the Beastmen this time was the fact that their weapons were unable to be used against the Divine Race. If Zhao Hai hadn’t given them some blood lightning beads, then it might have been very difficult for them to kill any heavy cavalry unit.

This did not mean that their weapons were vastly inferior to the Divine Race, this simply meant that they had inferior strength. It can be said that the heavy cavalry only had average strength. Without their charge, then they wouldn’t have had many good points. However, even with their 8th rank strength, the heavy cavalry soldiers also held innate strength, something that even Beastmen were unable to compare with. This aspect allowed the Beastmen understand the Divine Race’s strength.

Seeing with one’s own eyes was truly different from hearing about it. The Beastmen now knew why Zhao Hai paid so much attention into the war with the Divine Race. At the same time, the Beastmen were now more convinced of Zhao Hai. They understood that they needed to pour all of their strength into the war, sparing nothing in order to gain victory.

As the fight continued, Cloud Ying began to discover that taking the city this day would be impossible. Zhao Hai had too many methods in order to deal with their advance. It seems like the war would need to be drawn out for a long time.

At this time, the Elves had returned to the battlefield. However, there were no horned pegasus cavalry going after them, all of them killed, never to come back.

Cloud Ying started to count the losses on his side. He discovered that from the start to the present, they had losses that surpassed ten thousand people. One must know that it had only been a few hours since the fight started. Cloud Ying didn’t expect that they would have this much loss.

In the past, Cloud Ying felt disdain towards Silver Shuke for being unable to take the city and even managed to take heavy casualties. He thought that Silver Shuke was very incompetent in his job. But as it turns out, it was actually because of the multitude of tricks that Zhao Hai had. Most importantly, Zhao Hai even managed to eliminate the Deity’s projection, this was too big of an impact to their morale.

The heavy cavalry has been stopped, as well as the light cavalry. At this point, there was no way for them to proceed. This made Cloud Ying think, they had already lost ten thousand people, it wouldn’t be great if this situation were to go on for much longer.

Cloud Ying looked at the battlefield. The infantry were yet to go forward, but the heavy and light cavalries were already stopped, they even managed to take huge losses. Additionally, the combat capabilities of Zhao Hai’s undead wasn’t any weak and were still quite numerous. Cloud Ying couldn’t help but grit his teeth as he commanded, “Withdraw!”

Just as he said that, a messenger beside him immediately took out a small copper bell and proceeded to knock on it. Although the bronze bell was very small, it was very loud. The entire battlefield were able to hear the loud banging sound of the bell.

The Divine Race knew that this signal meant retreat. Therefore, they didn’t dare to continue on. They made their formations and the proceeded to slowly retreat.

Zhao Hai saw this and didn’t order his troops to pursue. The army the Divine Race had sent out today wasn’t a lot. Zhao Hai was afraid that if they pursue, then they might fall into an ambush. And even if there was no ambush, the Divine Race could just send their other troops to attack the city while Zhao Hai clashed with the retreating troops. After all, Zhao Hai was aware of the number of troops that were present in the Divine Race’s camp.

Zhao Hai just stood there, looking at the Divine Race army as they slowly drew back. However, his mood was actually very heavy. Although they had managed to repel the Divine Race today, the methods that they showed made Zhao Hai feel quite terrible.

This was especially true for their method of summoning that immortal cultivator. This made Zhao Hai very vigilant. The opposite party’s projection almost managed to kill him. If that was his main body, how strong could he be? If the Divine Race decided to summon a lot of immortal cultivators, then the Ark Continent’s troubles would surely be big.

After the Divine Race retreated, Zhao Hai returned to the city’s wall. When Lizzy saw Zhao Hai, she quickly said, “Big Brother Hai, are you alright? Did you get hurt?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I’m fine, don’t worry. We’ve also managed to get some good harvests this time. Right, a lot of Dwarves and Beastmen managed to get injured this time. Prepare to have them cured as soon as possible.”

Lizzy nodded, then she immediately gave orders to the people in the army. They also had the city’s defensive formation taken down, allowing the three groups from outside to go in.

Before long, the three army divisions came back. Some of these people were injured, while some died. Zhao Hai didn’t turn those who fell in battle into his undead, that method was only reserved for his enemies, he wouldn’t do the same for his allies. Although this will make him lose a lot of potential undead, he knew that if he did this, the three races would get angry. Even if they didn’t get angry in front of him, it would still bring resentment, possibly making future cooperation very difficult.

Since Lizzy already made preparations ahead of time, the injured were immediately given treatment after they arrived. Zhao Hai also had his undead assist in giving aid. At the same time, Zhao Hai also called the various leaders over. They were to meet at the city lord’s mansion’s battle room.

After all of them arrived and had sat down, Zhao Hai immediately said, “The fight with the Divine Race, what do you think?”

The complexion of these people weren’t very good. The Divine Race were more powerful than they imagined. If they didn’t have the blood lightning beads and Zhao Hai, then it would be impossible for them to achieve today’s result.

Seeing their expressions, Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Can’t speak? Think that they’re too powerful? Haha. They are indeed strong, but as you can see, they were still repelled. Don’t worry, my side has been working hard in order to produce potions that can promote your levels. When that time comes, you won’t be too afraid of fighting with the Divine Race anymore.”

Baker gave a nod and said, “The Divine Race are surely formidable. However, they aren’t invincible beings. If our strengths improved, then we could surely fight them head to head.”

The group nodded. They were also aware of the difference between them and the Divine Race. The most gleaming disparity was their strength. The weakest level soldier in the Divine Race army were 8th ranks. However, 8th ranks were already seen as strong people in the Ark Continent’s side. This difference in perception was just too big.

Chapter 745: The Prophecy Must Be Fulfilled

The disparity of strength was obvious, but it also lead to a headache. Strength cannot be met with just a day of practice. And this issue was prevalent to all the armies in the Ark Continent.

Ordinary armies in the Ark Continent weren’t very strong. At most, the soldiers in those armies have about 5th rank in strength. Even the elite troops of the continent had 7th and 8th ranks as their strongest members, and on average, have 6th rank soldiers.

If the Ark Continent went to war with the other countries using such armies, then there would be no problems. However, these kinds of armies were simply insufficient when it came to fighting the Demons and the Divine Race. There was no need to say about the army of the Divine Race, their weakest soldier had 8th rank strength. At the same time, the Demons were very strong as well, their weakest being 7th rank. If we factor in their environment and upbringing, the Demons would be no worse than the Divine Race. As the matter stands, there was a huge gap of strength between the residents of the Ark Continent and their two invaders.

Zhao Hai looked at the group present and then gave a smile, “The matter of strength is easy to deal with. Soon, I will bring in a batch of potions that would improve your strengths to at least 8th rank. When that time comes, you would have more capabilities to fight against the Divine Race.”

Baker and the others nodded with a happy expression. For them, this was absolutely good news. If they didn’t come to to Upper Bank City, then they might not have known when they’ll be able to drink Zhao Hai’s potions. After all, the continent’s population was just too large. Even if the plan to upgrade soldiers had begun, they wouldn’t know which month or even year they would get their turn. Zhao Hai looked at them and said, “While we wait for the potions, everyone should think of tactics in order to deal with the Divine Race. You have seen their capabilities in today’s battle. They are quite strong, moreover, their formations were skillfully executed as well. If we want to defeat them, then we would need more than strength to do so.”

The group nodded, then Zhao Hai continued, “You just need to wait for a bit before I arrange for the potions. Also, make sure to place those injured in the rear. I will deal with the other injured soldiers when I return. Take care of them, I’m sure the Divine Race wouldn’t attack so soon. I am more worried about the Demons at this time. It wouldn’t be great for us if they decide to move.”

When the group heard Zhao Hai, their hearts couldn’t help but tighten. In the past, they didn’t have any feelings about this, but after going against the Divine Race, they truly understood the situation they were in. There was already a huge disparity between the Ark Continent and the Divine Race, and there were the Demons as well. They couldn’t help but feel anxious while thinking about this.

When he saw everyone’s expression, Zhao Hai said, “Alright, you should all get a rest. We just had a fight, everyone should be tired.” Then everyone stood up and left after giving Zhao Hai a salute.

When the group left, Zhao Hai immediately brought Lizzy and the others back into the Space. Laura’s group were quite busy inside the Space, taking care of the various commodities to be supplied to the continent. It can be said that Laura and Ruyen were the most busy among the people inside.

Zhao Hai greeted everyone before they all sat down. Then Zhao Hai said, “In today’s battle, the Divine Race summoned a person. He was called Deity by the Divine Race. From this title, one could say that he is a higher level existence compared to the Divine Race. And he was really powerful, only a mere projection from him managed to show such great strength. If it weren’t for Cai’er, I might have been in grave danger. If the Divine Race can summon a person like that, then it might be possible for them to summon another one. It would be a big problem if several of those people appeared simultaneously.”

Laura and the others knew about the degree of danger that this entailed, therefore, they couldn’t help but frown. Lizzy replied, “What is Big Brother Hai planning to do with it?”

Zhao Hai said, “We’ll just need to prepare for it. If the Divine Race could really summon a lot of people just like that, then we need to get ready to transfer the people of the continent into the Space in the shortest period of time. What do all of you think?”

Laura nodded and said, “It looks like this is the only way. The Demons and the Divine Race are already our limit. If those higher level people appear, then we could only evacuate the entire continent’s population into the Space.”

Lizzy looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Big Brother Hai, do we need to tell the Patriarchs about this matter? Making them prepare for it in advance?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “Let’s withhold this information for now lest we cause unnecessary panic. Let’s wait first and hope that our speculations aren’t true.”

At this time, Zhao Hai’s expression suddenly changed. He waved his hand and took out a messenger fish. This messenger fish was paired up with the Elf Queen’s own messenger fish. What matter did the Elf Queen have this time? Did an accident happen in the Elven Forest?

Zhao Hai immediately talked into the messenger fish, “Your Majesty, what’s the problem?” Then he looked towards the monitor as Cai’er displayed the Queen’s room.

Currently, the Elf Queen looked very anxious. Her complexion was somewhat pale, it seems like something terrible has happened.

When the Queen heard Zhao Hai’s voice, she immediately replied, “Mister, something happened. Our Elven Race’s Divine treasure, the Tree of Life, is withering. Mister, please come over and see it.”

Zhao Hai gawked, then he immediately thought of the Dwarf Race’s prophecy. In that prophecy, the Elves’ Tree of Life would wither.

The Elves had always regarded the Tree of Life as their Deity. They had always thought that it was a gift from the Goddess of Life to the Elves. And the Tree of Life did indeed give benefits to the Elven Race. Not only did it allow the Elves to understand life magic better, its liquid of life was also a good medicine for healing and cultivation. The first version of Spatial Water was another form of the liquid of life.

The Tree of Life had grown for many years without withering. Even with Zhao Hai’s status, the Elves still wouldn’t allow him from seeing it. Once could see how well-regarded the tree was to the Elves. However, they didn’t expect the tree to actually start to wither. To the Elves, this was an extremely important matter.

When Zhao Hai heard the Elf Queen, he couldn’t help but get anxious as well, he quickly replied, “When did you find out? Tell me what happened.” The Queen’s expression stayed tense as she replied, “Just today. I always go to the Tree of Life everyday in order to offer my worship. While I was praying, I found out that there was a hint of withering to the Tree of Life. I knew that this matter has been mentioned in the prophecy of the Dwarves, therefore, I decided to approach Mister to ask if you have any way of healing it.”

Zhao Hai immediately said, “First, block this news from going out. Don’t let other people know about it. I will be coming over there soon.”

Zhao Hai was very clear, if the Elves were to know that their Tree of Life was withering, then there was no doubt that they would go absolutely crazy. Its significance would trump the threat that the Demons and the Divine Race had caused.

The Queen agreed, then Zhao Hai immediately stored his messenger fish before his figure disappeared from the Space before it reappeared inside the Even Race’s city. Then he directly soared towards the Royal Palace.

Zhao Hai’s status was now an Elder of the Elven Race, and in addition to the times being hectic, the guarding Elves only thought that something had happened in the frontline. Therefore, they didn’t mind Zhao Hai’s presence too much and just opened the doors to the Royal Palace.

The Queen was very uneasy as she repeatedly walked around the room and then took a seat and then took a walk again. So when she heard the notification that Zhao Hai had arrived, she immediately said, “Invite Mister over, quickly!”

After Zhao Hai entered the Great Hall, the Queen turned to the guards and said, “Go and leave the hall. Make sure to close the door and don’t allow anybody else to enter.” The two guards nodded before they turned around and left the Great Hall.

After the guards left, Zhao Hai turned to the Queen and said, “Your Majesty, why did the Tree of Life wither? Do you have any ideas about it?”

The Queen shook her head and said, “I really don’t know. I just discovered that the leaves of the tree had begun to wilt. This case never happened before. Mister, come with me.” Then Zhao Hai gave a nod before the Queen turned around and led Zhao Hai behind the Great Hall.

Behind the Great Hall was a small courtyard. In this courtyard were two voiceless soundbirds. The Queen sat on one of them as Zhao Hai rode the other. Then the voiceless soundbirds flapped their wings and proceeded to fly upwards and towards an area above the city.

The city was very high, Zhao Hai didn’t even know how much, he hadn’t gone this high up before. Therefore, he had no idea about where they were going.

The voiceless soundbirds were almost flying in a vertical fashion. They flew non-stop for about a couple of hours before they stopped on a branch. This branch was not very thick, only able to accommodate one person walking on top of it. Not too far from where they landed was a hole, it was dark inside making it hard to see what was going on.

The Queen dismounted from the voiceless soundbird as she proceeded to walk towards that hole. While she walked over, she said, “For many years, mister will be the first outsider to come to this place.”

Zhao Hai stared blankly at the Queen. He didn’t understand what the Queen was saying. He thought that they were currently on the massive Tree of Life, it grew for all these years to become this big and tall. Zhao Hai thought that the Tree of Life was this giant tree, now it looks like this wasn’t the case.

Before long, Zhao Hai had entered the hole with the Queen. Upon entering the hole, they took a turn before taking yet another turn. This explained why the hole looked dark from the outside. At this time, Zhao Hai noticed a hint of green light shining in front of him. Then he slowly felt a strong wave of energy coming from that direction.

The Queen didn’t speak as she unconsciously made light footsteps. Zhao Hai had a faint understanding of where they were going to, so he also did the same.

The green light up front got brighter and brighter. Zhao Hai can also feel the energy getting stronger and stronger. Although this energy was very strong, it actually gave people a type of gentle feeling, just like warm sunlight, just like a mother’s hand, gently stroking your skin, making you feel warm. Zhao Hai’s mind couldn’t help but turn tranquil.

Chapter 746: Method to Upgrade the Undead

After entering a small arched entrance, Zhao Hai and the Queen got into a fairly big room. All in all, this room had more than 100 square meters. In the middle of this room was a pool, and in the middle of the pool was a short and small tree.

The tree was very unusual. Its whole body was green but it was almost transparent. It looked more like a crystal than an actual tree.

What made Zhao Hai feel strange was that this tree only had nine twigs, and each twig only had a single leaf. Each leaf also looked like a crystal, but their veins were of deeper color, they looked very beautiful.

However, among these nine leaves, one of them had started to turn yellowish. It looks like the leaf was slowly dying.

On the side of the pool were several mats. One could see that these mats were very clean, evidence that it was used quite frequently.

The Queen arrived on a mat and gently knelt, paying obedience towards the small tree in the middle of the pond. Then she stood up and turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, this is the Divine treasure of our Race, the Tree of Life. In the past, all of the leaves of this tree are green. But today, I have discovered that one had turned yellow. This reminded me of the prophecy of the Dwarves. So I immediately asked mister over in order to see it.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he arrived by the pool. The pool wasn’t very big, but it was completely filled with water. He examined the liquid of life inside the pool, it seems like this one was of a higher quality compare to what the Space had before.

The Tree of Life lived on this pool. There wasn’t even a single particle of soil inside the pool, making it seem like the Tree of Life was being a parasite on the giant tree.

Zhao Hai frowned, to be honest, he didn’t know if the Space was able to save this tree. It would be great if the Space did, however, if it can’t, then the Elf Race would be in big trouble.

The Queen looked at Zhao Hai’s expression, her heart couldn’t help but sink. She thought that Zhao Hai didn’t have the means to save the Tree of Life. However, she still asked, “Does Mister have any ways of saving the tree?”

Zhao Hai turned his head to the Queen and replied, “I have a solution in mind, however, I’m not sure if it could work. Moreover, I cannot treat it here, I need to bring the tree to another place in order to cure it. If Your Majesty agrees, then I can try. If you don’t, then I have no other methods in mind.”

As soon as she heard Zhao Hai, the Queen couldn’t help but stare for a moment before she knit her brows and said, “Mister, the Tree of Life is too important for the Elves. I alone don’t have the authority to immediately decide on this matter. I need to discuss this with the elders before giving you a concrete answer.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright, but Your Majesty should know about the effect of this matter more than I do, so I will not say any more. I just hope that you keep this a secret, we can’t afford to have panic among the Elves at this time. Just know that if you decide to let me cure the tree, then I am confident that I have an 80 percent chance of succeeding. Also, it wouldn’t take too long.”

The Queen stared for a moment before she gave a nod and said, “Alright, Mister can rest assured. I shall handle this matter with care.” Then she led Zhao Hai out of the hole.

After exiting, Zhao Hai didn’t ride the voiceless soundbird, instead, she turned to the Queen and said, “Your Majesty, I won’t be staying here for long. My presence if heavily needed in the frontlines. If you agree to my arrangement, then you can just inform me through the messenger fish.”

The Queen nodded and said, “Alright, then I’ll have to trouble Mister when the time comes.” Then Zhao Hai gave a bow before his figure vanished. After Zhao Hai vanished, the Queen silently rode her voiceless soundbird and then proceeded to return to the Royal Palace.

Zhao Hai didn’t return to Upper Bank City, but instead entered the Space. He had assigned Cai’er to look after the city for him.

Since nothing happened in the city, Zhao Hai decided to count his gains from today. Currently, the magic beasts of the Space had been promoted. Unfortunately, the majority of them only reached 9th rank, nobody reached God-rank. Moreover, of the undead that he had absorbed, very few of them were God-rank. Most of them were 9th rank or were promoted to 9th rank by the Space.

There was no other explanation for this, most of their kills today were from the Divine Race’s heavy and light cavalry. These two units weren’t that high in the Divine Race’s hierarchy, so their strengths were very limited.

Moreover, Zhao Hai discovered that the Space’s hurdle to God-rank wasn’t as easy as before where he only needed to wait for specific conditions to be filled before the undead gets promoted. Take the light element undead, after acquiring the three divine artifacts, this made them God-rank. As for the undead assassins, they only managed to get promoted by having absorbed Shiying. And lastly, the fire element undead were only promoted after absorbing Tiger Huan along with more God-rank fire element experts.

Zhao Hai guessed the reason why this was the case, it was because of the number of the undead. At this time, the largest number of undead that he had were all from the water element while the least number came from the light element. This was the reason why it only took three divine artifacts before all the light element undead got promoted to God-rank. The energy needed to upgrade all of those undead was only small. This was the same case for the dark element undead, they only needed Shiying’s energy in order to be promoted. This case was also proven when we think about the time where Tiger Huan’s death didn’t immediately upgrade the fire element undead. Only after absorbing more fire element God-ranks did the fire element undead get promoted to God-rank.

At this point, it seems like upgrading the undead in the Space wouldn’t be very easy. It would need a lot of energy before all of the undead were to become God-rank.

Although they had killed a lot of Divine Race soldiers today, a large part of them weren’t God-rank, some haven’t even reached 9th rank. Because of this, the undead in the Space didn’t level up. On the other hand, Zhao Hai managed to get living magic beasts into the Space, which in turn promoted the magic beasts in the Space.

Although all of these were just guesses, Zhao Hai felt that his speculation wasn’t wrong. Still, he wanted to confirm, so he called Cai’er over and asked about the Space’s condition of promoting the undead.

Sure enough, the explanation that Zhao Hai got from Cai’er was similar to his guess. If he wanted to promote the undead into God-rank, then he would need energy that was the same as their attribute. Moreover, the energy needed to be related to death. As for the Divine Artifacts, they weren’t living beings in the end, so the energy inside them can be considered as dead. It was completely unlike the living energy inside trees and grasses as well as living beings. All of those living energies were useless to the undead.

The reason why Shiying and Tiger Huan managed to upgrade the undead was because they were killed. After being killed, their energies became dead, allowing them to benefit the undead.

Upon hearing Cai’er, Zhao Hai understood. This was the reason why the undead didn’t level up after Bubble entered the Space. Although Bubble didn’t seem like a living being, he actually had consciousness, this was akin to being a living creature. The energy in Bubble’s body was living, therefore cannot be used by the undead.

Zhao Hai became impatient about this condition. It seems like if he wanted to upgrade the undead in the future, then he would need to kill God-ranks with the same attributes as them. Only in this way could the undead have enough energy to level up.

Zhao Hai sighed and then let go of this matter. Then he looked at Cai’er and said, “Cai’er, can you analyze the state of the Tree of Life? Why would it suddenly wither like that?” Cai’er shook her head and said, “Young Master, unless the Tree of Life goes inside the Space, there is no way that I can analyze its state.” Zhao Hai knit his brows and replied, “Then do you think that the Space can cure the Tree of Life?” Cai’er smiled and said, “There’s no issue about that. Young Master, don’t forget, the Space could even resurrect plants that are dead for over one month. Curing the Tree of Life wouldn’t be a problem. Moreover, seeing how formidable the Tree of Life was, it is highly probable that it could make the Space level up.”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly and said, “Let’s hope so.”

Then Zhao Hai opened the monitor to see the situation at Rising Sun City. He wanted to see the current development of the Demon Race. Although there weren’t any actions coming from the Demon side, their numbers of God-ranks had kept increasing. At this moment, their God-rank experts had reached ten thousand. This made Zhao Hao’s expression uglier. The Demons and the Divine Race were very strong. Now that the Demon numbers had increased, Zhao Hai alone wouldn’t be able to stop them even if he went to Rising Sun City. But fortunately for him the had sent some crystals and magic cannons over to the city. This would allow them to withstand for a while, but not for long. At that time, Zhao Hai can only make use of the Space to rescue the people there.

The main issue for them at this time was the possibility that the Demons and the Divine Race would simultaneously attack. This will make Zhao Hai unable to focus on one without abandoning the other. With him being unable to split his head into two, true trouble would come.

Zhao Hai didn’t have any good ideas to deal with this situation. Although he held good things in his hands, these weren’t even enough to deal with one of them, much less two.

At this moment, the main weapon in Zhao Hai’s hand were his undead. All of these undead would be able to resist one of them but were not enough to block both. Splitting the undead would only lead to them being killed off by the Demons and the Divine Race, causing losses on both fronts. Once the undead gets killed off, then Zhao Hai’s might would diminish as well. When that time comes, it would be extremely difficult for him to find ways in order to resist the Demons and the Divine Race.

Chapter 747: Anxious Elves

Zhao Hai was calmly walking on the Space’s grassland. After the Space absorbed the wind bead, a breeze would blow here once in a while. This made the Space much more comfortable to be in, allowing Zhao Hai to relax more.

The Divine Race and the Demon Race were two colossal mountains that weighed down on Zhao Hai’s shoulders. Majority of his time was consumed in thinking about how to fight the two. This thought tightened his heart, not allowing him time to relax, making him feel very tired.

As he slowly walked around, Zhao Hai had unexpectedly arrived by the Processing machine. While looking at the timer, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but sigh. He was very happy about acquiring a treasure, but behind such a treasure was a powerful enemy. This gave Zhao Hai an even bigger headache, much bigger compared to the Divine Race.

Zhao Hai gently rubbed his temples, everything was quite rocky at this point. Things kept coming one after the other, it’s very exhausting.

However, these matters needed to be dealt with, no matter how troublesome they were. Zhao Hai couldn’t help but give out another sigh as he looked back at the beating timer. In less than two days, the soul eating pagoda would have been finished in its upgrade.

To be honest, Zhao Hai liked the ability of the pagoda. As long as the tiny pagoda levels up, then perhaps he might be able to get a better method in upgrading the undead. Moreover, through this tiny pagoda, Zhao Hai would be able to understand more about the immortal cultivator, this would allow him ample materials to prepare for.

After having a walk on the surroundings, Zhao Hai managed to relax his mood quite a bit, then he proceeded to return to the villa’s living room. Laura and the others were also done with their chores and were now currently sitting in the living room, looking at the monitor. The monitor was currently showing the Radiant Empire. At this moment, the Divine Race had already seized the whole Empire. Moreover, they had also established protective shields in the various major cities while building military barracks inside them.

After seeing these barracks, Zhao Hai finally understood why the Divine Race decided to bring such bulky magic cannons. The cannons were already placed on the city walls, manned by several soldiers. It seems like the cannons were to be used as the city’s defensive weapons.

After noticing that Zhao Hai had come back, Laura and the others quickly stood up. Laura looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, you’re back.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I just went on a short stroll to relax. Are done? How was it?”

Laura nodded and said, “The transportation is on track. The nations already knew how to coordinate, so we’re quite relaxed this time.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “That’s good, don’t tire yourself too much. Now we’re waiting for the Elves to finish their discussion. If they decide to allow the Tree of Life into the Space, then the Space might level up. Let’s just see where their decision takes us.”

Laura gave a faint smile and said, “Of course they’ll agree. If they don’t then they could only helplessly look at the Tree of Life as it slowly dies. The Elves couldn’t bear such a sight.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he turned to the Divine Race barracks, he sighed and said, “I’m afraid that this is only a part of the Divine Race army. I have a feeling that there’ll be more of them coming. If our strengths aren’t promoted when that time comes, then I’m afraid we won’t be able to stop the Divine Race’s attack.”

When they heard Zhao Hai, Laura and the others couldn’t help but turn silent. The attacks made by the Divine Race in the past two confrontations could be said to be fairly non-violent, and the number of attackers wasn’t that large. It seems like the Divine Race were still focused on their barracks. From what Zhao Hai could see, although the barracks has been set-up, they also look completely empty, they weren’t filled up. This might not be strange, after all, the Radiant Empire had about 100 million citizens while the Divine Race army only numbered 10 million.

However, seeing that they can’t fill the cities, the Divine Race still decided to construct their barracks. The only explanation to this was that they were preparing for the arrival of more armies in the future.

In this regard, one could say that the Divine Race were stronger than the Demons. Although the Demons had prepared to invade the Ark Continent for a long time, they were quite behind in preparation compared to the Divine Race. The Divine Race had the Radiant Church to aid them, and also the Radiant Empire for sacrifices, allowing them to change the laws of the Ark Continent. Now, the Divine Race already had their own place to settle in, unlike the Demons who needed to construct their own city.

Lizzy turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Big Brother Hai, if the Divine Race and Demons decided to attack at the same time, what do we do?”

Zhao Hai knit his eyebrows and said, “Then we can only retreat and fall back to the Accra Mountains. There, we would be able to block both the Demons and the Divine Race. As long as we stop them for quite some time, I believe that their cooperation would start to crumble.”

Laura nodded and said, “This was our previous plan, however, we still underestimated the Divine Race and the Demons. We originally wanted to have the fight happen in the Buddha Empire, but now it seem like that won’t be the case.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “If the Demons and the Divine Race keep on increasing their numbers, then we could only fall back to the Accra Mountains and defend on both fronts. However, we must drag the current situation for as long as we can. The Accra Mountain needs to have more time to prepare.”

Laura nodded, then she said, “Brother Hai, how about we give some blood lightning beads to father? Maybe he can find ways in order to improve it.”

Zhao Hai shook his head, “No, the blood lightning bead is extremely dangerous, it wouldn’t be good if father gets injured. Having the blood lightning beads in the hands of the Elves is enough. What we need to do is to promote their strength as soon as possible. Speaking of which, I need to bring some spatial water out into the city. We’ll strengthen the soldiers first.”

Laura and the others nodded, then Zhao Hai looked at the situation back in the city. Everything was very normal, after all, a fight just happened. Everyone was very tired and has been resting.

Lizzy turned her head to Zhao Hai and said, “Big Brother Hai, you should take a rest as well. You can go out after you wake up. This would also allow the soldiers to have proper rest.”

After seeing the situation of the soldiers, Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright, everyone should also get some rest. I’m afraid the Divine Race would make another move in the following days.”

Laura and the others were also quite tired in the past few days. Battles were happening one after another. Although Laura’s group weren’t involved in the fighting, their logistics work was more troublesome and exhausting. They haven’t rested well for a long time, so they needed this time to recover.

The next morning, Zhao Hai got up early and prepared a massive amount of spatial water before going out of the Space. At this time, the entire mountain was much livelier than before.

After the battle, the people were extremely tired. But at the same time, they also felt excitement they never felt before. They were too tired yesterday, so they immediately went to rest. Now that they had recovered, their vigor flared up, excited conversations began to bubble up in every part of the city.

After arriving at the city lord’s mansion, Zhao Hai immediately called the leaders of the various groups and gave them some spatial water. Moreover, he also told them that in the next two days, they wouldn’t need to fight, they needed to focus on improving their strength.

Naturally, the leaders of the groups became very happy. They had been waiting for this day. Even if they were the most elite troops of their respective armies, 8th ranks were still quite rare among them. Having this opportunity to reach that rank would make anyone very happy.

After having distributed the spatial water, Zhao Hai received a message from the Elf Queen. They had agreed to Zhao Hai’s conditions.

This made Zhao Hai stare, he didn’t think that the Elves would reach a decision in such a short time. However, he still made his way to the Elves’ Royal palace. After arriving at the palace, Zhao Hai discovered that the atmosphere was not quite right. Although the ordinary guards didn’t know about the problem, the 9th rank supreme elders of the race were all inside the palace. This made the atmosphere inside the Great Hall very hard to breath in.

Zhao Hai stared at this development before going inside the Great Hall. Inside, the Queen wasn’t on her throne, instead, she stood right by the 9th rank Elders of the Elven Race. Zhao Hai hasn’t seen these people before, it seems like they were the strong and elderly people in the race. What made Zhao Hai quite happy about these people was that some of them were very close to breaking through to God-rank.

However, Zhao Hai also discovered that the mood of these people were quite gloomy, their expressions pale. They were actually very anxious, it can be seen from their faces how much they valued the Tree of Life.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but frown, if these elders maintained this kind of mindset, then they would find it impossible to break through to God-rank. It looks like the matter of the Tree of Life needed to be solved as soon as possible.

Upon seeing Zhao Hai arrive, the Queen immediately welcomed him. With an anxious expression she said, “Mister, you came. We agree to Mister’s request. Mister, please follow me quickly, please save the Tree of Life.”

Zhao Hai looked at the Queen, he couldn’t help but be curious as he asked, “Your Majesty, did something drastic happen?”

The Queen looked at Zhao Hai and sighed, “Mister, just this morning, two of the tree’s leaves have withered. Time doesn’t allow us to wait.”

Zhao Hai gawked, in just two days, two of the leaves had wilted. If they couldn’t cure the tree in the following days, then it might certainly die. Losing the Tree of Life would be an extremely huge hit towards the Elven Race.

Zhao Hai immediately replied, “Alright, please take me over there. I’ll cure the Tree of Life as soon as possible.”

The Queen nodded, then she walked towards the Palace’s back courtyard and sat on a voiceless soundbird before flying up. Today, she didn’t prepare a mount for Zhao Hai. She knew that with Zhao Hai’s strength, there would be no need for him to ride a mount. Moreover, Zhao Hai wasn’t the only one who wouldn’t need a mount. The 9th rank Elders were also going with them so see the tree.

Chapter 748: Unlocked, Magic Background

When Zhao Hai arrived by the Tree of Life, he could clearly see how worse it had become. Yesterday, only a single leaf had turned yellow. But now, there were two leaves. Although they had yet to fall from the tree, one could see that they were already dead, without any life.

Zhao Hai slowly walked over to the Tree of Life, carefully investigating it. The tree wasn’t showing any defects, it was still beautiful. However, the two dead leaves had taken away some of the tree’s elegance.

The Queen and the elders were nervously looking at Zhao Hai. They were afraid that Zhao Hai wouldn’t be able to cure the tree. If that were the case, then the Elven Race would be in deep trouble.

Actually, Zhao Hai wanted to see how long the roots of the Tree of Life were. He wanted to collect the tree without damaging the roots. After watching for a while, Zhao Hai discovered something special. Zhao Hai thought that the Tree of Life was being parasitic towards the large tree. Now that he had taken a closer look, this didn’t seem to the the case at all. The tree of life was actually growing inside the small pond, there was no connection between it and the large tree. It can be said that the Tree of Life was floating on water.

This discovery made Zhao Hai surprised. He didn’t think that this would be the case. But this also made him more relaxed in gathering the tree.

Zhao Hai turned to the Queen and said, “Your Majesty, I’ll be taking the Tree of Life. I will have information by tomorrow. Does Your Majesty agree?”

The Elf Queen turned to look at the 9th rank elders who proceeded to nod their heads. The Tree of Life was just too important to the Elven Race, and Zhao Hai was their final hope. If Zhao Hai couldn’t treat the tree, then nobody in the continent could.

The reason why these people had confidence in Zhao Hai was because he already managed to help them fix their Divine Artifact, the Elven Bow. For the Elves, the Elven Bow and the Tree of Life held the same importance. It was because of this that the Elves decided to trust Zhao Hai.

Seeing the elders nod, the Queen turned her head to Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, please continue. We agree.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he waved his hand, making a spatial rift appear and cover the Tree of Life. The Elves looked with worry at the appearance of the spatial rift. They were afraid that the rift would wound the Tree of Life.

Fortunately, Zhao Hai was now very skillful in controlling his spatial rifts. The rift slowly slid down the sides of the pool, never touching the Tree of Life. The rift also brought the water from the pool into the Space.

After transporting the Tree of Life as well as the liquid of life over to the Space, Zhao Hai let out a long breath. Then he turned his head to the Queen and said, “Your Majesty, I will surely find a way to cure the Tree of Life. I’ll see you at the Palace tomorrow.” Then Zhao Hai’s figure vanished as he returned to the Space.

After arriving at the Space, Zhao Hai immediately took the Tree of Life out of the warehouse and placed it in the space’s pool. Just as the Tree of Life appeared, the Space immediately issued a prompt. “Pollution detected in item full of wood element. Treatment of the lifeform would need 1 million gold coins from the host.”

When Zhao Hai heard the prompt, he immediately became happy before he was met with grief. He was glad that the Tree of Life can be cured, and was sad because he would need to fork out a million gold coins in order to do so.

However, Zhao Hai still didn’t delay as he said, “Immediately start the treatment.”

A white light suddenly shone from the Space and covered the Tree of Life. The previous yellow leaves of the tree started to turn back into green. Moreover, the leaves have become more vibrant compared to before.

Before long, the white light vanished as the Tree of Life went back to its healthy state. Moreover, it looked more healthy compared to before. Zhao Hai couldn’t help but let out a long breath after seeing the result.

At this time, another prompt came from the Space, “Discovered massive amounts of dark energy from the lifeform. Increasing its resistance to dark energy. Dark energy has been withdrawn, may be used by the Processing Machine in order to upgrade itself. Wood element energy inside the Space has been increased. Five element requirement has been met. Host may use the power of the five elements in order to upgrade his Life Treasure Dao Lotus.”

Since this was a good thing, Zhao Hai quickly said, “Upgrade it immediately.”

Then another prompt came, “Upgrading Processing Machine, time required, 12 hours. Upgrade to host’s treasure can be done immediately, gold coins are not needed.”

Zhao Hai gave an affirmative nod and said, “Do it.” Then just as his voice fell, a five colored light suddenly fell into his body. Zhao Hai could vaguely feel the five colored light penetrate his body. After going around his body two times, the light entered his middle dantian and into the lotus. After the lotus absorbed the light, it looked even more beautiful. Zhao Hai knew that its beauty and delicateness was an illusion. The strength of the Dao Lotus right now was equal to the tiny pagoda, it might even be stronger.

What made Zhao Hai most surprised was the core in his lower dantian. It seems like it had also benefited from the five elements. It became golden yellow and had gotten bigger. On its top was a golden dragon. This wasn’t the same dragon as the ones in the Ark Continent, instead, it was a chinese dragon. The small dragon was on top of the core, eyes closed, as if it was sleeping.

On the other hand, the small man on Zhao Hai’s dantian had become more solidified. This startled Zhao Hai since he can also feel his spiritual strength increase. Moreover, his sense of the heavens and the earth had become more distinct.

Zhao Hai turned his head to look at the Processing Machine. It seems like there wasn’t much change aside from the timer that counted down from 12 hours.

At this time, Laura and the others arrived outside of the villa, curiously looking at the Tree of Life. Cai’er has also flown to Zhao Hai’s side. At this time, Zhao Hai discovered that Cai’er’s height had doubled. She was now as tall as a grown man’s arm.

Zhao Hai looked at Cai’er and said, “Cai’er, did the Tree of Life give you this much benefit?”

Cai’er smiled and said, “Young Master, I gained so much. Not only did it benefit me, the Tree of LIfe also influenced the plants in the Space. If the Tree of Life stays inside the Pace, then it can slowly upgrade the plants inside, giving it consciousness. When that time comes, they would be no different to the Flower Demons.”

Zhao Hai stared, then he immediately said, “Then can the Tree of Life develop sentience?”

Cai’er shook her head and said, “It can’t. The Tree of Life is just like an energy converter. It can convert all types of energy into wood element energy. If it lives inside the Space, not only could it let the plants grow better, it can also produce wood element crystal stones. In the past, the Tree of Life couldn’t convert dark energy, but after going through the Space, it would be able to. Young Master, I suspect that your tiny pagoda and Dao Lotus has the same ability.”

Zhao Hai looked at the Tree of Life and couldn’t help but smile bitterly, “It’s a pity that we need to return the Tree of Life back to the Elves. We can’t keep it in the Space.”

Cai’er smiled and said, “Young Master, did you forget? The Tree of Life can now be purchased in the Space’s shop. You can buy a sapling and then wait for it to grow up.”

Zhao Hai forced a smile and said, “But we would need to wait for many years. This Tree of Life that the Elves grew took many years in order to reach this state. I’m afraid that by the time it grows up, I may have been dead for way too long.”

Cai’er smiled and said, “Young Master, you don’t know this but the Tree of Life is just unsuitable to be grown in the Elves’ forest. The land there didn’t have the requirements to grow a healthy Tree of Life. Because of this, their Tree of Life can only be considered as an extremely malnourished plant. This explains why it is this small. On the other hand, the Space is very suitable for growing the tree. This will cut a huge chunk of time for it to grow. Moreover, it would be much healthier compared to this one.’

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but laugh in glee, “Then we’ll wait. Immediately buy two saplings. Where do you think we’ll plant them? Do we need to grow them on the Farming Ground?”

Cai’er gave a smile, “There’s no need. Placing them on both sides of the Villa would be fine. The Tree of Life is not only an energy converter, it can also keep the energies stable. It will make the five elements in the Space more balanced.”

After she said that, Cai’er planted two Tree of Life saplings by the side of the villa. Zhao Hai was happy after seeing the two saplings. These two saplings weren’t any smaller than the Elves’ Tree of Life. It seems like the Elves’ Tree of Life was indeed undernourished.

After buying the two seedlings, the Space suddenly issued a prompt, “Energy stabilizing plants detected. Introduction of the plant has fulfilled the upgrade condition. Space has been upgraded to level 70. Host can now buy ten more backgrounds. Ample magic energy detected in the Space, unlocked a new type of background. Magic type background can now be purchased.”

“Hint: There are a lot of special environments in Magic-type backgrounds. In these environments, the host can cultivate more exotic magical plants and animals.”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare blankly after listening to the Space. This was the first time that he had heard of this type prompt. He didn’t understand what was happening, so he turned to Cai’er and said, “Cai’er, what’s happening?”

Cai’er smiled and said, “Congratulations, Young Master. You’ve gained a lot this time. The Space has unlocked the Magic backgrounds for our use. In other words, the Young Master can now purchase backgrounds commonly seen in magical worlds. For example, floating islands, mystical mountains, and some extreme terrains. These places would supply the proper environment for special plants and animals to grow in.”

Chapter 749: The Usage of the Magic Background

Upon hearing Cai’er, Zhao Hai understood. When Zhao Hai was still back on Earth, he had read some magic novels. Therefore, he knew that in these types of special environments treasures would thrive.

Although there were a lot of plants and animals in the Space, they weren’t that special. As for the treasures in the Ark Continent, there really weren’t much to begin with.

Compounding potions in the Space needed special materials. Ginseng, fo-ti, and other materials needed special environments in order to be grown efficiently. It was because of these limitations that the God-rank potion took a long time to make.

Just as what the prompt said, Zhao Hai can now purchase magic world backgrounds. For example, he can now buy a volcanic environment, a very hot place, but will be safe enough that the volcano would never erupt. In this place, herbs would be infused with fire element constantly, becoming treasures as time passes.

Moreover, these backgrounds can also be used to rear magic beasts. If a snake were to be placed in an environment with the same conditions as the Carrion Swamp, then that snake would eventually produce deadly poisons.

In the past, there was no such environment in the Space. Now that the magic backgrounds were unlocked, plants and animals can now be placed in special environments for controlled growth. In the future, herbs would be more readily available in the Space, this was also true for magic beasts. This will in turn cause potions to be more abundant.

After thinking about this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but laugh. He couldn’t stop himself from grabbing Cai’er and kissing her on her small tender face.

Zhao Hai’s action made Cai’er turn red, causing her to hide her reddened face from Laura and the others in embarrassment. Although Laura and the others couldn’t understand why Zhao Hai became overwhelmingly glad, Zhao Hai being in this state also made them happy. They couldn’t help but chuckle while looking at Zhao Hai’s actions.

After some time, Zhao Hai calmed down, then he turned to Cai’er and said, “Cai’er, are these backgrounds expensive? If they aren’t, then immediately buy ten. Just remember to pick the environments properly according to our needs.”

Cai’er’s face was still flushed, but when she heard Zhao Hai, she quickly replied, “Young Master, feel relieved, they aren’t very expensive. Our gold coins are enough to buy ten of them. I’ll arrange it immediately.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “That’s great. I’ll hand this matter over to you. If we have these backgrounds, will our production of God-rank potions increase?”

Cai’er nodded and said, “Yes, Young Master. As long as we have magic beasts and plants in these backgrounds, we should be able to make God-rank potions more frequently.”

Zhao Hai nodded, but suddenly he frowned as he said, “These backgrounds don’t have Farming Grounds that can shorten growth time. This is quite problematic.”

Cai’er smiled and said, “It won’t be. Young Master, now that the Space has levelled up to 70, you can now turn red clay into fertile soil. Not only could it increase yield, it can also make growth faster. And in those backgrounds, you can select some specific places where you can cultivate some plants. The land that can be transformed is limited to 1 percent of the total land area, however, I think that should still suffice.”

Zhao Hai became happy with this news, “Good, good. Then I’ll leave it to you to pick the spots, I don’t want to pick them myself. However, I’m certain that these would cost some money. Cai’er, look into our gold coins, if its not enough, then look at the things inside the Space that we won’t need in the near future and then sell them. These upgrades are more important to us, the rest are relatively worthless.”

Cai’er nodded. Zhao Hai’s choice to give this task to Cai’er was the right decision. This was because Cai’er was linked to the Space, so she knew every single change that happened inside it. And with the Space’s speed of calculation, Cai’er would be the most fit person to handle this task.

After arranging these, Zhao Hai felt relieved. Then he turned to look at the Tree of Life that had been healed and the Tree of Life saplings that looked healthier. Then he turned to the others and said, “I’ll have to send this back to the Elves. In any case, we already have our own inside the Space.”

Laura smiled and said, “Wait for some time, it hasn’t been too long. Let the Elves wait, hehe, its great looking at their worried faces.”

Zhao Hai laughed, “Alright, then let’s return to the living room and rest for a while. We gained greatly today. Let’s a;sp take a look at the magic world backgrounds that Cai’er had bought.”

After the group returned to the living room and sat down, Cai’er opened the store page and showed a decorated display. The difference from before was that the magic world column was now unlocked.

Cai’er picked ten designs, some of them beautiful while there was one with a gloomy and terrible aura. Then Cai’er turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Young Master, at this point, these ten backgrounds are the most suited to our cause.”

Zhao Hai looked at the backgrounds, the volcanic environment that he had thought of before was among them. There was also an environment filled with ice and snow, among other unique environments. Zhao Hai was quite satisfied with the choices. What Zhao Hai didn’t understand was the gloomy environment. You can even see skeletons, zombies, and other ghosts inside it. Moreover, there was no sun, the only thing on the sky was a round blood red moon. One could describe hell and this would be what they would show.

Zhao Hai looked at Cai’er and said, “Cai’er, why choose this background? It looks quite terrible.”

Cai’er smiled and said, “Young Master, this background is actually a replica of the Demon Realm. But this isn’t really the Demon Realm, this background is called Hell. It has strong dark energy inside, something very helpful for the undead. Young Master should remember that our undead aren’t too strong. If we can place them in this background, then it is possible for them to be promoted. Moreover, there are also plants that thrive in this kind of place, and they are of great value. These are the reasons why I chose to get this background.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “You’ve been very careful, good, I’ll trust your decision. Do what you need to do. Even the possibility of promoting the undead is a great investment to make.”

Cai’er nodded with a smile, then she waved her hand as she bought all of the backgrounds. Zhao Hai didn’t give much care as he saw the amount of his gold coins drop drastically. He thinks that these gold coins were placed in worthwhile investments.

After Cai’er bought the backgrounds, Zhao Hai went on and explored them. Every background was visited, he looked like a tourist strolling a new place.

On the other hand, Cai’er was busy placing plants and magic beasts in each of the backgrounds. She didn’t only plant herbal ingredients, she cultivated some agricultural crops as well. Cai’er decided to plant them in the backgrounds to see how they would develop.

At the same time, Cai’er also planted a Tree of Life on each background. Although the Trees of Life can balance energies, its capabilities weren’t that omnipotent. In the background named Hell, for example, the Tree of Life couldn’t just absorb every dark energy inside and transform the background into a normal one. Instead, the Tree of Life would only convert some dark energy into wood energy in order to aid the growth of the plants inside.

Zhao Hai didn’t bother Cai’er with her job, he was fully confident in her capabilities. It can be said that the one who knew the most about Zhao Hai wasn’t Laura, but Cai’er instead. Cai’er was combined with the Space while Zhao Hai was the host, one could say that Cai’er was Zhao Hai’s version of Artificial Intelligence that some novel protagonists would have. Since the Space was inside his mind, and Cai’er was connected to it, Cai’er was able to know what Zhao Hai needed.

After exploring the backgrounds, Zhao Hai returned to the Villa. To be honest, even if the backgrounds were beautiful, they still weren’t great places to live in. Think about it, do you want to live next to a volcano? Obviously that would be impossible.

It was still early, so Zhao Hai wasn’t anxious in returning to the Elves. Instead, he turned the monitor on and looked at the situation back in Upper Bank City.

The present situation of the city was quite good. There were plenty of 6 and 7th ranks that rose to 8th rank. Some still had low levels and were working hard. Those who had become 8th rank were now sporting happy expressions while they were getting familiar with their newly gained strength.

Zhao Hai likes to see this situation, but he still needed to wait before everyone gets to 8th rank before he begins to distribute the 9th rank potion. He wanted to promote them in batches, so even if the Divine Race attacks, there would still be people who’ll be available for battle.

It was wartime, anything was possible. Therefore, Zhao Hai wanted to be prepared for anything.

For the Divine Race to not make any further moves only meant that they were waiting. When their larger army arrives, then they would proceed to deal with Zhao Hai in one fell swoop. At this point, they have nearly 10 million troops. However, not all of them were God-ranks, 9th and 8th ranks still account for the majority. On the other hand, Zhao Hai had nearly 20 million undead, and majority of them were 9th ranks. If these two clash this instant, then it wouldn’t be good for the Divine Race. Therefore, they decided to wait for reinforcements before they attack once more.

Chapter 750: Another Prophecy

Zhao Hai calmly walked into the Elves’ Royal Palace. Upon reaching the palace, the guards couldn’t help but look at him in confusion. This was the third time in two days that Zhao Hai came to see the Elves. They didn’t understand why Zhao Hai would come here this frequently. If a huge incident happened in the frontlines, then they should have already heard about it. However, there was no news, they couldn’t help but be puzzled by this.

But they still didn’t dare to ask. This was because the Queen already gave an order to let Zhao Hai in if he ever came. Therefore, the guards politely guided Zhao Hai towards the Great Hall.

The Queen and the Supreme Elders were currently waiting for any news from Zhao Hai. At this time, it would be impossible for the Supreme Elders to resume their cultivation. Their minds wouldn’t be able to calm down as long as the problem with the Tree of Life still persists.

At this time, an elder opened his eyes and said, “He’s here.”

The people in the Great Hall immediately stood up, anxiously looking at the doors of the Great Hall. Before long, Zhao Hai walked in. The Queen immediately waved her hand, making the guards exit the hall while she and the Elders went forward to welcome Zhao Hai. All of them were looking at him with hopeful expression.

After seeing their expressions, Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Fortunately, I didn’t embarrass myself.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, the Queen and the Supreme Elders couldn’t help but cheer. This matter has been weighing down on their minds the entire time.

The Queen and the others immediately bowed to Zhao Hai. After seeing this, Zhao Hai immediately reacted, “Your Majesty, Elders, you are too polite. We’re allies, your problems are my problems. There’s no need for such gestures.”

The Queen and the Elders immediately straightened themselves up. The Queen looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, although what you said is true. This gesture is something that you needed to receive. Mister doesn’t understand how important the Tree of Life is to the Elven Race. Mister’s help in reviving the Tree of Life is equal to saving our entire race. We would be impolite if we don’t express our gratitude.”

Although the Elders didn’t say anything, each one of them were still looking at Zhao Hai with a grateful expression. Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Your Majesty, Elders, let’s head to the Tree of Life’s dwelling immediately. I can’t stay here for too long.”

The Queen immediately replied, “Alright. Mister, follow me.” Then she led Zhao Hai and the Elders to the back of the Great Hall before she rode on a voiceless soundbird and flew directly to the Tree of Life’s cave.

After arriving inside the cave, Zhao Hai didn’t hesitate as he placed the Tree of Life directly into the pool. Upon seeing that the tree was healthier than before, the Elves couldn’t help but cheer once more.

Zhao Hai smiled and then turned to the Queen, “Your Majesty, the Tree of Life wasn’t sick, but instead it was invaded by a massive amount of dark energy, causing it to slowly wither. I have used a secret method to remove the dark energies. I also used a potion to allow the Tree of Life to be immune to the damages caused by dark energy. However, you still need to pay attention. The Elf Forest isn’t something that would have that much dark element energy. This matter is very strange.”

After the Queen and the Elders heard Zhao Hai, they couldn’t help but freeze. Then all of them looked at Zhao Hai as the Queen asked, “Mister, are you telling the truth? Was the Tree of Life really invaded by dark energy?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Right. I wouldn’t dare hide this information to Your Majesty. The Tree of Life was really invaded by dark energy, I’m quite assured of this point.”

The Queen looked at the Elders while the Elders looked at one Elder. Then that Elder gave out a long breath as she said, “I didn’t think that this day would come.”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare at the Elders. Seeing Zhao Hai’s confused expression, the Queen gave some context, “Mister, you don’t know this, but the Elves also had our own prophecy. However, our prophecy is different from the Dwarves. This prophecy was written during the time when the first page of our history was being made. However, this prophecy was sealed. Only during a certain encounter would it unlock itself.”

Zhao Hai stared blankly, he didn’t expect that the Elves would have their own prophecy. As soon as he heard the Queen, he had a faint understanding of the matter. He turned to the Queen and said, “Your Majesty, you mean…?”

The Elf Queen nodded, “Right, only when the Tree of Life gets invaded by dark energy would the prophecy unseal itself.”

Zhao Hai knit his brows and said, “But if I didn’t treat the Tree of Life, then how would you know that it has been invaded by Dark Energy?”

The Queen replied, “It can still be found out, but it would take a longer time. When the nine leaves of the Tree of Life turn yellow and it starts to turn black, then it would mean that it has been invaded by dark energy. However, we didn’t manage to think about this line since we were too anxious when the leaves of the tree started to turn yellow. Fortunately, Mister has reminded us. Otherwise, we wouldn’t have found out that the dark energy inside the Tree of Life.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Can Your Majesty allow me to take a look at the prophecy?”

The Queen turned to the Elders, all of them gave a nod. Then the Queen turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, come with me.” Then the group went out of the Tree of Life’s cave and then returned to the Great Hall.

After arriving at the Great Hall, the Queen asked Zhao Hai to take a seat and wait for a moment. Then she went to a room and took out a small wooden box.

The Queen placed the box on a table then gently opened it. What surprised Zhao Hai was the fact that there were no seals nor locks on this box. It looked very ordinary and was very easily opened.

On the other hand, when the Elders saw how easily the Queen opened the box, their complexion couldn’t help but change.

After seeing the expressions on the Elders’ face, Zhao Hai knew that something was going on. He looked at the similarly shocked Queen who quickly calmed herself as she looked at Zhao  Hai, “Mister, in the past, this box wouldn’t open. We have thought of numerous methods for many years, but we haven’t succeeded. We just wanted to take a look at what the prophecy says. This is because the Tree of LIfe is just too important for our race. Even the previous God-ranked Elves were unable to open this box. And for generations, the Elf Queens would come over each month and try to open the box.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then the Queen turned to the Elders and said, “I tried to open it two days ago, but was still unable to do so. I didn’t expect that it would open now.”

Then the Queen carefully opened the box under the stare of everyone in the Great Hall. Since the box still had a huge space inside it, everyone thought that it was empty. However, upon looking closely, everyone became relieved to see a piece of paper on the bottom of the box.

There wasn’t anything wrong with the paper, there was no damage. One should know that this box has been with the Elves since time immemorial. If it was any other paper, it would have rotten a long time ago. However, this paper seemed flawless, it looked at good as new.

The Queen gently took the paper out, revealing the green characters written inside. The Queen looked at the characters and couldn’t help but frown, then she handed the paper over to the closest Supreme Elder.

That Supreme Elder received the paper and slowly read the characters. He couldn’t help but knit his brows as he read it out loud, “When the darkness and light become our enemies, when skeleton and steel fights, and when the heavens and the earth merged, the only person who could save the world will be the one who holds the pure land!”

This prophecy was very short and not as straightforward as the Dwarves, making everyone frown. But when Zhao Hai heard the prophecy, his entire body couldn’t help but tremble. He couldn’t help but admire the person who left the prophecies to the Dwarves and the Elves.

The Elves might not understand the entire prophecy, but Zhao Hai did. In this prophecy, the darkness should refer to the Demons while the light to the Divine Race. In other words, it was when the Demons and the Divine Race became the enemy of the continent. The skeleton and steel should pertain to the undead and the magic cannons. The merging of the heaven and earth should refer to the changing of the laws made by the Divine Race when they descended into the continent. At this time, the only person that can save them would be the one who holds the pure land.

Zhao Hai doesn’t need to think about the last part. The pure land can only mean one thing, the Space!

Aside from the Space, Zhao Hai couldn’t think of any other place that can be called a pure land. Zhao Hai sighed and said, “I think this prophecy is describing the current situation in the Ark Continent. The darkness and light should be the Demons and the Divine Race. The skeletons and steel, to the undead and the magic cannons. But as for the pure land, I am still left unclear.”

As soon as the Queen heard Zhao Hai, her eyes shone as she said, “Mister is too modest, I think the pure land can only refer to the Black Wasteland. At this time, the wasteland has become the safest place in the entire continent. It should fit the title of pure land. It seems like the prophecy is similar to the Dwarves. In other words, mister will be the continent’s savior!”

Zhao Hai stared, he didn’t think that the Queen would connect the Black Wasteland with the pure land. But it wasn’t that strange, after all, the Queen and the others were clueless about the Space. The only thing they were aware of was Zhao Hai’s ownership of the Black Wasteland.

The Black Wasteland has become a shelter for everyone. Moreover, the Black Wasteland has given favorable conditions everybody no matter what race one was. For the Elves, the Black Wasteland can be titled as a pure land.

However, was the prophecy this simple?

Chapter 751: Favoring Two Races

Zhao Hai was currently sitting inside the Space along with Laura and the others. They were outside the villa facing a small table arranged on a meadow. On the table was a pot of tea, and not far from then were two Trees of Life. If it weren’t for the Demons and the Divine Race, then their lives would have been peacefully beautiful.

However, Zhao Hai wasn’t in the mood to enjoy life. In fact, he was thinking deeply into the prophecy of the Elves. After he returned to the Space, the more he ruminated on the prophecy, the more he felt that it wasn’t that simple.

He can understand that the darkness and light referred to the Demons and the Divine Race. However, does the skeleton and steel really refer to the undead and the magic cannons? Zhao Hai thought that this wasn’t the case.

In the end, Zhao Hai was left with no way to find out, so he shook his head and sighed. At this time, Laura looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, don’t think too much about it. Right, the people in Upper Bank City have already reached 8th rank. Do we proceed to the next step of the plan?”

Zhao Hai was taken out of his stupor. He looked at Laura and nodded, “Yes, we should proceed. Who do you think we should upgrade to 9th rank first?”

Laura thought for a moment and said, “If I were to choose, then it should be the Elves.” Lizzy and Megan agreed to this idea. Zhao Hai looked at the three and said, “Why?”

Laura explained, “The Elves are the best in using the blood lightning beads. Their harp archers can display its might far more than the other races could. And since the Divine Race won’t be attacking quite soon, it would be the opportune time to promote the Elves. This way, when the Divine Race did attack, the Elves would be ready to receive them.”

Lizzy and Megan nodded, then Lizzy added, “The weapons we can use against the Divine Race aren’t a lot. Needless to say, the magic cannons are best used by us Humans. As for the blood lightning beads, the Beastmen can only throw the out, which wouldn’t go far, which will affect its power. The Dwarves are similar, they were more suitable for just straight up battle. On the other hand, the Elves were specialists in ranged attacks, especially their harp archers. The blood lightning beads would become deadly weapons in their hands. Continuous ranged attacks while charging and retreating was not something that any ordinary archer could do.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then said, “Alright, then that’s settled. We’ll promote the Elves first, I’ll give them the potion so that they can be promoted as soon as possible. Right, when I went to the Elves, I also told the Queen to refrain from disturbing the Supreme Elders in their cultivation. There are a lot of 9th rank elves, and most of them are in the verge of breaking through to God-rank. Relay this instruction to the other powers as well, making their 9th ranks go all out in cultivation. On the other hand, the 9th ranks that had taken potions needed to be prepared to fight. Only through battle would they be able to get accustomed to their 9th rank strength, and gain a chance of entering God-rank.”

Laura and the others nodded. There were currently plenty of 9th ranks in the continent. However, majority of them were promoted using Zhao Hai’s Space, not through their own effort. Because of this, it would be difficult for them to reach God-rank.

They haven’t experienced the toil of improving slowly, so their mentality still couldn’t catch up to the genuine 9th ranks. If they wanted to break through to God-rank, then there would be two ways. First was to use the Space’s God-rank potion, and the other was to fully adapt to their 9th rank strength through plenty of battles. At that time, they would slowly get accustomed to their strength and begin to gain progress in becoming God-rank. However, the latter method won’t be that easy.

Zhao Hai had some preference on which races he wanted to promote to God-rank first. They were the Elves and the Fishmen. The Beatmen had fairly the same numerical strength to the Humans while the Dwarves were just innately strong. Because of this, Zhao Hai wasn’t too anxious in promoting their ranks.

The Beastmen, Dwarves, and Humans held a similar weakness, their lives were too short. But this also came with an advantage, this meant that the three races would find that their cultivations were quicker compared to the Elves and the Fishmen.

The lifespan of the Elves and the Fishmen was much higher compared to the other three. This allowed them to accumulate 9th ranks across multiple generations despite the lack in cultivation speed. Although their 9th ranks weren’t as numerous as the Beastmen, Dwarves, and Humans, their experts occupied the top spots in terms of cultivation experience. This caused the two races to have a lot of 9th ranks that were on the verge of becoming God-rank.

On the other hand, although the Beastmen, Dwarves, and Humans had a lot of 9th ranks, they weren’t advanced enough to get to God-rank. Because of this, Zhao Hai settled on the Elves and the Fishmen.

Although it can be said that the first genuine God-rank expert in the continent was humanity’s Origin Sword Saint, one shouldn’t forget that the Origin Sword Saint has been at the peak of the continent for a long time. At the same time, he had also received benefits from the Space. Even if he wasn’t artificially promoted, he still underwent nourishing from the Space’s abundant energy, something that was completely lacking in the Ark Continent. The Origin Sword Saint, although a genuine God-rank, was just lucky to encounter the Space.

On the other hand, the Elves and the Fishmen didn’t cultivate in the Space, but they still held strength comparable to the Origin Sword Saint.

At this point, turning average people in the continent into 9th ranks wasn’t that difficult for Zhao Hai. The reason that he wanted to limit the number of 9th ranks was because he didn’t want them to think that obtaining the rank was too easy. Easily obtainable things aren’t seen as valuable.

Moreover, he didn’t want to use human-wave tactics in dealing with the Demons and the Divine Race. If they use this method, then nobody would be left in the continent after expelling the Demons and the Divine Race.

Therefore, Zhao Hai can only make God-ranks en masse at this point. Only through numerous God-ranks can the Ark Continent have the qualification of waging war with the Divine and the Demon Realms.

After discussing the matter with Laura and the others, Zhao Hai went out of the Space. In his hand was a big red bottle containing Blood Pond water. This bottle was to be given to the Elves so that they can reach 9th rank at the shortest period of time. After Zhao Hai arrived at the city, he immediately summoned the various leaders to the mansion. The people in the city were already accustomed to Zhao Hai’s appearance and disappearance. Because of this, they weren’t very disgruntled about sudden summons. They knew that Zhao Hai was busy, a lot busier compared to them.

After the group arrived at the battle room, Zhao Hai had them sit down before he said, “You’re now 8th rank experts. And as long as you take this potion, then you would reach 9th rank.” Then Zhao Hai gestured towards the blood red bottle on the table, causing the eyes of the group to shine.

After looking at their expressions, Zhao Hai continued, “I know that you all wanted to reach 9th rank. However, you cannot take this potion at the same time.” Upon hearing Zhao Hai, the people in the room couldn’t help but gawk. However, they quickly understood the reason. The Divine Race would make their move soon. If all of them were to cultivate simultaneously at this time, then there would be nobody left to defend when the attack came. Because of this, the group immediately gave an understanding nod.

Seeing that the group understood, Zhao Hai felt relief, then he said, “Once you take this potion to become 9th rank, becoming a God-rank expert would become much more difficult. Relying on this potion to become 9th rank will make it hard to adjust one’s own strength. Only after plenty of battles will you start to see the road to God-rank. Can all of you understand?”

The group nodded, if they can sit in this room, then this meant that they weren’t fools. They knew how the slow cultivations was, even cultivating from 6th to 7th rank was difficult. There was needless to say about 9th rank to God-rank.

Then Zhao Hai continued, “In the present situation, I can only provide 9th rank potions. When my research on God-rank potions are done, then I will proceed to help you.” The group lightly chuckled, they didn’t believe that Zhao Hai could research God-rank potions so easily. In their minds, this was close to impossible.

Zhao Hai didn’t mind their laughter, then he said, “I brought this 9th rank potion in order to make the Elves rank up first. What do all of you think?” The people in the room stared, then turned their head to the handsome but cold-faced Elf. As soon as the Elf heard Zhao Hai, his ice-cold expression couldn’t help but freeze.

After seeing their reaction, Zhao Hai didn’t wait for them to ask. He immediately said, “I decided to give the potions to the Elves first because they are the most efficient in using the blood lightning beads. Everyone should know about how powerful the beads were. Normal archers simply aren’t able to fire this bead, only the Elves are able to. Once the Elves reach 9th rank, then their strengths would undergo a qualitative leap, which would supplement the blood lightning beads even more. Even when faced with the Divine Race, they would still be able to hold on.”

When they heard Zhao Hai, the group couldn’t help but think. It didn’t take too long before everyone agreed. In the hands of the Elves, the blood lightning beads were indeed extremely lethal. If they wanted to utilize the blood lightning beads as much as possible, then promoting the Elves first would be a good choice.